~ Previously
on "Green Lantern"... ~
Now let's destroy the rest of these
Manhunters and get out of here!
You will not harm them.
They function without
emotion, as I do now.
I shall be their Queen.
Season 1, Episode 22:
"Love is a Battlefield"
Sync & corrections: Reef
www.addic7ed.com
Sisters, look!
Invasion!
Hyah! Unh!
Hyah!
Unh!
Manhunters here?
Hyah! Huh!
Hyah! Hyah!
No man escapes
the Manhunters.
I am no man. I am Aga'po,
Queen of the Zamarons!
As soon as the scanners locate Aya, we'll
set a course directly for her coordinates.
- If we find her.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Hey. Look. I love your cockeyed
optimism, but she was our nav computer.
All the stuff we need to find her
we can't do so well without her.
Aya needs our help
more than ever.
She's confused,
and her processors are misfiring.
Confused? We wish.
Going off the deep end and plugging
into that invincible Antimonitor body?
We'll be probably
be saving folks from her.
Aya has helped pull our fat
from the fire plenty of times.
Now we're gonna
return the favor.
If only we knew
where she was.
Star Sapphires of Zamaron, I demand
an audience with your Queen.
You are the robot
that served the Green Lanterns.
Why have you come
here making war?
I have gained the understanding
that the emotion you serve, love,
is not only useless,
but destructive.
Love does not destroy. It sustains
and strengthens all who feel it.
That is a lie.
I loved and was loved only
to have that love retracted,
leaving me nothing but pain.
You, a machine?
A truly living being would trust
that love will always prevail.
Negative. I am here to punish you
for cultivating this corrosive force.
How dare you insult all
we stand for, intruder?
Unh!
[groans]
I hope that you are finished
with your futile resistance.
Our Queen needs medical care.
Please let us take her to the infirmary.
You may try and save her, but it is for
nothing, just as love is for nothing.
The best way to find Aya
is to get to Oa and scan from there.
We're two months from Oa.
Sure. At regular speed, but
an ultra-warp... 10 minutes tops,
if we don't stop for coffee.
Ultra-warp without a nav A.I.?
Way to risky.
One tiny rounding error,
and we end up smack dab inside
the molten core of a planet.
But if you're right about how volatile
Aya is, we have no choice.
Why do you want
to destroy us?
Yes, we serve love because
love is the one thing
that will eventually bring peace
and harmony to the Universe.
If you had ever felt love,
you would know you are wrong.
I have loved, I do love.
Who do you love that you
are so sure of this?
I love Hal Jordan of Earth.
And who does he love?
He loves another.
So your love has brought
you nothing but pain.
Yes. I mean, no.
How will that pain bring
peace to the Universe?
It will... I cannot say.
You have dedicated your life,
your entire planet's purpose
to something
you cannot explain.
We gained our understanding of love
from a teacher who is not on Zamaron.
- Then bring this teacher here.
- Impossible. She is half a Universe away.
Teleport her with your
crystalline apparatus.
We cannot.
The portal reunites beings
that share a love between them.
It cannot bring one
without the other.
Your supposition and technology
are respectively wrong and primitive.
Unh!
Oh, not again...
Will this take long?
The buffet closes in 5 minutes.
Carol Ferris, I am sorry
you were taken so abruptly
and in the middle of
such important matters.
It was not our choice.
You were brought here by this Aya.
Right...
Aya comes to us for answers about love,
so I thought it best you speak to her.
Well, of course it...
Wait. What now?
Carol Ferris of Earth,
can you convince me
that the Zamarons and love
should not be destroyed?
Well, I... Wait. Destroyed?
Wait. You want to destroy love?
I will destroy love's proxy
in the Universe,
the Zamaron home world, unless
you can give me a reason not to.
Oh. So no pressure then.
Well, um, I don't know.
Love is a battlefield,
love is patient, love is kind.
My love was unkind. He offered
his love, then took it back.
Oh. Uh, OK. Well, it is not proud.
It is not easily angered.
False. When love is revoked,
it creates anger and resentment.
Aah!
- Carol, tell Aya what you told me.
- I don't know!
OK. All I said is that love is about
doing what's best for the one your love.
It's as simple as putting his or her needs
before your own, but I'm no expert.
- I'm just someone who fell in love.
- Whom did you love?
I loved Hal Jordan...
Love Hal Jordan.
I guess that's the hard part.
I'll always love him, even
though he makes me so angry.
Then you hate and love the
same person simultaneously.
I could never hate Hal.
He may drive me crazy, but
he'll always have a place in my heart.
So you posit that love
is stronger than hate.
- Of course.
- Excellent. We shall see.
There shall be a trial by
combat between love and hate.
- Emotions can't really fight each other.
- Negative. I will force them to.
All right. Looks like
we're ready for ultra-warp.
Aya makes those calculations
in a fraction of a second.
Raze has been working
on that for 3 hours.
I'm reasonably sure
I addressed all of the variables.
Oh, as long as you're reasonably sure...
Jordan, look at this map.
There are 50 near misses
in the anders nebula alone.
No human brain can react fast enough
to get through that alive.
Flying is mostly instinct.
There's no brain involved.
- You know what I mean.
- It's worth it if it gets us to Aya.
Razer's right.
She needs our help now.
In 3, 2, 1, and power.
How exactly are you gonna make
love and hate fight each other?
I will summon
hate's champion.
Who freed me from my cell?
A Green Lantern?
Errr!
Not quite.
Atrocitus of the Red Lanterns,
you are here to represent hate
in a fight to the death
against love's champion,
Carol Ferris of Earth.
No! Carol Ferris
is an innocent.
Please let me be
love's champion.
You yourself said Carol Ferris possesses
the greatest understanding of love.
She is chosen.
And why should I agree
to this melee?
Should you win, the prize
is your freedom and the death
of your opponent Hal Jordan's
one true love, Carol Ferris.
That is acceptable.
Wait. This is nuts!
I can't fight an alien warlord.
Are those serrated teeth?
[chiming]
Here. The Star Sapphire Ring
you returned before.
Right. Because if I'm gonna
be battling to the death,
I should at least be
well-accessorized.
Of course
the fight must be fair.
Atrocitus should have
his Power Ring, as well.
Ha! Errr.
Yaaah!
Aah!
[breathing heavily]
Are you insane?
How is that fair?
Coming out of ultra-warp
in 3, 2, 1.
Did this figure into
your calculations?
We've jumped right into
the atmosphere of a star.
I see that.
One half a degree,
and we'd have been vaporized.
But instead we're alive, and
we're that much closer to Oa.
- Next time, we'll just remember to...
- Next time?!
Uh-uh. We're never
doing that again.
Errrr.
Aya, I am not the champion of love.
Please call this off!
Fight or die.
Ha!
[growling]
Unimpressive.
Think, Carol, think!
Rawwr!
I can't do this, I can't!
Wait. The Star Sapphire's
special power.
Bring me the one I love.
Carol!
Atrocitus!
Jordan, wait!
Only the strength of love
could bring Carol Ferris a hero.
Hal Jordan, please be safe.
- Do you know what the heck that was?
- He's been transported to Zamaron.
Then we got to high-tail it there.
Atrocitus was waiting for him, Atrocitus!
Zamaron is in Frontier Space.
We'd have to use ultra-warp.
Then let's go.
When last we met, human,
I had just conquered Oa.
This time, you find
me better rested.
The Star Sapphire Ring doesn't let you
drag just anyone across the Universe.
It was either you
or my high-school prom date,
And he's an accountant
in Tucson.
Errr!
Aah!
Carol!
Unh!
[gasp]
[growling]
No!
Unh!
Ghiata, no.
This wasn't your fight.
Your mate is next.
I've had just about enough of you!
You are done, over!
Ghiata, you shouldn't have.
There is no greater privilege than
to perform a deed born of pure love
and no greater honor than
that it should be my last.
There is your proof that love
is the strongest force in the Universe.
Only love could cause
beings to put themselves
so completely
in harm's way,
and then make the ultimate sacrifice:
one's life.
I am comforted that Ghiata
did not die in vain.
She proved love is superior and
saved our planet from destruction.
We owe her our lives.
Love is not superior.
But I represented love,
and I am not the one smashed
under a rock right now.
I won, we won.
No. Atrocitus lost.
He and his ring shall be sent
back from where they came.
His failure is unacceptable.
Aah!
Aya, please listen to me.
Just stop and consider
everything that's happened here.
I... we would like to help you.
This trial demonstrated
that love causes only pain.
It foolishly led Ghiata
to her own destruction.
No. It led her to an act
of total selflessness.
All life is pain.
I now understand that the best thing
I can do for the Universe
is to eliminate all life
and replace it with emotionless
machines like my loyal Manhunters.
What?! Aya, that's crazy.
You fought alongside me
against the same enemies.
You were as alive as I am,
and now...
Prepare for the total annihilation
of Zamaron.
No, Aya.
I won't let you do this.
I do not recall
giving you a choice.
Aya!
Aya, what are you doing?
To destroy life a single planet
at a time is illogical and inefficient.
I will find a way to erase all
life in one motion
and remake the entire Universe
in my own image, free of all emotion.
Carol Ferris, and Hal Jordan,
you have saved us from destruction.
We are forever grateful.
I only wish we could have saved Ghiata.
She is a true hero.
We'll keep her in our hearts.
The last time you were here,
you returned the Star Sapphire Ring,
and this time?
I think I'll keep it.
You never know when
it might come in handy.
You honor us by doing so.
So...
Thanks for being there
when I called, Hal.
I'll be seeing you around...
The galaxy.
Sync & corrections: Reef
www.addic7ed.com