Jake: Are you guys
ready for this?
Billy: Yes, yes.
Here it comes!
Oh! Oh! Oh! (Chuckles)
(Laughing)
Oh my God!
That's so weird.
Gunderson: Oh!
Oh!
Wow. Why don't we
hang out more often?
I told you he can
still do it. I told you.
All right.
Yes, you can
vomit without
finger penetration.
You're a freak
of nature.
Thank you.
You must be so
proud of yourself.
You say that like
it's no big deal.
Oh, you must be so...
That's not easy to do
by the way.
That actually burned more than
I thought it would.
Billy: That was amazing.
Gunderson: Yeah.
Billy: Ah!
Here he is.
All: Rocks!
Gunderson:
It's a time warp
Billy: Yeah!
Rocks: Hey, we can let go,
we don't...
Gunderson: How are you doing?
Jake: Oh, God.
Look at this we're getting
the band back together.
This is weird.
This is weird, but us.
Holy shit, all right!
Welcome to
my final day in
New York City.
So, if you'll just
follow me, it begins.
Gunderson: Here we go.
Jake: All right.
Hey!
All right.
Billy: Yes. Yeah.
Did you burn your legs out?
Whoo! Let's go
guys! Yeah!
Hey, what'd you think
about to make yourself
throw up?
Uh, the future.
Oh!
Are you gonna
tell him?
Tell me what?
It sucks. Maybe
I'll just bail.
Bail? Bail on
what, Billy?
Billy: You don't
think I should?
You don't think I should?
Guys, what the hell
are you talking about?
Gunderson: You don't wanna go
to work, don't go to work.
Whoa! Work?
You're kid...
Today? You shitting me?
I have to go.
Come on. No, no, no.
Look, like,
yesterday, my partner
cornered me at the...
At the firm and he said
because we have this...
Not today.
It's just gonna be
like, for an hour.
All right. Ready?
Hold on. Hold on.
Three, two, one, go. Go!
Oh! Not even close.
Not even close.
Oh!
I wasn't looking.
Did you see?
I'm sorry, ladies,
are you missing
a little boy?
Okay...
Is this little
boy yours?
Okay.
He's not yours?
He's just following us.
We don't know
whose he is.
I have to pee.
Oh, God I have to pee.
Could be a different city.
Correct. Yeah.
So, even if you're clothed
when you have an erection
exactly.
Yes.
That's out and greasy.
Okay.
Up to two is this?
Jake: All right. All right.
Time to start drinking.
260 blocks,
the entire length
of Manhattan,
my final day in
the city, so...
To one last
great adventure.
Okay, just
real quick.
Does it have to be last?
How about another?
Sure.
You got it.
Really?
Wait a second, you
know what, how about...
It's his toast.
Let him have his toast.
Another in the
long series of...
All right, fine.
In a long series
of adventure.
(Stammers) Maybe just...
How about one?
To coming
and semen.
You got it.
I like it.
I'll drink to that.
To coming and semen.
Yeah.
And all the joy
they provide.
Rocks: Yeah? Yeah.
Oh wow!
Did you hold up?
It's like, it's like giving
head to a fine gentleman.
(Chuckles)
Give me that.
Billy: All right.
Ah!
Careful.
Okay.
All right.
We gotta get
moving, guys,
this island's not
gonna walk itself.
260 blocks.
(Car horns blaring)
Jake: All right,
now is as good
a time as any.
A robber walks
into your house.
All: Oh.
That's what I'm
talking about. Robber
walks into your house,
says, Sophie's choice,
you gotta pick one or
I'll shoot you in the face.
This is just
occurring to me,
but why is he a robber?
Uh, you meet the
love of your life...
I mean, what's he robbing?
You of your time.
This woman is
perfect. She's like.
An 11 out of 10.
All right. She got this
incredible body and
the sex is great.
Intelligent.
Is that
intelligent sex?
Don't worry
about it, you're
never gonna have it.
I'm gonna go on.
All right, so time comes
in the relationship,
about six
months in...
Where it's time to
meet her family, okay?
So you all decide
to go away to
a little county house,
just you and her
and her folks,
for about
two weeks.
But you all share
one bathroom.
That's important.
All right, now
for the entire time
you're there, remember,
two weeks, long time.
Every time you have
to take a shit,
you do it...
(Clears throat)
You have to take
a shit in the bathtub.
(Chuckles)
All right, okay.
Boom!
Okay, all right, wait
I'll tell you what I'd do.
I would just hold it in.
You can't.
You can't hold it in.
Why not.
Firstly, it's impossible.
Secondly, it's
against the rules.
And thirdly after you
leave that dookie
in the bathtub,
you have to
deny it forever.
You can never say
that it was you.
Wow.
Billy: Is this a museum?
Rocks: Well, that ends the
relationship, so fine.
Not necessarily, I mean,
remember, this is like,
the perfect woman,
so she might
forgive you
Billy: Got it.
Shit down the drain.
Billy: What? I'm just trying
to understand the parameters
of the scenario.
Rocks: What's
option number two?
Jake: Uh, right.
Option two.
Okay, so...
For the next year,
starting tomorrow,
everywhere
you go, you,
and only you are
responsible for taking
two cars.
(Chuckles)
So, the logistics...
(Man shushes)
Uh, so think
about it.
If you need to go
to work, then you
need to drive there,
then you have to
somehow get back,
walk or cab or something.
And then you have
to take another car,
then you're there.
Can you...
No, you can't walk.
Can...
And no you can't
take the subway.
Okay? You can't tow
the car. You can't get
a ride. Nothing like that.
Okay.
Uh...
What kind of gas
mileage do these get?
What is the
matter with you?
How do you clothe
and feed yourself
seriously?
How are you
such an asshole?
Practice.
Okay.
Yeah?
All right. I, okay
option two is
take two cars and...
Option one is
fortnight of in-law
bathtub shitting.
Yeah. Okay.
Not even a question.
I'm gonna go
option two.
Uh.
Take the two cars...
Why is that not a question?
'Cause I can't even
imagine what Emma's
parents would do.
I don't even
wanna see it.
Yeah.
If I was to shit
in their bathtub.
It's true and she
shouldn't forgive you.
Nightmare.
No.
Shouldn't...
Where is your
sense of romance?
I mean this is the
love of your life
we're talking about.
Yeah but the love
of your life should
leave you
if you defecate
in the bathtub.
You're...
Don't knock freestyle
defecation, man.
Okay, so that's
what you would do.
You're a bathtub,
bathtub kinda guy?
I'm not knocking it
I just wanna be
honest about it.
I'm just... I'm not
you don't have to
lie about it
playing this game
I find it childish
and silly.
(Chuckles)
Classic gunderson.
Do they have
museums in Ohio?
Oh fuck.
(Chuckles)
Fuck you.
You couldn't
help yourself.
No, do you...
This is a
dumb question.
Is that a serious question?
What museums are in Ohio?
Uh, the...
Woman: Excuse me.
Sorry.
We'll be quiet.
Yeah.
What is wrong with you?
Who? Which one?
Don't put your bare
feet on the bench
up like that.
Come on.
She's right.
Put it down.
Sorry. Sorry.
People actually have
to sit there after you.
I got it.
Put your feet down.
I gotta put
my socks on.
Woman:
It's disgusting.
Okay.
You've been
moving around
and sitting there like
a child for 10 minutes.
You're just
incredibly rude.
Okay, that's called
cognitive dissonance.
Yeah. Ding ding.
I said, excuse me.
Yeah, okay.
And I said that's what
we call cognitive dissonance.
Right, and then I put
my sock on. That's
what happened.
So, we've have
covered everything.
Come on, Barb.
Gunderson: Oh, don't
drag Barbara into this.
Billy: Yeah.
I'm gonna request that
you boys be thrown out.
No.
Wait, wait,
no, no, no.
No don't do that.
All: No.
Why don't we just
step outside.
You me,
tweety bird there.
Let's take you out
for a nice juicy steak.
Yeah.
(Chuckles)
Rocks: We're young.
We're flirty.
We're nervous.
I'm nervous around
older women.
Because I assume
you're older,
I'm not sure.
Gunderson:
We could all just
have a little fun.
So let me ride the
lightning of your love.
I would definitely
get that little canary
to sit on my finger.
Come on.
(All chuckle)
Fuck you!
All: Oh!
Shhh!
You're in a museum.
Have some respect.
Excuse me?
(Chuckles)
You really should
get your feet off there.
Oh, dude.
For real it's disgusting.
How old are you?
She's got a great point.
Really? Okay.
Yeah.
(Flushing)
(Shaking permanent marker)
Billy, let me ask
you a question.
Do you have a single
independent thought
in that head of yours?
Why are we friends
with you again?
Yeah, why are we even
friends with you again?
Gunderson: Come on,
you love me.
I'm an anarchist,
but I'm not a dangerous one.
I don't accept that
there's any order
in the cosmos
but I do want
the trains to run.
I mean, I'm just looking
at the two of you and...
You do everything
he does, like,
you're just...
You're his shadow.
I mean why did you
order an egg cream?
What are you intimating?
I love egg creams.
Why else would I order...
Delicious.
Yes, they are
delicious. Yeah.
You love egg creams?
Then tell me,
lover of egg creams,
what's in an egg cream?
Rocks: You don't have
to answer that.
What?
No, he does.
What's, what's in
an egg cream?
It's fine. All right,
all right I'm gonna
tell you.
Okay. First of all
there is chocolate.
Cream.
Chocolate syrup.
Syrup and there
are eggs in there.
Seltzer. Seltzer.
Rocks: Seltzer. Seltzer.
Billy: And there's seltzer.
Whole milk...
Uh, there's...
You know...
You know what,
there are... who cares
what is in the egg...
I don't...
All that matters
is that they're refreshing
and delicious.
Right.
Couldn't agree more.
Okay?
(Train whistle sounds)
Gunderson: Look no one
wants to stop you from going
and helping your dad,
but why are you
staying there?
You don't know anything
about rubber and plastic.
Jake: Ach, what's there
to know. And that's not
the point anyway.
The point is that it's
a stable career and
that's what I need.
You know what else
is stable? Death.
You should try that.
Gee whiz, thanks, buddy.
That makes me feel
a whole lot better.
You're welcome.
Jake: What do you want
me to do? My dad needs me,
you know.
He asked for my help
and I'm gonna help him.
If I don't go now,
he's gonna have to sell.
Gunderson: I guess
I didn't expect you
to give up.
Billy, maybe...
Who said anything
about giving up?
My work is still up
at starving arts.
You know, like...
I can still paint from
wherever I am, including Ohio.
You know, tabatha
thinks it's very sweet.
Oh, so you're taking
advice from your
ex-girlfriend?
Nice.
A friend.
A current friend, as well.
Sure, that's a
sound decision.
Jesus, man there's
only so many times
I can watch my bank account
fall before zero before
I want to kill myself.
You know, I'm in
my thirties...
And I'm moving into
my dad's basement!
Temporarily, I said.
Temporarily.
Yeah, that's what everyone
who moves into their
dad's basement says.
Oh my God!
And 30 years later
they murder someone.
Oh, I get it now.
I get it. So obvious.
Oh. (Chuckles)
You're gonna miss me.
You know me
better than that.
You are.
You're gonna miss me.
Come here. Give me
a goodbye kiss. Huh?
No.
Don't touch me.
You think our facial hair
is gonna stick together
nobody, nobody
likes you.
Like velcro? Baby. Baby.
Gunderson:
Nobody likes you.
Rocks: I, uh...
I have to meet
the baby before we
name him officially.
Okay, no,
I get that but...
But have you
considered Billy?
Yeah, if he's
a humongous pussy.
I'll name him Billy.
Ah, the gallery.
Always look like
a coffee shop to me.
(Chuckles)
Hey, Cece.
Where's my stuff?
Cece: Jake.
Ty didn't call you?
Who, Ty? No. Why?
What wrong?
Let's sit.
Okay.
Uh... (Clears throat)
Mckenze was here.
What? Max mckenze?
He was so drunk.
Oh, he's in town
because um...
'Cause that showing
of his, his early work.
It's going on all week
down in soho.
They have a dj.
And snacks.
Yeah, I know.
He was um...
(Clears throat)
Totally sauced.
And he...
Well, he thought
that you were trying
to copy his style.
The whole New York
nostalgia thing.
What?
I tried to explain
it to him.
Hold on. Hold on.
He thought I was
copying him?
He said that?
He destroyed them.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Who did? Max mckenze
destroyed my paintings?
Jake, I am so sorry.
I am like...
Wait.
Rocks: Feet are
already tired.
Billy: Yeah, I hear you.
I didn't know you
got a tattoo.
Gunderson:
Yes Billy, I have a tattoo.
Just saying for the record,
I did not know
that you did that.
Great story.
(Sighs) Fuck me...
Cece: I saved this
one before he could
slice it up.
But not, not
before he...
Peed on it.
Excuse me?
He what on it?
That's piss?
You're always saying
how you wanted
to collaborate with...
Max mackenze, so...
Now you have.
God, I feel so bad.
He put his paintings
up there specifically
'cause that's where
mckenze got his start.
Really?
Yeah.
We should help him.
Gunderson: You can 't
help a dead man,
as the saying goes.
Billy: That is not
a saying.
Maybe not in
your limited experience.
Guys, he doesn't want
to go back to Ohio.
I mean, he invited tabatha.
Why did he do that?
Masochism.
No, he's just looking
for a reason to stay.
I'm been shaming
the guy all day.
It hasn't made a dent.
The dude is leaving.
No, we can
get him to stay.
Listen, I'm gonna
somehow, I'm gonna
skip this
checkup with Emma.
Can you still get
out of work, Billy?
Yeah, but you told me
not to skip.
I know but
my heart is changed.
No worries.
Done and done.
Okay.
Ooh, and what irrational
foolhardy thing
should I do?
You two could stop
the constant bickering.
We're not
constantly bickering.
Yes we are.
Okay, okay.
You know what guys,
let's uh... let's...
Call it a day.
No.
All: No, no, no.
It's been great that
we got to hang out,
but you're busy,
we're all busy.
No, not anymore. No.
No, no, forget it.
It's been taken care of,
let's keep walking.
Got a really good idea,
I think you'll like it.
Come on, now, Jake.
Yeah?
Absolutely, come on.
Billy: Let's do this.
Okay.
Come on.
Adventure time.
Let's gonna go down
memory Lane.
You're gonna love it.
All right.
Billy: It literally looks
exactly the same.
Hey man, thanks again for,
you know, letting us...
Uh, yeah,
no problem, man.
You guys want
some breakfast or...
Oh, did you
just wake up?
Oh, man remember
those days?
Barely.
(Chuckles) What?
Billy: I had the bed
the other way, but still...
Lotta history
in this room, Alex.
Lot of history.
You know there was
a fire here,
like eight years ago.
Really?
Yeah.
No, there was
no fire. Stop...
Don't start calling
it a fire again. Okay?
Hey, no
bickering, right?
He's just really
sensitive about the fire.
Takes a few minutes,
but it was like,
instantaneous.
Yeah.
This place is so much
smaller than I...
So was there,
like a fire or not?
I try to help.
That's what I do.
I'm a hero.
You know if somebody
else like Jake
had been there,
who know? The whole
place would have
probably burned down.
Okay, there was no fire.
Okay? You destroyed
everything I owned.
Sorry, man.
Billy: With a fire
extinguisher.
Brings up a lot
of old issues.
I almost 100%
sure there was a fire.
If there was a fire,
why wasn't anything
in my room burned at all?
Because I put the fire out.
I prevented your room
from burning.
You're welcome!
Not a single part
of the room, gunderson
was in the least bit charred.
Okay? And yet,
all my photographs
and my books
and my, my computer, my...
Magazine collection,
my mom's prized collection
of presidential campaign
buttons dating back to
grover Garfield
were completely covered
in foam and destroyed.
(Stammers)
It's just a little difficult
to reconcile with this fire
that you so heroically
put out.
I think the important
question is,
who the hell
is grover Garfield?
Okay, I misspoke.
That's not
a president.
It's not
the...
Point.
Hi.
No way.
Oh, yeah. That was here
when we got here.
Huh.
Man: Thought it was
pretty fucking gershwin.
Jake: Yeah,
it's pretty gershwin.
Jake: That's a good
thing, right?
Man: Yeah, I guess.
You know, I feel
like doing something
really dumb.
What do you think?
Oh, I don't know you.
Uh, guys.
Billy: No, no,
I know Mr. Kim.
Larry, sorry.
Yeah, yeah it's just that,
it's just flared up.
It's terrible timing
and I really wanted to come
to work today.
Billy: It's just a general
kind of hurting feeling.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, no, no, no.
It's a urologist...
(Inaudible)
How much for all those?
Five?
How much for everything?
Squirrel and
a hydro post.
It's got a little nut for
a football.
What, rocks
thought it was funny.
(Both chuckle)
Bee in your face.
There's a bee in your face.
Billy: I already have
an appointment.
You don't have
to do that.
It's in the network...
Don't wanna bother
your friend on a Saturday.
Rocks: There he is.
Jake: Hey.
What do you think?
Hey.
I like it.
Jake: Yeah?
You gonna leave it here?
Yeah.
This is kind of
a symbolic bathroom for me.
(Clears throat)
Truth be told tabatha
and I actually...
Had sex in there.
Go on.
It was super uncomfortable.
But, you know I've
actually thought about it a
lot about it since then and...
Even though it was awful,
honestly awful.
Disgusting...
(Flushing)
I think it was maybe
one of the most
enjoyable sexual
encounters of my life.
In retrospect.
It's so hard to pee
with a boner.
(Chuckles)
I'm sorry about that.
God to say it out loud,
it sounds so uh, trite.
Sex in the bathroom?
Jake: Yeah.
No, no it sounds
all right.
I uh... I need
to tell you something.
When I saw
tabatha...
She...
At Ted and Audrey's?
Yeah, she told me
that her and...
You know,
what's-his-fuck broke up.
Sebastian?
Yeah.
What are you
talking about?
Are you fucking
with me?
Tabatha's single now?
Currently single?
Yeah.
Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on.
And you found out
this when?
On Wednesday?
And now it's Saturday.
I thought she
was coming
to the walk,
she said you invited her
so I just figured you...
I wanted...
Are you fucking...
You know what?
No, I glad I
didn't know that.
Wednesday was...
That was bad for me.
No, it is actually
good timing.
This is fucking
terrible timing.
Dude, I'm leaving
tomorrow.
I do not need
to know this now.
Oh, come on, man
this is fucked up.
I mean what am I going
to do with this information?
In fact why didn't
she tell me?
Fuck her!
I didn't mean that.
That was knee-jerk.
That's not me.
She's probably
in pain. Oh God.
I should call here.
No, no, no, no, no.
What? I don't understand
what you wanted me to do.
God! Man, you know what
dick move for telling me.
Real dick move.
But I appreciate it.
That took guts.
Should I not have
told you at all?
You should not
have told me at all.
No.
Okay and I apologize.
You should have
told me before.
Okay, then I'm not sorry
and you're welcome.
I can't do
the walk, it's...
No in fact...
You can do the walk,
come on.
Ah! God!
This changes nothing.
You're right.
Right, let's go, tabatha...
Rocks... oh, fuck!
Jake: No and to think that...
For the last three years
she was with Sebastian.
Tristan before that.
Where are the normal
names here?
She's almost literally
been with somebody
every single day
since we broke up
and now that
I have a chance
to be with her, I can't
because I'm leaving
and I'm never going
to see her again.
Okay, well, why
don't we focus
on the walk?
I mean, where
are we going next?
No, I think
Jake's right.
Let's focus on
things that we have
no control over.
Gunderson, will you
look at, look at him.
Okay? Look at this
little face.
Cant' we, can't you be
supportive of this face
for once in your life?
I've been supportive.
Hey, who put the fire
out in your room?
Okay, for the last time
stop calling it a fire.
Then what should
I call it? A conflagration?
A holocaust?
Here we go.
Just drop it.
How dare you!
Let it go.
We lost... no.
I will not...
We lost great aunts and...
You didn't lose
anyone at all.
Well, not directly but...
Rocks: I don't know
what that means.
Indirectly,
almost surely...
Okay, all right.
Fair. Fair.
Jake, I got a call
from work,
and one of my teachers
got food poisoning
for like,
the umpteenth time,
and I have to go in
for just an hour,
I couldn't get anyone
to cover, it's on the way.
It'll just be an hour.
You guys can come.
No.
Are you fuckin'
kidding me?
It's on the way.
No! Dude, not now!
Now's the worst possible
time. I've got an
existential crisis afoot.
You don't mean
existential.
I don't even know
if I mean afoot.
What does afoot mean?
Rocks: Pythagorean's theorem,
you guys.
It's super cool.
You're gonna have...
Five to seven
questions on it.
On the test,
depending on which
one you get.
So, I wanna go over it
and make sure we all...
Billy: Did you
just look at my test?
Gunderson, stop
looking at my test.
Gunderson: I'm not
looking at your test.
I've already done
number 21.
I bet you forgot
about the three quadratics,
gunderson.
Gunderson: I bet you forgot
that you're a college graduate
and this is pointless.
Billy: It won't be
pointless when I beat you.
Gunderson: Yes, it will.
Hey, is he almost
done with his class?
(Phone ringing)
Is that Emma?
I'm just disappointed.
I know.
Emma: I just...
I can't believe you
would miss one of
the last appointments
before the baby
would come.
I'm very sorry.
And to go out drinking
with your friends...
It's just such
a fucking cliche and...
Okay.
Oh my God! I sound
like I'm one of those
bitchy annoying girls.
Well, you have every
right to me mad, okay.
You do. I'm sorry.
I absolutely
shouldn't have missed
the appointment.
No, you should not
have missed
the appointment.
But it was not about
just drinking with
my friends, okay, it wasn't.
We are trying to get
Jake to stay.
You know if he has
a good time today,
he might actually do that,
it could go either way.
Really?
Yes.
And you know between
Billy and gunderson,
he's our only viable
babysitting option.
(Chuckles)
Oh.
Okay. I can't
argue with that.
So listen...
At the appointment
today...
Doctor leponis and I discussed
the birth plan...
Yeah.
You know,
and who's gonna
be in there when
it all goes down and...
I decided that I want
to keep the participants
to a minimum.
Fine. Yeah.
Okay, it'll be
just... just us.
Cozy.
No, I...
I mean not you.
She said that it's actually
really common
for women to not want
their partners in there...
Are you kidding?
For that. I mean...
God! I don't want
you to see that.
You just decided this?
Well, marcel, I...
You know that I've been
really stressed out
about this. I'm scared.
I mean, what if you
don't want me after that?
Are you kidding me
right now?
You're not one who
has to have a baby
coming out...
Of your vagina, okay?
Yes, I do realize that.
I understand how
children are born.
Look, how would
you feel, if I brought
a bunch of strangers
into the bathroom to watch you
do whatever it is you do
in there for 45 minutes.
That's not something
that you want people to see.
What are you
talking about?
How is me being there
for the birth of our son
remotely like
you bringing in strangers
to watch me take a dump?
Okay, I get that
that's not a great analogy,
now, okay.
No, it's not a great
analogy at all.
It's not even a
mediocre analogy.
I don't, I don't even
understand. Am I...
Am I the one going
into the bathroom?
Am I bringing
in the strangers?
No, you're the stranger.
(Sighs)
I didn't mean
it like that.
Yeah, you did.
Oh shit!
(Students chatter)
Billy: Okay, I don't know who
any of you are...
Billy: Inside voices, please.
Is there a Renee here?
Tasha? Is that right?
All right. Kuyken...
Kuykendall? Is that you?
Wait, what's
your question?
I don't know
what a function is.
What is a function?
How come you
don't know the answer?
Well, I...
Guys, can you?
Look, none of this
matters in the real world.
And I don't even
teach here.
Is that lady
Mr. reznowski's wife?
No, that is his fiancee,
but they love...
So his kid's gonna
be a bastard?
(Chuckles) Yes.
What are they
arguing about?
Jake: Ah, good question.
You know, actually French
playwright Jean anouilh
put it best.
Okay, my friend
is having an
existential crisis, please.
He does not
mean existential.
You know what,
you need to know this.
You really do.
So write his down
if you have to.
Life is not gonna
turn out the way
you planned it.
That's the bottom line.
Okay. And here's
another piece of advice.
Don't invest in anyone.
You probably
meet a guy,
and he's gonna
be great.
And you'll love him
and you give
everything to him
and just when
you think it's perfect...
He's gonna take
your heart,
he's gonna put it
in a blender and
he's gonna press frappe.
Okay. Then he's gonna
pour it down the toilet
and if that
wasn't bad enough,
you're gonna jump on
into that toilet after
and try and grab it
and you're gonna come out
the other side covered
in piss and shit
like Tim Robbins at the end
of Shawshank redemption
and if you haven't
seen that movie,
then I cannot help you.
Okay? But here's
the good news.
Okay, because
at the end of all that,
the next thing you got
marked on your calendar
is a probably painful,
inevitable death.
Gunderson:
So, all right,
class dismissed.
Right, why don't
you figure this out...
Hey, em.
Bye, guys.
(Sighs)
Decisions. That's the
big thing right now.
We're just having all
these arguments about...
You know what color
the baby's room should be.
Yellow or cream,
things like that.
Yellow.
Rocks: And I find myself
talking all these hard lined
positions really just to
argue, I mean...
I don't care what color
the actual baby's room is,
'cause in the end
it doesn't matter.
Billy: It should be yellow.
But I hear myself arguing
that one color
will literally lead
the child becoming
president and the other one's
gonna make him a murderer.
Same thing.
Yeah, it's totally
irrational, all right,
I mean...
Nobody actually
remembers what color
their baby room was.
Yellow.
Really?
Yeah.
Explains a lot.
It was awesome.
Billy: What are we
doing here? Is this
a planned stop?
I hate cathedrals!
Billy: Ugh!
And the answer is,
back in 1895,
"construction
of the cathedral
"was halted due
to a labor dispute
"that resulted in..."
(Clicks tongue) Fuck it.
No. (Chuckles)
Put myself to
sleep with that.
I apologize...
What happened
to labor dispute?
Oh, who cares. Fuck it.
You know. (Sighs)
You know what,
teaching here
is one of the...
One of the great
achievements of mine
in New York.
Maybe the only
great achievement.
That's not true.
That's not true,
come on.
It's true! No,
honestly. I think
I did about the only thing.
No, that's
not true.
Gunderson: None
of your students have
amounted to anything. So...
Yeah.
Doesn't really count
as an achievement.
Billy: Gunderson,
come on...
Rocks: Yeah, you know,
like, great achievements.
No.
Rocks: I mean, that's it.
No, but...
What about that show
you had in New Jersey?
Yeah...
That was awesome.
It was in New Jersey
but still...
You had one in staten...
You had a thing
in staten island.
I mean, if
it's staten island,
yeah.
It's something.
Gunderson: Remember,
you almost sold
a painting on the subway?
Billy: Oh, yeah!
No, no, no.
The guy almost
stole the painting
on the subway.
Billy: Oh.
Gunderson: But still,
he liked it.
Yeah, I guess.
I mean,
people who are
really excited...
You gotta start
somewhere.
That's true,
I guess.
It's tough.
I don't know.
It's good.
This is actually...
Kind of makes me feel good.
I love this place.
Really, 'cause
these are garbage.
And your fridge
is gonna be
filled with that.
Rocks: Yeah, I hope.
How do you pretend
to like that?
That's awful.
I don't have
to pretend.
That's a beauty.
I mean, I...
I genuinely
like this.
You're not understanding what
this kid did with space,
negative space.
Uh...
Gunderson: Now, I understand
why you like Jake's stuff.
Hey...
Is it about the money?
Does your dad need...
I mean...
Is that why
you're leaving?
If it is,
I'm more than happy...
I don't want
your money.
I'm just saying,
I'll give you a little...
I'm not your
charity case, okay?
Jacob.
I was wondering
if you could clear up
something for me.
Weren't you planning
on breaking up
with Emma
before you found out
she was carrying
your demon seed?
I... (Stutters)
No, man, I...
Really,
you weren't?
No, we were gonna have
a bit of a conversation
that, you know,
could've pre-empted...
Good.
But...
And my son.
Right, yeah.
But the fact...
But, I...
I don't... we were
definitely not gonna
break up, no.
Not... not for sure.
Hmm.
What's the latest?
Well, my partner
at the firm
has actually set up
an appointment
with his
urologist friend
for me today.
Right.
So I am telling him
that the rash
has spread to my legs
and I'm having
trouble walking.
Ah. Oh.
Ergo, I won't be
able to go
to his doctor.
Yeah. (Sighs)
Well...
Sounds medically dubious.
Yeah.
(Sighs)
Hey, do you think
that the guys
hate me?
Yeah.
No, seriously.
I mean, the whole
lawyer thing,
the money,
it just
feels different
than when we were all
unemployed and broke.
Yeah, you don't wanna
go back to that, though.
Well, I mean, do I?
Remember how much
you used to give blood?
Yeah...
It's not safe.
Yeah, but it was...
It was sort
of exciting.
I guess.
I keep thinking about
what the most
important thing is
for my son, what I...
What I want
for him the most,
besides, obviously
wanting him to be...
Healthy, easy-going...
Yeah, sure.
I think it's just
for him to be confident
and not worrying
all the time,
about what
everyone else thinks.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I like that.
I'm sorry
for your loss.
(Sighs) My God...
The thing is, that I can't
really talk to my friends
about it, you know.
They're good guys, but...
(Sighs) It's...
We're not really
the kind of guys
who can, you know,
open up and...
(Clears throat)
And really, I'm sorry,
is there meant
to be, like, a booth
or a partition,
or wall, or...
That's confession
in a catholic
church, Jacob.
We are episcopalian.
Sure. Okay.
(Clears throat)
Just kind of feels
weird talking
to someone I can't see.
I feel that way
every time I talk
to God.
(Laughs) Zing.
Not really.
No. I guess not.
Well, I may as well
just dive into it, then.
I think I'm still in love
with tabatha. (Laughs)
There it is.
I am.
And I also know
that my dad needs me.
That's important.
Especially now.
He's sick.
But I just... I can't
shake this feeling
that maybe leaving
is the wrong thing
to do.
Let me tell you this.
God very rarely
limits us to two options.
In fact, our choices
are endless, infinite.
But it is up to us
to make one.
I would love to be able
to tell you what to do.
But I'm an episcopalian,
not a catholic priest.
Right.
I get it. (Laughs) Okay.
You know what,
just before I...
I'm not 100% on it.
So, when you
say "infinite"
you know, there...
How many
is that exactly?
It's like with Jesus.
Okay, hold on. (Laughs)
Accepting we
all know how that
turned out for him.
You know.
It's probably not
the best example,
that's all.
Go on.
I tell you what,
maybe it's time
that you convert
some of that
analytical energy
into kinetic energy.
Right.
Rocks: (Sighs)
Why is he
taking us east?
(Children shouting
indistinctly)
Gunderson: Maybe
he's gonna go
to the bathroom.
I need a cupcake.
I'm out of breath.
What the fuck is this?
Rocks: It's a birthday
party for children.
Goddamn it!
Hey. (Laughs)
Jake! (Laughs)
Yeah! Hey.
Hey. Hey, raja, ankur.
Marty.
Wait. Did you finish
your walk?
No, not yet.
We will.
I just wanted to...
Have you got
a second?
Could I talk to you
for a second?
Uh, yeah.
Okay. (Laughs)
Of course.
Come on.
No, I'm
not cheating!
Billy: I'm serious.
I cannot fucking
believe this.
I haven't been...
No, I abandoned
work for this
and now, Jake just
diverts the whole thing
for his ex-girlfriend?
It's unconscionable!
I wanna fly! I wanna fly!
I wanna fly!
Oh! Hey, there.
Sorry, little fella,
but we're all
out of pixie dust.
Oh. Oh my...
Oh, my God!
He just licked me!
Yeah! Get him!
Get him!
Why did you lick me,
you little monster?
Hey! I gotcha!
Hands! Stop it!
Stop it!
Ricky, Ricky, Ricky,
go, go over there.
Over there.
Ugh!
That kid is awful!
Oh.
Kid is my son.
Oh! Hey, friend.
Guys.
Rocks: Hey, Zeke,
how you doing?
(Laughs)
Whoa! Blast from
the past...
What are you guys
doing here?
Jake came
to visit tabatha.
We're on a bit of a...
Nostalgia tour.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I thought nostalgia
was supposed to be
a pleasant thing.
(Children screaming
and laughing)
Right. So...
Yeah.
So you have to shit
in a bathtub?
Yeah, two weeks,
and you can't
tell anyone.
You have to
deny it forever.
Yeah...
You know,
I forgive that.
Really?
Yeah! For the love
of my life, yeah. Yeah.
Wow!
Wow.
Yeah. But that does not
give you permission
to shit in Chuck
and Joyce's bathtub.
Do not do it.
Oh, bummer.
Yeah. (Sighs)
And as far as
the second part...
Hey, should I stay
in New York?
Do you think?
Am I doing
the right thing by...
I gotta get back
to the party.
Hmm.
You still got it.
Yeah.
(Baby wailing)
(Man shushing)
Man: Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
(Baby's crying continues)
Man: You got a problem?
You got an issue?
Do you have
a problem?
All right, I'm gonna
give it a shot.
Oh. Yeah, sure.
She doesn't
like men, so...
Oh. Let's see
how this works.
(Stops wailing)
There you go. Yeah.
(Clears throat)
There you go.
Kids like me.
Yeah.
I don't really
like them.
But what are you
gonna do?
Don't ruin
her life.
Ah.
Yeah.
(Wailing)
Thanks.
Okay.
Argh! Go!
Whoo! (Screams)
(Screams)
(Laughing)
Terrible choice.
Gun!
(Shrieks) It's Melanie!
(Laughs) Melanie ortmeyer?
Well, Melanie MacDonald now.
I thought that was you.
You're that girl
that doesn't
listen, right?
I can't believe it!
So what are
you doing here?
Living a
personal nightmare.
This is such a coincidence.
You know, I just
had a dream about you.
Who cares!
God! You know,
I haven't seen you
since teach for America.
Yeah.
I was a fucking
disaster, right?
You don't really wanna
have this conversation.
Oh!
Do you?
You're here with Jake.
I saw him, too.
It's just like
old times, huh?
Not at all.
I've got my little
rugrat running around
here somewhere.
I don't give a shit.
You have stupid glasses.
You never
would've have thought
I'd be a mom, right?
I thought you'd
be dead by now.
I feel so old
just saying it
to you...
Yeah, same to you later.
(Gasps) Oh. Bye!
(Screams)
Ahh! Why is this
happening to me?
Help!
(Screams) You fucking
bit me
(laughs) Yeah.
Yeah. Get him.
Oh, my God!
It's a nightmare!
(Laughing) Yes...
Billy: Oh, God!
Get off. Get off of me!
Um...
Do you have
another second just to...
It'll be quick.
Oh. I can't.
Well, we can. We did.
So we've already
kind of, you know, done.
It's been did. So...
I... I can't...
I'm still
in love with you.
So...
Yeah.
I'll you get
back to the pixie
dust station.
Okay.
Don't say it
unless you mean it.
Okay, then, I'm still
in love with you.
Tabatha...
(Chuckles) Look.
My parents are having
one of their pre-show
dinner parties
in, like,
in an hour and a half?
Why don't
you come by?
We'll talk.
Yeah. Done.
(Laughs) All right.
Look, I... I'm just
warning you.
I've been crying
for, like, three days,
on and off.
Mostly, on.
So I don't know
if this is nostalgia or...
I just...
Come at your own peril,
that's what I'm saying.
Understood.
(Whispers) Okay,
no more talking.
We'll talk about it
on the way over.
(Muffled) Okay.
(Chuckles)
Great.
Oh. Can I
meet you there?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Fuck...
How quickly...
What is the vaginal
rejuvenation like?
(Laughs) Good question.
That I don't
actually know.
Because Noreen
had a c-section.
Oh, okay.
Right, so it was fine.
Or it would've been fine
if we have had any desire
to have sex afterwards.
(Groans)
Do you remember
boys' breakfast
every Saturday?
Yeah.
God.
The only way
that a girl
would get invited
was if she'd slept
with one of us
the night before.
Bunch of assholes!
(Laughs)
Anyway,
boys' breakfast turns
into couples' brunch,
which eventually
becomes birthday parties.
Completely elaborate,
unnecessarily complicated
birthday parties
at which I am dressed
as a pirate.
(Inhales)
And somebody's gotta
take you to breakfast.
I haven't
had pancakes
in eight years.
I'll make you pancakes.
Shit!
What? I'm
doing it now.
Now.
You're doing it now?
Dad!
Yes, I...
I'm getting
the dessert.
What do you mean,
what have
I been doing?
I'm... I've
been playing
with children!
(Ricky screaming)
Now!
Ricky, not now.
Ricky,
that's enough.
Now!
Woman: Before the party
that I organized...
Dad!
I planned this!
Oh. Okay.
Guys, I need
to tell you something.
(Cell phone rings)
Billy: Oh,
look who it is!
Jake, it's my partner.
You know the guy
I've been lying to all day
so that we could
go out and have
an adventure,
that guy,
remember that?
Yeah, I do.
Unconscionable.
Yeah, I know,
I got the files.
You know what,
I'm actually
on my way
to the doctor's
right now.
He's gotta go.
Fuck you!
Oh.
Gunderson,
what the fuck!
What the fuck!
(Mocks) "What the fuck!"
This... no,
this is not a joke,
okay? This is my job.
Oh, it's not
a joke?
No.
Is this a fucking joke,
"this is a tattoo?"
All right, guys.
You know what,
I told you before that
I didn't know
that you got a tattoo.
Jake: Okay.
Gunderson: Oh, you didn't
know I got a tattoo.
Guys.
Billy: That is correct.
For one second,
if I could just...
And anyway mine
is completely different.
Rocks.
What? Just leave
me out. What...
Rocks!
Yeah, fine.
He knew.
Rocks!
When he found out
about your "this is not
a tattoo" tattoo,
he decided
it'd be ironic
if he got a "this is
a tattoo" tattoo.
It doesn't matter.
Who cares?
That's not ironic,
you imbecile.
Yeah, it is!
No, it's not!
You have a tattoo
that says it's a tattoo.
That's the exact
opposite of what
"ironic" means!
Yeah, but that
is the ironic part.
No, it's not.
Yes, that's what
I was going for.
You're a fucking idiot.
Fucking stop it, okay?
Gunderson,
you are a shit-face,
you know that?
You're an inconsiderate
shit pile!
All right.
You know what?
I wish that I let
your stuff burn up
in that room.
You fucking...
(Laughing)
Ow!
Cut it out, guys.
Billy: You son of a...
So civil.
What are you doing?
Stop. Enough. Billy!
Jake: Leave him alone!
Get off of him!
I will pummel you!
All right. Fine! It was me!
All right, it was me!
I did it.
Not gunderson, me.
It was me!
Stop it!
It wasn't gunderson!
I ruined your stuff!
All right?
(Sighs) I destroyed
your stuff, all right?
I'm sorry.
It's true. It wasn't me.
Jake: I was hammered.
I mean...
I was shit-faced
and I thought
it'd be funny.
I had no idea
that the foam
in those extinguishers
cause so much damage.
I thought they were...
What?
Gunderson wasn't
even with me.
You just immediately
assumed it was him.
I got to say,
I admired your work
and was happy
to take credit for it.
I can't believe
you took the blame
this whole time.
Jake: It was dick
thing to do, Billy.
I should've
told you sooner
and I will totally
pay you back
for everything
that was damaged,
with interest.
Wow, feels good.
That actually
feels good.
It's a relief.
(Chuckles)
Dragging that around
for so long.
It's good. It's nice...
Nice feeling.
(Sighs)
There's one other thing
I need to tell you.
About the walk.
And tabatha (Laughs)
(Sighs) Guys, no offense,
but, you're
not invited, all right?
I need to do this
on my own.
Damn it,
that's broken. (Sighs)
Let the record show
that I'm no longer
in this to keep
Jake in New York.
Excuse me? You're trying
to keep me in New York?
Well, it was.
Now, I just wanna
make sure
that you and tabatha
never get back together.
Are you fucking with me?
You're trying to break
tabatha and me up?
You guys aren't
together now. (Laughs)
Not current...
You know what I mean,
for crying out loud.
You guys
are awful together.
You're worse
than heathcliff and Cathy.
I was always
more of a Garfield
man myself.
I'm just looking
out for you.
You don't need
to look out.
I can look after my...
You know what,
I had the stupid idea
that maybe you'd be
happy for me. God, stupid.
I was happy
for you, Jake,
when I thought
we're gonna be
out adventuring.
All right.
Why don't we just meet
up with each other
in a couple
of hours and grab
a drink then, huh?
How's that sound? Rocks,
drinks in a couple of hours?
No? He's drunk.
What's your big plan
anyway? Aren't you
leaving tomorrow?
Yeah. I don't know.
Maybe we'll do
a long-distance thing.
Maybe I won't
leave, I don't know.
Really? Seriously?
It's possible.
I don't know, Billy!
I just know that
I've never been happier
than I was
when I was with her.
That is not true,
all right?
Life sucked back then
You know what,
I didn't want to have
to do this, but you...
You leave me
no choice. All right?
Oh, come on!
I'm on your tail!
Fuck's sake!
Guys, guys, guys!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Okay, okay, fine.
You can come,
but for fuck's sake,
just please, please,
behave yourselves.
Who you're
talking to?
Of course, we will.
Yeah.
And we're gonna
need to bring wine.
And you're paying.
Okay. Well, we are
near my office.
There's a place a
couple of blocks down
that we've got
an expense account.
Great.
I need a cupcake.
Just real quick.
The... I know
the fire extinguisher
debacle was Jake,
but I'm still
gonna blame you.
Impressive,
and I accept.
Billy: Come on, Jake,
just one.
Jake: No.
Billy: Please! Jake.
Jake, Jake, Jake,
Jake, Jake.
Real quick.
Ugh...
Fine. All right.
A robber walks
into your house,
puts a gun to your head,
he says Sophie's choice.
Option one is
you have to gain
and lose 30 pounds
every month
for the rest
of your life, or...
Oh.
Or option two,
you could stop making him
play this stupid game.
Gunderson, will you just
shut the fuck up?
Billy?
Mr. Kim.
Larry, please.
How are you feeling?
Not good.
I am coughing up blood.
Oh, dear, really?
No. No.
I don't know
why I just said that.
I see.
Yeah. No, I just...
I just... you know.
I thought
I'd pick up a wine
on my way
to the doctor.
It's not exactly
on the way.
No, it is not.
That's true.
(Clicks)
And my friends
are here, too.
We're not his friends.
You know,
I just wanted to...
Wanted to pick
up a bottle,
little something
to wet the palette.
It's just
a little parched.
Next time,
you wanna spend the day
horsing around
with your friends...
Oh, Mr. Kim, that's...
I get it.
I do. Just...
Next time
tell me the truth.
Okay? (Laughs)
(Laughs)
Nailed it.
Congratulations, you got
away with it.
What the hell,
I mean, was that?
I mean, is he serious?
He seems perfect.
Hey, where is Jake?
(Sighs) Bumblebees.
Gunderson: (High-pitched)
Surprise!
Oh, no. Oh, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Billy: Hey.
What are you doing
here? Please, no.
For me? Thank you.
(Door opens)
Billy: Hi.
Gunderson: These are
for you.
Hey! Oh! Hey,
good to see you.
Hey.
Tab, hey, hey.
Thank you. What?
(Rocks clears throat)
Rocks: Here's the answer.
You sleep
with Helen Keller
because of
the heightened
sense of touch.
You should kill Amelia earhart
because there would
finally be a body.
Oh.
And there
would be closure.
Ah, that's a sweet story.
There'd be closure.
And then,
you're gonna marry
no one, actually.
Because that one
was a trick question.
Because how
do you know
someone well enough
to marry them?
You don't.
(People laughing)
Oh, yeah.
I'd probably sleep
with all of them.
And then, maybe
one would die
accidentally.
Thus solving two thirds
of the problem.
(Woman laughs)
Man 1: Oh, very nice.
Man 2: No, very daft.
Classy, dad, classy.
Woman: But, wait,
wait, wait. Tell...
Now, tell me.
It's how long,
this walk?
The walk
is 260 blocks.
Oh.
It's about 15 Miles.
Oh, that's marvelous!
(Gasps) I'm envious.
You guys are
on a walkabout?
It's just four guys
getting...
I wouldn't call it a...
It doesn't
have to be a walkabout.
Tabatha: No,
I mean that
in a good way.
I don't mean
to devalue... look.
I'll plead my case
for you.
Um...
Throughout time,
throughout history,
there has been...
Before man began...
Yes.
Right, okay.
Take it way back,
to the beginning.
Um...
There's always been
something to signify
the mechanism of
men going
from childhood
to adulthood.
There's always
been something.
There's been
a trek, a hunt,
a whore,
whatever it is,
there is this...
Or all three.
There we go, or...
Now, there's nothing.
Right.
There's whores.
There's nothing.
What in this culture
signifies that
for men?
(Women laughing)
See, Billy, that's why
you're still a child.
You don't have
that mechanism
that will make you
into an adult.
I had a bar mitzvah.
(Man laughs)
Gunderson: Bar mitzvah.
Tabatha: Okay.
And for women it's just,
you know, it's...
There is, like,
an internal clock
there's something
very different
for women.
It's biological.
Rocks: I don't think that
not knowing how to grow up
or having difficulty
with that.
Is that new
a concept, necessarily.
No, no.
Also, I would...
Also I think that
saying that women mature
better than men is...
(Emits fart noise)
Whoa! I did not
say that.
I was not saying...
Man: If I may,
perhaps the idea that we
ever grow up is flawed.
Adults, children,
children, adults.
We are all both, at once!
Mmm-hmm.
I would say, it feels good
to think otherwise.
But, just because
you feel good,
does not make it so.
Huh?
(Laughs) Mmm-hmm.
Dan, your wisdom never ceases
to amaze, yet confuse me.
All: (Chuckling)
Tabatha: Hear, hear.
The more you drink,
the smarter I get.
All: (Laughing)
You know what?
I have a game.
I think everybody is
going to love this game.
I can't take credit
for this game.
It's not my game.
It's actually Jake's game!
Billy: Jake's game!
Jake came up with this.
This is all Jake.
A robber bursts
into your home,
puts a gun to your head,
and says, "you have
two options,
Jake: Hey, hey.
Come on man, no.
"Or I kill you."
You leave the city
that you have called
your home for so long.
You have to leave it.
You can never return.
Or option two.
You can stay in
that city you love
but you have to stay in
a loveless relationship.
Someone who your friends,
everyone in your life,
knows this person
is bad for you.
Trying to shape you
and mold you into
something that you are not.
So her only goal...
So sorry guys.
Oh my God. I'm so sorry.
That was on me.
There's a bathroom upstairs.
Are you serious?
I was just, I'm looking for
the bathroom, and your room
snuck up on me.
The panty drawer's in there.
The panty drawer?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
What I was trying to
say to you before
just so you understand,
is it's not that women
necessarily grow up
better than men.
It's just that, their path
to adulthood is... different.
I don't give a shit and
I was just being contrary.
Hmm.
So this is the room then, huh?
This is.
This is my childhood bedroom.
It is exactly
the way I left it.
That's nice.
Mine's pretty much the same.
It's got a treadmill
in it now.
Yeah.
I don't want to freak you out,
but there's six enormous
faces looking at us.
Who are they?
What's their story?
Tabatha: You know what?
Rocks: They seem...
Tabatha: I have...
A story for you.
(Music playing)
Just doesn't make sense.
I mean, I lied repeatedly
and then directly to
Mr. Kim's face,
and then, nothing.
It's funny. I don't remember
inquiring about you,
in any kind of way.
It's just unsettling.
That's, that's the word
that I would use.
Fine, I'll bite.
Billy, you got away with it.
What's the big deal?
It's just that
the universe has an order.
Your transgressions
must be punished.
Without that order,
there's... chaos.
You really are a
simple, simple boy.
Have you seen her?
Huh?
Tabatha. Have you seen her?
Billy: No.
Asshole. You don't care.
Neither of you care.
What are you even doing here?
I asked you not to...
I begged you not to come.
You. You!
That stunt you pulled
at dinner, come on man.
I'm going through an
existential crisis here.
You can't go...
Whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
You are not going through
an existential crisis.
An existential crisis means
that your whole existence
is being called into question.
What you're dealing with,
are transitional issues.
Is that really what
existential means?
Yes.
Oh.
You don't have to yell at me.
I didn't yell at you.
That was yelling.
So for my birthday,
my dad bought me
mmm-hmm.
A holga camera.
It was my first camera ever.
And, this photograph
was taken
the first time that I ever
heard my parents having sex.
Okay.
(Chuckles)
I heard all these
sounds and...
I knew it was significant
so I ran back
and I got my camera
and I got a tripod.
And I stood outside
and I faced away
from the door.
And I looked
and I took the picture.
What a weirdo.
I know.
I know, right.
And you would
not, not frame that
and put it on your wall
because...
It's a keeper,
and you put it up
on your wall.
I didn't frame it.
Well, it's in a frame.
I know, they framed it.
They framed it.
Yeah.
So sick.
And did you tell them
honestly what it is.
Do they know
what they framed?
I don't know.
I don't want to know.
I don't want
to know, either.
(Laughing)
God! I'm worried
about her.
Maybe she's got diarrhea.
You know, sometimes
when she drinks too
much coffee,
her stomach
can get a little...
How about this one?
A robber shoots you
in the head.
Says, "Sophie's choice.
"Play chess with the dog
or scrabble with the cat."
Hmm.
I don't think
you understand
how this game is played.
Oh! (Laughing)
I'm gonna get some scotch.
I'm gonna take a shit.
You know, Jake,
you're a good egg.
Well, that is true, sir.
You know what
you should do?
Marry my daughter,
have babies
and name one after me.
(Laughing)
(Chuckles skeptically)
Ow.
Oh, boy.
(Laughing) Wine stain?
Yeah. Let's not go down...
This really...
That's really
quite a mess.
That's quite unfortunate.
Looking for...
Oh, I could get you a shirt.
I need to borrow a...
Back, back under
the mattress
where it belongs.
A thoroughly
bad choice...
I don't know why...
I've...
Tabatha...
Here's your picture.
Can you...
I'm so.
That's my fault.
I'm sorry.
One, have a threesome
with a couple twice your age
or two, masturbate
in front of a room
full of strangers.
(Laughing)
We should go.
Oh, God, yes.
Jake: I don't get it.
I thought you invited me
around so
we could talk.
Jake, I... just...
I don't think...
(Sighs)
Do you remember this?
Oh, my God.
From our first date.
Do you remember?
I saved it, obviously.
And I...
(Chuckling)
I framed it and...
Anyway...
(Laughs) Look at that.
I thought I was really
fucked up for the last
couple of days.
Hmm, but I think
I've been fucked up
for a long time, maybe.
So...
Damn.
You need to
finish your walk.
Tabby, hey.
(Clears throat)
All right.
All right, all right,
guys, let's go.
Rocks: Yeah.
Gunderson: You liked living
in hell's kitchen?
Jake: Yeah,
the noodle place.
You remember that...
Must have taken you there
a thousand times.
Billy: You sure there
wasn't one here on
the lower east side?
Jake: No, no, no.
That was a donut shop.
You're thinking
about a donut place.
Jake: Oh, east village.
Remember that
east village place
with the weird door man?
Sounds like roland...
Rudolph.
Gunderson: The guy was always
giving me mix-tapes.
Jake: (Laughs) Oh, God!
Jake: You know, I don't
think I've ever not loved
a neighborhood
in this city.
Jake: (Sighs) Man,
I really don't
wanna leave.
Billy: Then don't.
Billy: We could
just go to a park.
Jake: It'll be worth it,
trust me.
(Shouting)
Okay.
You guys
are gonna love this.
Oh, goddamn it.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
That's an
interesting choice.
Jake: God damn, taggers.
Ruined it.
My breasts are nice.
When did you make this?
Couple months ago.
They're turning the whole
place into a hotel.
So I kinda had
this stupid idea that
you know,
that we could live on,
our legacy or something.
Jake: (Sighs) God.
Nothing about this day
has turned out the
way I wanted it to.
Well, the day's not over.
We can salvage this,
we'll go to a bar,
have a few drinks.
I kissed tabatha.
What?
Me and tabatha,
we kissed.
What are you
talking about?
You did not.
No, we did.
Fuck you, you did not.
It happened.
When?
Rocks: In her old bedroom.
Not where. When.
After dinner.
Okay.
Why?
I don't know.
Just tell me why?
I'm not mad.
I just want
to know why.
Because
I'm a fucking
piece of shit.
Uh-huh.
Why else?
Jake, Jake,
come on, Jake.
I don't know.
Jake, let go.
You fucking know.
I don't.
Billy: Jake...
You fucking know.
You do know.
You do know!
Why did you do it?
Billy: Come on, Jake, Jake.
Come on, Jake. Jake.
Smooth, rocks,
really smooth.
It was probably
just a little drunken kiss.
Like a peck.
No.
Sure, I mean,
it was a momentary lapse.
You weren't thinking.
I wish that were true.
I do.
Billy: It is.
Jake is overreacting.
And...
No, Billy, stop.
I know you,
you would never...
Stop it.
It's not a big deal...
Billy, Jesus Christ,
I messed up, okay?
I'm not perfect.
What the hell
is going on today?
You okay, shit head?
Do you realize
that the last time that
we all hung out together
as a group
was at my birthday
last year.
What do you care
if I stay or if I go.
What does it matter to you.
Come on,
of course it does.
We're not...
...friends anymore.
Billy: Is it true about
the birthday thing?
Jesus.
(Ringing)
Emma: Leave a message.
(Beeps)
Hey, em. It's me.
I think you're
with your sister.
I'm just calling to say
that we got done early
and I just wanted to see
what you're up to,
where you're at.
It's been
a pretty crazy day...
I'm calling from
a pay phone,
because I broke my phone
so I guess I'll just give
you a try again later. Okay.
(Sighs)
God, please
call me back,
all right?
I really, I really
need to fucking
talk to you.
All right, rocks
told me everything.
And...
(Door closes)
(Throws down keys)
(Thumping)
This place is ridiculous.
(Sighs)
You deserve none of this.
I'm so tired.
(Line ringing)
Hey, Larry.
Yeah.
I just wanted to call
and apologize
for earlier.
You're totally right.
I should have
just told the truth.
Yeah, but the thing is...
About this merger.
Honestly,
I'm completely
and utterly beat
and I think
I'm gonna need
tomorrow to recover.
Yeah, I understand
we've got the deadline.
I don't want to
slow things down
so why don't you just
take me off the team
on this
and I will go get
them next time.
Okay, thanks
for understanding.
(Sighs)
What?
Nice work.
(Cell phone ringing)
Huh.
Emma's sister.
Weird.
Hello?
No, I haven't seen...
What? Yeah, okay.
(Techno music playing)
Man: Where is he?
Hi.
Hey.
Bartender: Hey.
Water. No ice.
And keep it coming.
All right.
(Car alarm blaring)
I haven't seen him
in like three hours.
I don't...
How am I supposed
to know where...
Let me call you back.
What's up?
(Laughs)
So simple.
Rocks. (Laughs)
(Whistles for cab)
(Inaudible)
(Sighs)
(Urinating)
(Gasps)
I copied him.
(Horn blaring)
(Keys clattering)
(Cell phone ringing)
Yeah.
(Siren wails)
(Elevator bell dings)
Hi, Emma,
Emma Bryant.
Her water broke,
she came in
a few hours ago.
I'm the father.
Miss Bryant?
Yeah.
She's recovering.
She's recovering?
Don't worry, she's fine.
Your son was born
45 minutes ago.
I missed it.
Are you sure?
Pretty sure.
What room are they in?
Where are they? Stat.
6820.
6820, okay.
(Sighs)
(Woman paging for doctor)
Hey.
Man, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for coming.
(Whispers) Hey.
You guys wanna
meet my son?
Yes.
Oh...
(Baby cooing)
(Singing softly)
No, man,
I wouldn't know.
(Cooing)
(Baby cries)
Yeah, baby...
(Softly) Oh, cute.
(Makes popping sound)
(Laughs)
Can I try it?
(Babies crying)
I'm gonna
grab some food.
Hmm.
Hey.
Harry, I got
a secret for you.
You wanna know
why we call
your dad rocks?
He literally has just these,
nasty, gigantic,
Godzilla sized testicles.
(Laughs) So there it is.
You know, that's the
kinda stuff you learn about
your college roommate.
Most of it is...
(Clears throat) Disgusting.
So...
All right, what else.
Not too much pain?
(Laughs)
Hanging in.
I should've been there.
I'm so sorry.
I wasn't mad.
How can you say that?
I just wasn't...
Jake: What else can
I tell you guys?
Your parents will probably
tell you that you're special.
But chances are,
you're not.
Unique, yeah, sure,
I can buy that.
But not special,
come on.
Just because
you can draw doesn't
mean you're an artist.
And there is no such
thing as a permanent record.
So have some fun
in elementary school.
Yeah, you.
Columbus didn't
discover America
and the guy was
kind of an asshole.
And trust me
when I tell you,
that your parents,
are only looking out
for your best interests, okay?
You know, I...
I...
So call them once in a while.
You know, believe me
on that one because...
I'm telling you.
There will be a time.
When you can't anymore.
So, you know...
I know it's a hassle.
You don't even
need any excuse.
Just call and say hi.
(Sighs)
Hey, buddy,
can we leave for a bit?
Emma is sleeping,
why, what's up.
I think we got
to do one last thing.
Thank you.
I got that.
Here, thanks.
So...
She really wasn't upset
that you weren't there?
(Sighs) I think
we've both known
for a while now,
no matter how much we want to,
we're just not in love.
Maybe we never were.
But everything
is gonna work out,
right?
I think so, now, yeah.
In a way.
This is a fun story.
Tonight, at the dinner party,
I shat in the bath tub.
(Laughing)
You did not.
(All whooping)
(Laughing)
Whoo-hoo!
(All whooping)
(Exhales) Awesome.
(Sighs)
(Splashes)
Jake: Hey, I really
appreciate what you
guys did for me today.
Even you, kinda.
But...
I'm still leaving.
I have to. I got to move on
I gotta...
Face the future, you know.
Good.
Good?
Good riddance.
(Chuckles)