Tonight there are still
many questions looming
in the wake of serial killer
Nate Haskell's escape from
from police custody.
Haskell, the convicted
Dick and Jane Killer,
was being transported
in a prison van
when an apparent coconspirator
smashed her vehicle
into the prison convoy,
fatally shooting
two corrections officers
and another
female accomplice, before she
and Haskell
then fled the scene.
Police continue
to ask the public
for any information
they may have
regarding the case.
Don't turn it off on my account.
Nothing I haven't seen,
nothing I haven't heard.
You have any word?
I got nothing.
- Nothing?
- There's been sightings
from here to Poughkeepsie--
nothing substantial, you know.
Man like Haskell
gets on the loose,
people get shook,
start seeing things.
We got nationwide BOLOs,
NCICs have been alerted.
That's how we catch criminals.
Haskell's
a different matter, Jim.
Hey, Ray,
there are
a lot of people
putting in a lot
of time on this.
He'll make a move,
we'll get him.
And until he makes
a mistake, I guess
we just satisfy ourselves
picking up bodies, right?
MAN
Hey, buddy, you okay?
We should call 911.
Let's get some tape out.
Everybody back!
I'm not getting any pulse.
Hook him up to the EKG.
Not viable.
Flatliner.
No signs of life.
Affirm, a 419.
Roll coroner.
No apparent injuries.
I don't smell any booze.
Liver temp is 98 degrees.
Been dead less than an hour.
Okay, let's bag him.
♪ ♪
I'm busy, okay?
No, no, no, I can't talk
about this now.
Well, I-I tried to talk about it
this morning, but I'm busy now.
Uh-huh. I'm sorry.
Did you say I act like my job is
life and death?
Well, excuse me,
my, my job is just death.
Yeah, that's right.
60 hours a week, plus unpaid
overtime worth of death.
Which reminds me,
I have a customer waiting.
I gotta get back to work.
No, I'll call you later.
♪ ♪
David? David?
David, you're zoning out again.
I-I'm back, Doc.
So let me get
this straight.
You found a John Doe
in his 20s on the pavement
near the Strip, and
you brought him here dead.
Yeah, I-I was about
to take a sample
of his vitreous fluid
when he, uh...
Well, he just...
Decided to leave?
Well...
Oh, so a dead guy just
got up and left? Okay.
How'd you end up
on the ground?
Well, I had to defend my domain.
Well, you put a hole
in his liver.
I think I'd call that a draw.
Were you able to get
a fingerprint
or a blood sample or anything we
can use to I.D. the man?
No. No, I just had time
to snap a few photos,
take personal effects
from his pockets.
There's no wallet.
Captain Brass, coroner's office
has been cleared.
No suspect found.
Copy that.
Put out a broadcast:
"Suspect has left
the building."
Dead man walking.
♪ CSI 11x16 ♪
Turn On, Tune In, Drop Dead
Original Air Date on February 24, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
♪ Who... are you? ♪
♪ Who, who, who, who? ♪
♪ I really wanna know ♪
♪ Who... are you? ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Who... ♪
♪ Come on, tell me who are you,
you, you ♪
♪ Are you! ♪
Sweetie, I'm okay.
I'm sorry, too, honey bunny.
I feel awful, Doc, but I
swear the guy was dead.
Did you check
respiration?
- Yes!
- EKG?
I'm telling you,
it was a flatline.
Sweat on the body bag where
the dead man's palms
would have been.
Dead men don't sweat,
do they, Doctor?
About as often as they get up
and walk away.
Have a trace of blood,
as well.
That's from
the liver stick puncture.
What'd you find in his pockets?
City bus pass.
No particular route.
This old notebook,
very well used, filled with
all kinds of data.
"Stonewall 1/14, day seven.
"Number one-- Status quo.
Number two-- Moved from
Falcon to Chameleon."
And then these last pages are
written in
a completely different hand,
dated a week ago.
"Making progress,
feeling closer."
Hey, got some
surveillance.
Dead rising,
birds falling from the sky,
fish dying in rivers.
Should we be looking
for the Antichrist
to make an appearance?
Haskell being on the loose is
enough to fill our quota.
- Coffee?
- Yes.
Thanks!
No ambulance yet, huh?
Nope. Early bird
gets the caffeine.
You said you have
a DB with a head wound?
I do. Some of the shop owners
around here complain
about the homeless people
being too at home
in these alleys.
So I check on 'em
from time to time.
- Just how far a walk are we talking about?
- Right here.
Are you sure?
He was right here, dead!
I checked his pulse
myself.
I'm not kidding
you; he was here.
Well, we got a blood pool.
You weren't dreaming.
Looks like he, uh, hit his head
on the gutter spout?
Maybe he was
intoxicated.
You know, heavily enough
to suppress his heart rate,
make him appear pulseless.
That's him.
Surveillance footage from the
garage at the end of the alley
where you found him...
and then lost him.
Captain, I swear.
Look, the good news
for you is
this isn't the first time
this has happened today.
That's the second body that's
just got up and walked away.
It's a zombie epidemic.
A zombie epidemic?
Is that how you're gonna
characterize it?
Turn around and tell
these guys we have
a zombie epidemic in
Las Vegas.
See how far
you get.
Come on.
Maybe you ought to keep that
to yourself.
DMV facial recognition?
Yeah. Yeah, it's worth a shot.
You know, I considered calling
the DMV. Half the people
that work up there are
the walking dead anyway.
Maybe they recognize
this guy.
Uh, I got the DNA results
on the blood found
in the alley
and the body bag.
Neither John Doe was in CODIS.
Hodges has a proposal:
that they become the inaugural
entrants
in his copyrighted ZODIS.
Hmm?
Yeah, "Zombie DNA Index System."
He made me say that.
He also wants you to know
that zombie blood
is no different
than regular human blood.
The potassium
and glucose levels
are consistent with the living.
That's all you have for us?
I ran tox, too, and both
samples were clean.
Although, working with such
minimal samples is fairly
useless.
You know, brain-hungry zombies
could say
the same thing about Hodges.
Minimal sample.
Fairly useless.
Exactly.
♪ ♪
I searched for
combinations of the terms
in morgue zombie's notebook,
and discovered a Defense
Department program
called "Stonewall" that took
place on the WLVU campus
in the early '70s.
Psychological research.
Found a schematic
of the campus building that was
used in the experiments.
Included some rooms code-named
"Falcon" and "Chameleon."
Researchers were exploring
a variety
of fringe psych concepts
such as ESP, out-of-body
experience.
- Science fiction.
- Not if they help us defeat the commies.
One of the most notable
psychologists involved
was a man named Dr. Eliot
Davis Aden.
"EDA."
This probably belonged to him.
He's an interesting guy.
World-renowned psychoanalyst,
but fell down the rabbit hole
of psychedelic drugs.
Was dismissed
by the scientific community,
but not without
one big, fat scandal.
Rumor has it that Dr. Aden
had become a bit
of a Dr. Feelgood
for the student body.
At least until one of his
students threw himself out
of a fifth-story window,
and the party came to an end.
He was banished by
the university,
but charges
were never pressed.
So the government didn't want
to step on the toes
of someone who
knew their secrets.
All right, so our morgue zombie
is walking around
with Dr. Aden's notebook.
There's got to be a connection.
Is Aden still around?
He still receives a government
pension check.
And I was able to track down
the address where
he receives it.
Hello, Doctor.
♪ ♪
Casino's three
miles further.
Dr. Aden?
Dr. Aden... Uh...
we'd like to speak with you.
You got the wrong guy.
We're from the crime lab.
We found something of yours.
Lying government bastards!
Ivory-tower turncoats!
Frat boy plays window Icarus,
and the university throws
my reputation out the window
with him.
They claimed that all of
my papers had been destroyed.
Banished me from
university property.
It was a good way to cut me out
of the green and the glory.
It's Philo Farnsworth
all over again!
I'm sorry.
Where did you find this?
In the pocket of, uh,
this young man.
Do you recognize him?
Uh-uh... He's dead?
He's obviously on
an autopsy table.
Actually, the young man
in question...
...arose.
The Lazarus myth made real?
Re-animation? This is
getting more interesting.
It's, uh...
not as easy as you might think,
bringing back the dead.
It's not work for neophytes.
Or the reckless.
Or the timid.
Oh, sure,
they can conjure up
a cardiac spasm,
or a momentary flash from
the bioelectric system.
That's not the same as...
Doctor,
are you saying
that you conducted
re-animation experiments
at Stonewall?
What's your clearance, soldier?
Uh...
about five-nine.
Doctor, are those your notes
from the re-animation
experiments?
It's hard to say.
It's my writing.
I won a lot of awards for
penmanship in third grade.
Of course, staying between
the lines for me wasn't easy.
These... last entries.
It's not my handwriting.
Some vulture
is perching on my
giant shoulders.
Feasting on the carrion
of my discoveries.
Treating the work as their own.
In your, um, re-animation
experiments, Doctor,
how far would you say
you were able to get?
I had the Ithaca of that
most profound mystery
within my sights.
Could almost reach
out and touch it.
But I saw the storm
clouds gathering.
The maelstrom.
For those not wise enough
to pull their sails in,
certain destruction awaits.
I'm trying to say...
this isn't good.
San Francisco girl, huh?
Left my heart,
and half my cerebral
cortex in Frisco.
You ever see The Dead
play the Fillmore?
No, uh... too busy with
the dead everywhere else.
Lucky you.
The research librarian said
that your work was archived
in a disused wing
of one of the buildings,
gave me the keys, but said
"enter at your own risk."
Preface fit for any
worthwhile venture.
Where is it?
Lincoln Hall,
room 317.
Right where I left it.
Lazy, lying bastards!
I really don't know, Conrad.
Maybe we need a new
classification
for this type of situation.
D.O.-AWOL.
That was a joke!
- Hey, Catherine.
- Later, Conrad.
I got a DMV facial recognition
match on the morgue zombie.
Oh, Max Ferris.
Mm-hmm.
Home address is on the WLVU
campus, so I called the school.
He's a grad student
in psychology.
- Could be how he got Aden's notebook.
- Yeah.
I'll have Brass send
a uniform to his place,
trap his credit cards,
see if we can track him down.
Nice.
We don't need a key.
The lock's been busted out.
Easy. Easy, Doctor.
Easy, easy,
easy.
We don't want to
tamper with this.
This is all evidence.
This...
is my Library of Alexandria.
My trove of treasures.
I may have been banned bodily,
but I wandered it
nightly in my dreams.
Looks like someone's been doing
some independent study here.
Doctor, are these...
all your papers?
Do you know how many
papers I wrote?
I'm asking.
How about we get
back to you on that?
Hmm.
"Reflections On
Near-death Experiences."
"Death As Gateway."
That was my "White Album."
They all appear to be
on the same subject.
Sooner or later, all us
chickens cross the road.
Now, aren't we all curious
about what's on the other side?
Hey, Doc.
Your other subjects
look untouched.
Whoever's been playing around
with your papers
was only interested
in your research on
death-related
phenomena.
Making your acolyte's visit
to the morgue... what?
A field trip?
In all my journeys
to the other side,
I never left
this building.
DMT, ketamine,
those were the only
tickets I needed.
Hallucinogenic trips?
Better than a ride
in a coroner's van?
Where is it?
What have they
done to my song?
Dr. Aden!
So, Captain Klepto,
you don't look like Max Ferris.
Guy was passed out
on the sidewalk.
A real eyesore.
So it's your
civic duty
to steal his wallet,
take his cash,
and swipe his credit card?
I had that plastic for a whole
day. I only used it once.
For a six-pack of beer, so...
Cleaning up the streets
and fiscally responsible.
You ought to run for office.
Look out,
Mayor Goodman.
Hey, I gave you his
wallet and his...
phone...thing.
What are the odds
you'll just cut
me loose, huh?
This is a phone?
Didn't look like any phone
I'd seen, either.
But I'm a couple
iPhones behind.
Yeah, I'll bet you are.
It's not a phone.
It's a wearable camcorder.
Wireless video camera
and receiver.
Our morgue zombie
was using it.
Well, grab some popcorn.
Tonight, we take
the ultimate step.
Beyond our past journeys
of the mind.
Tonight, we free ourselves
from the physical plane.
Unspooling the mortal coil,
we seek the mystery
that lies beyond...
Hey, Discovery Channel,
kill the speech and let's
kill some brain cells.
This guy on the left-- his
clothing matches the description
of our alley zombie.
It's a dead man's party.
Except the third person
looks like a woman.
DR. ADEN:
How could they do this?
What have
they done?
If they've given it to
some health club...
Dr. Aden, slow down.
Dude. You going to tell us
what we're taking?
No need to add baggage to your trip.
Trust me, Kurt.
It's going to be an adventure.
It's time
to put your cameras on.
See you on re-entry.
Godspeed, Alice.
Max's friends Kurt and Alice.
Maybe we can get access to Max's
university email account;
check his contacts.
See who his co-pilots were.
Yeah.
Angelfish. Triggerfish.
Blue-ringed octopus.
All poisonous.
All alive.
Someone has been in here
on a regular basis.
20 minutes after ingestion.
Effects are manifesting.
So Max has made his way
to the Strip. He's at the plaza
by the Tangiers.
Increasing numbness
of the mouth.
S... Speech is becoming
difficult.
Numbness spreading.
That hum.
The fish tank filter.
No, no, it's another harmonic.
She's here!
Oh, my...
Santa Maria, my Nautilus!
The vessel of all my dreams.
Dr. Aden!
Oh.
That's not Max Ferris.
That's our alley zombie.
De-animated.
The good doctor is content
to wait in the hall.
He hasn't had
this much excitement
since Altamont.
Or so he says.
Police and coroners
are on their way.
Pulled the victim's wallet.
Kurt Dawson.
Lived near campus,
but his student ID expired
about a year ago.
Dropped out of school.
Or dropped out
of reality.
A sensory deprivation tank.
Did you ever see that movie
Altered States?
Oh. Yeah.
My mom took me.
She found it
therapeutic, calming.
Says it all.
- I saw it with some really good buds.
- Go, Dr. Ray.
I know. I only talk
like a square.
Tank water's highly salinated;
kept at body temp
so the user floats
in complete silence
and darkness.
Blocking out all
earthly stimuli.
You know, in the movie
Altered States,
William Hurt went
into the tank naked.
To strip the self down
to one's primitive,
disembodied being
is how you free the
mind, allowing it
to venture
into other realms.
You wouldn't want
to go venturing
in ten pounds of
wet clothes and sneakers.
Maybe the tank
wasn't his idea.
I noticed some faint bruising
that started to develop
on Kurt's back and shoulder.
So, I snapped
some infrared photos.
Hand marks.
He was held down.
That's one way to drown in
just ten inches of water.
So drowning is COD?
Heavy, edematous lungs,
and fluid in his sphenoid sinus
make it pretty clear.
I thought maybe you'd
start chaining them down.
Although yanking out
vital organs is
a good way to
keep the clients.
Henry.
Right. Um, found
trace of Tetrodotoxin--
TTX-- in his system.
It's a naturally
occurring poison,
1,200 times more
toxic than cyanide.
It's present in a variety
of sea creatures.
The toxin blocks
sodium channels,
blacking out the body's
nervous system.
A dose the size
of a pinhead can kill,
and short of killing, it can
completely paralyze a person
for hours.
Considering his condition
in that alley, I checked out
the half-life table for TTX,
and the current level of toxin
in him would be consistent
with a dose
of two milligrams
16 hours ago.
Enough to paralyze, suppress
heartbeat and breathing,
and get him mistaken for dead.
There was a fish tank with
some poisonous specimens
in the same room
we found him in.
Could the toxins have been
extracted from them?
Sure. With some sophisticated
biochem resources.
Although there were two
other substances present
in his system--
LSD and cannabis.
Body was frozen,
mind was ablaze.
I've been there.
This one's actually dead.
Congratulations.
You're batting .500.
Yeah, great for a hitter,
bad for pronouncing death.
Let me see your EKG.
What are you looking for, Doc?
Your zombie from the Strip
was under the influence
of a paralytic,
which we would have known if
you'd had the gain on this unit
correctly calibrated,
which it's not.
The way you've got it set, it
wouldn't pick up my heartbeat.
I'd be a flat-liner.
You're lucky
you're not benched.
Misdiagnose the undead again,
put my assistant
in harm's way,
and you'll find yourself
unemployed.
Footprints in salt water
leading towards the door.
The vic was wearing sneakers,
size eights.
Yeah, well, these feet
are at least size 11 or 12.
Maybe his pal Max
came back here first.
I've got some
light blue fibers here.
Same as the T-shirt Max Ferris
was wearing in the morgue.
So...
Max makes a break
from the coroner's office,
comes here, dumps his clothes,
gets in the tank to decompress.
And Kurt Dawson shows up.
They get into some sort
of drug-induced fight.
Max wins and walks out of here.
Hey, Sara.
Hmm?
Looks like Kurt lost his camera
in the fight.
LSD and Tetrodotoxin--
"voodoo powder"--
curious combination.
To paralyze yourself
in order to free yourself...
Well, what kind
of state of mind
would that produce in an
individual-- this cocktail?
There's an entire spectrum
of possibilities.
Blazing,
manic lucidity,
to oppressive darkness.
Designer drugs--
one size does not fit all.
Could this cocktail produce,
in certain individuals,
uncontrollable rage, say?
Why do you ask?
Well, one of our young
explorers killed the other.
Well, I would have to know
more about the particulars
of the situation.
There's no fighting in
the war room, Dr. Strangelove.
I want you to
look at something.
...beyond our past
journeys of the mind.
Tonight, we free ourselves
from the physical plane.
Unspooling the mortal coil,
we seek the mystery
that lies beyond.
Hey, Discovery Channel,
kill the speech
and let's kill some brain cells.
Dude, are you going to tell us
what we're taking?
No need to add baggage
to your trip.
Flag on the play.
This young Columbus
didn't prepare his crew.
He knew what the toxins
would induce.
There's a vast difference
between leading others
into the beyond, and throwing
them into it unwittingly.
To some,
that's sinister science,
and could inspire
rage and fury.
So, Kurt, not knowing
what he was taking,
survives the
paralyzing nightmare.
Comes back to confront Max.
They fight.
Max kills Kurt.
Yes. The reckless master
kills the wronged squire.
Sounds like a role you're
not unfamiliar with.
Max was modeling himself
after you, Dr. Aden.
You and your work.
And here, you see,
he sent his friends
Alice and Kurt, unwittingly
as you said, into the fire.
Probably felt like it was
a... a worthy sacrifice.
Knowledge demands its payment.
It's always nice when somebody
picks up the bill
for you, though.
Went through Kurt Dawson's
e-mail accounts.
Found a number of messages
exchanged between him,
Max Ferris and another WLVU
student, Alice Katsu.
Alice from the video.
Yeah. Biochem major.
And like Kurt, she seemed
to be under Max's spell.
Agreeing to his every
experimental whim,
late night meetings
in the abandoned lab,
rambling discussions
on the afterlife.
Well, we know what happened
to Max's other friend.
We need to find Alice.
Do you have any earthly
contact info on her?
So, Mr. Katsu, when was the last
time you saw your sister?
Three days ago.
It's just Alice
and me here.
When she's at school
and I'm at work
sometimes we go
a couple of days
without even bumping
into each other.
Even when she's
here, she's quiet.
Sometimes, it feels like having
a ghost in the house.
Mom liked jelly beans.
It's a Shinto shrine--
offering for the dead.
Alice even plucked
out the black ones.
She's got some
academic honors awards
from the past few semesters,
but an academic probation letter
from just a month ago.
A card from her mom's funeral
five months ago.
Doesn't take a detective.
Mom's death took a toll.
Ooh, another one of Dr. Aden's
notebooks.
"Question of crossing over
physically versus mentally.
Are they inextricably linked?"
She took a picture
of Mom's grave every day.
Capturing the change in light
and seasons.
Trying to shape something
living out of the dead.
I think, while Max Ferris
dosed himself
to explore the mysteries
of the afterlife,
and Kurt was out
for a good time, Alice...
Was traveling in search
of someone.
Maybe we'll find Alice
if we look in the same direction
she was looking.
Groundskeeper said it was
right around here somewhere.
I don't think they're
going anywhere, Mitch.
Yeah, right.
Hey.
Alice?
Max?
Max.
Whoa!
Down. On your knees.
I thought she'd be here.
Max, you're crashing
from a bad trip.
We need to get you
to a hospital.
Stop, Max!
Stop!
Stop! Max!
Oh, my God!
No pulse.
I'm cuffing him anyway.
Stand back, sir.
Dr. Aden said this was going
to end badly.
We have two dead.
Let's hope there's still
time for Alice.
♪ ♪
The notebook I found
in Alice Katsu's room
is a match to Dr. Aden's
handwriting,
but the ink looked fresh,
so I tested it.
It is a date-tag match to a formula
that's only been around a couple of years.
Which means Dr. Aden wrote
those notes recently.
Right. The notebook was not
among his archived papers.
So how did Alice get it?
From the doctor himself.
He and Alice
were e-mail buddies.
She initiated contact
five months ago.
- When her mother died.
- Hmm.
But Aden is not exactly
advertising on bus benches.
Alice saw an anonymous commenter on a
Web site about the doctor's past work.
She kind of felt like
Mr. Anonymous knew
a little bit too much.
So she e-mails, "Dear sir,
"I'm convinced by your
brilliant insights
"that you are
Dr. Aden himself.
"I'm a great admirer of your
courageous research
"into the afterlife.
I want to follow
in your footsteps."
He was quick to respond,
"Glad to have an acolyte,"
and encouraged her
to find more of them.
Max and Kurt.
And we thought Max
was driving the bus,
but it was Alice.
Hey, you guys.
I got something for you to see.
I was scanning through
through Kurt Dawson's video
and I noticed something strange.
So, here, Kurt's just
wandering campus.
Then this happens.
Some kind of interference.
Yeah, Kurt's receiver picked up
a signal from another camera.
I'm working on isolating
the competing image,
but in the meantime,
I managed to pull
a few frames.
Well, those are women's shoes.
Are we looking through
Alice's camera?
She must have been in close
proximity to Kurt,
if his receiver picked up
her feet.
Where is she,
and what's she doing?
It's hard to say.
But check this out.
What, a car stopped for her?
It looks like an old Saab.
Hey, didn't Sara mention
something
about Dr. Aden driving
an old dinosaur
like that?
His car's gone.
Well, he's smart enough
to lead us along,
maybe he knew
we were coming.
Dr. Aden!
Dr. Aden?!
Hello?!
"Alice-- DMT-- Feb 10, 2011.
Alice-- Ketamine--
Jan 18, 2011."
They had a regular thing going.
This one's from yesterday.
Can you blink, Alice?
Come back.
Come back! Focus!
Tell me everything you've seen.
I need to know
what you're seeing.
Let me in, Alice.
Let me in.
I'm not just your
hookah-smoking caterpillar.
Tell me everything
you've seen!
I need to know!
50 milligrams Tetrodotoxin,
just a mouse click away.
Dr. Aden supplied the paralytic.
Alice just passed it around.
Mm-hmm.
I know you've arrived there,
Alice.
Don't leave me behind!
Alice?!
The video camera.
This one's from today.
I've come to a crossroads.
The false path ends here.
I've flirted with the precipice
for too long...
dispatching canaries into
the celestial coal mine,
but shying from the descent
myself.
No longer.
I now slip not just the bonds
of mind, but of body and spirit.
I'm ready to set sail...
unafraid.
Ithaca... I come.
You hear that?
Yeah.
Dr. Aden!
Doctor?
A faint pupil response.
He ingested the toxin
around noon.
At his age,
depriving his brain
of oxygen for that period
of time, he's in there,
but I doubt he'll ever find
his way back out.
What rabbit hole has Alice
fallen down?
WILLOWS
Nick, are you at the campus?
Aden's car's parked out front.
Campus police called it in.
I'm, uh, checking
the building.
Copy.
♪ ♪
Alice?
We've been looking for you.
I was looking for someone, too.
Your mother?
I found her!
I saw she was happy.
She told me she loved me.
Told me to go back.
Alice...
Where, where, where are
Kurt and Max?
I have to tell them
it was everything I thought
I imagined.
I need to know
if they found it, too.
They're not coming back, Alice.
Hallucinogens, neurotoxins
and sensory deprivation.
These kids weren't really
venturing to the other side.
You think they were just
inducing chemical dreams?
All their visions could be explained
by neuroscience.
Yeah.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm sure Adam and Eve,
when they stood over
the first dead body,
meditated on where
his soul went.
Humans have
always pondered
whether there's
an afterlife.
Yeah, if the dead could talk,
we'd all have our answers,
but no one's talking.
They haven't so far.
Which leads me
to believe
that part of life that is death
is meant to be a mystery.
You don't sound
very scientific, Doc.
I see people on the last,
worst day of their lives.
And I'd like to believe
they go to a better place.
I'd like to think I know you
a little better than that.
Well, I was taught that
in Sunday school
long before medical school.
You know what I believe?
I believe that people that bring
suffering and pain
into this world should have it
repaid to them
tenfold,
either in this world
or the next one.
Careful.
Evil has a way of making friends
with the good
and dragging them
into the darkness.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==