♪ The Simpsons 25x15 ♪
The War of Art
Original Air Date on March 23, 2014
Hm... hmm?!
"Lisa wants
"a dot-dot-dot
guinea pig"?
Mm.
Hey, Homer, did you know that
guinea pigs are self-groomers?
And when the get excited,
they jump straight up.
It's called "popcorning."
Lisa got to you.
I don't know how,
but she got to you.
Emojis.
Now she's gone too far.
Lisa, your father and I
are very concerned
about all this hinting.
I've never had
a pet of my very own.
My clock is ticking.
I don't want to be
one of those girls
who waits till she's 16
to decide if she's ready,
and then it's too late.
Well, we've talked about it.
And if you really
want a guinea pig,
you'll have to sign
this contract.
"I, Lisa Simpson, hereby promise
to take full responsibility
for this dog, cat, other."
Circle "other."
"This includes
feeding, bathing,
"cleaning of droppings
and barfings,
and when the time comes,
burying or flushing."
Boilerplate,
boilerplate, boilerplate.
We can skip
all this litter box stuff.
"If pet
becomes Internet superstar,
all rights revert to father."
Sign here, here,
initial here, one
more over here.
And done.
Oh, my God!
I'm getting a guinea pig!
Thank you, thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
The kid-parent contract.
Unenforceable, yet you feel
like you didn't completely cave.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
You're doing the right thing
adopting a rescue pig.
You know, most of these guys
are rejects
from the big guinea-pig mills
in the Midwest.
Oh, I can't tell you
how many mill pigs
we get in here who have
bumblefoot or the slobbers.
You don't have
children, do you?
This one whistled at me!
Ooh, that could
be the one.
Oh, but that orange guy
looks like a pumpkin.
But this fellow is so fuzzy!
Well, they all have
their charms.
This one's nibbling
a sunflower seed.
Look at that hair.
Aw, I just want
to comb it forever!
Have you seen a pinker nose?
I have now!
Lisa, you've just
got to choose one.
Lisa?
She's gone, honey.
She's gone.
That one's fur looks
like a tuxedo!
A Band-Aid on its tail, aw!
Albino!
I'm definitely
getting this one.
Oh, but I forgot
about this one.
Oh, my God,
I never even saw this one!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh...
Maybe I should get
that sick one.
If I don't, no one else will.
Bart, list your top five,
best to worst.
No, no, no, no!
Worst to best.
I just wish the gray one had
the brown one's personality.
Okay, Dad, give me your phone.
I need to look
at the pictures again.
Aw, aw, aw!
Aw, aw!
Okay, this is the guinea pig
that will make me happy.
She thinks
she's decided.
Don't say a thing.
Don't blow this.
Okay, now, you sure
you only want just one?
They tend
to do better in pairs.
I could get two?
Farting tweakers rule!
I've tried to give Pokey
a perfect replica
of his natural habitat.
Peruvian feather grass,
an Incan sleeping mat,
and a portrait of
Marisol Espinoza,
the Vice President of Peru.
Are you sure you didn't create
a perfect habitat for you?
I wish I could
live in there.
Well, there's
plenty of room
because Pokey's gone.
Where'd he go?
This looks like a job for...
fireplace tongs.
No!
Oh, my God!
He's in the walls!
I hear chewing.
No, that's a much bigger animal.
Kettle corn.
The heroin
of the farmers' market.
I've lost my guinea pig!
Pokey!
Our boat painting!
I'm sorry, Mom.
That's okay, sweetheart.
Your pig thingy
didn't mean it.
It's just, it felt
comforting to know
that while we watched TV,
there was art
going on behind us.
Oh, well, I guess we have to go
to an art gallery
and buy a new painting.
Sure, we could go
to a fancy gallery
and spend a bunch
of money, or...
Mm... hmm, hmm,
hmm, hmm?
Yeah, Milhouse played
the violin for years
until it turned out
the vibrations
were screwing up his bones.
Yeah, these seem great.
Oh, too bad someone
used cello rosin.
Oh, my gosh, that's beautiful!
I've never seen a painting
with a lighthouse before.
Oh, that.
That was on the wall
of Kirk's bachelor pad,
back when we were
separated.
Yeah, it's a great piece.
I didn't have a mirror,
so I shaved in the reflection
of the chrome frame.
This could be
our new living room painting.
I don't know.
How about this poster
of a really rocking jukebox?
You know it's rocking
'cause music notes
are coming out of it.
Painting's only 20 bucks.
Oh, please, Homie?
I'll throw in
the tiny violins.
Oh, it looks great!
Well...
to me, it looks like...
garbage salad.
But that's
the great thing about art.
Everyone can have their own
opinion about why it sucks.
I've got to get rid
of this ugly chrome frame
from Kirk's bachelor bad.
I hate to think of the things
this mirror has reflected.
Hmm!
Hey, look.
There's a signature
that the frame covered up.
"Johan Oldenveldt."
Here he is!
"Johan Oldenveldt, painter.
"Lived in Amsterdam, Paris.
Prolific early 20th century
naturalist."
Ooh, I think this was painted
by someone famous.
Maybe it's valuable.
We should
have it appraised.
Pfft!
You guys are crazy.
I never even
heard of that guy.
It's not like
it was painted
by Leonardo Da Vinci Code.
Now, here's what
makes art valuable--
One: nudity,
two: holograms,
three: something terrible
happening to Jesus.
Ah yes, seascape,
marvelous natural light,
classic use of gouache.
You're right.
This is an early-career
Oldenveldt.
Quite valuable.
Oh, my God!
I expect it to go somewhere
between 80 to $100,000.
Nobody touch it!
Bart, stop looking at it!
But I want to see it!
No, you'll wear it out!
Baby, you saw something in this
painting, and you were right.
Wow, the Van Houtens
owned this for years,
and never knew
how much it was worth.
Think how happy they'll be
when we sell it and split
the money with them.
Split it? Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa...
whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Split it with them?
Kirk and Luann didn't
know what the painting
was worth when they sold it.
Yes, they sold it to us.
So, now it's our painting.
We can hang it on our wall,
cut eyeholes in it
to spy on people.
Or sell it for lots of money
which we keep.
For ourselves?
This dude gets it.
But the Van Houtens
are our friends.
Are they, Marge?
If you think about it,
aren't they really
just the parents
of a kid who happens
to hang out with our kid?
All our friends
are like that.
Well, how would you feel
if we sold them something
that turned out
to be valuable?
I would feel A) Happy
for their good fortune,
B) Proud to know rich people,
and C) Grateful
for an opportunity
to learn from a mistake.
How about this?
What if we give
the Van Houtens
25% of the money?
Then they'll just be mad
about the 65%
that we're keeping.
Marge, you like
kindness, right?
Sure.
So, even if we gave
Kirk and Luann
some of the money,
the knowledge of what they could
have had will eat away at them,
like piranhas devouring
a wounded yeti.
It's kinder never to tell them.
Okay, I see your point.
We should sell the painting,
keep all the money,
and never, ever tell
the Van Houtens.
Mm-hmm!
What'll it take to
buy your silence?
Hmm.
Okay, Milhouse,
the guys in back are shining up
your new bike.
And all I have to do
is not say anything
about some painting
to my Mom and Dad?
Oh, sweetie, you want your
parents to be happy, don't you?
I guess.
"I guess"!
You're funny!
No wonder Lisa's
in love with you.
She is?!
So, if I keep my mouth shut,
you get me new
wheelie sneakers,
and Bart agrees
to promote and encourage use
of my new
cool nickname, "C.J."
You got it, Ceej.
You found out that painting
was worth big bucks,
and you weren't
gonna tell us?!
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Hide the treasure!
I'm sorry, Mr. S.
I cracked!
We had a deal.
And now we've got nothing!
We considered you
our friends.
We trusted you!
I let Homer use
our master bathroom!
Then you stab us
in the back!
If you knew you sold
a valuable painting for nothing,
how could you live
with yourselves?
We were just trying
to be... kind.
Kind?! You call it kind
to give us nothing?
We were gonna treat you
to dinner
at an upscale chain restaurant
and never explain why,
but now forget it!
Oh, so that's how it is!
That's exactly
how it is.
Oh, is it?!
Oh, it is!
Luann, I hope
we're still on Thursday
for collecting used
cell phones for the troops.
I don't think
you need any help.
You're so good at...
collecting.
Oh!
Oh, that was cold,
Luann!
So cold!
Brr!
Sarcastic brr!
See what happens
when we get greedy?
Honey, there's something
I want to show you.
An ATM receipt?
I don't know
whose this is.
I found it next
to the cash machine,
and I've always kept it.
Look at the balance.
Five figures!
With that painting, we could
have what these people have:
a money cushion.
No more living
paycheck to paycheck,
one lost retainer away
from the gutter.
I could write a check
with today's date on it.
That's the cushion.
Tonight, a special report.
Fat cat art experts
take advantage
of John and Jane Yard Sale.
So, would you characterize
your friend of many years
cheating you out of your
painting as no big deal,
or a devastating betrayal?
Oh, definitely betrayal, Kent.
Interesting.
So if you see the Simpsons
walking down your street,
lock your doors and hide...
your friendship.
Great! Now we're raccoons,
the masked bandits
of the animal world!
Don't worry. No one's gonna see
this stupid show.
The whole town's
turned against us!
Ooh, a support rock!
This one's against us.
This one's for us.
For, for, against,
for, against...
We don't even get this many
Christmas cards.
There they are,
the Masterpiece Thievers!
Ah, shut your bone hole!
That painting belongs
to the Simpsons!
Sharing is what makes
a community strong!
All sales are final!
Keep it!
Finders keepers, moron!
You really think we're still
doing the right thing?
Just close your eyes
and think of the cushion.
"Untitled Landscape"
by Johan Oldenveldt,
from the Collection of Homer J.
and Marge B. Simpson.
Let's open the bidding
at $80,000.
The paddles, Marge!
Look at the paddles!
Stop the auction!
That painting belongs to me!
Dawn?
Good to see you again,
Beef Kirky.
Who is this woman?
Uhhhhhh...
While you two
were separated,
Kirk and used
to be friends...
with banana-fits.
You told me
you didn't see anyone
during our separation.
Uhhhhhh...
Madam, are you saying
this painting belongs to you?
Kirk stole it from me!
But I didn't know
it was valuable
till I saw the story on TV.
What?! I bought
that painting!
She's lying!
The auction is on hold
until we can determine
the true ownership.
Our cushion!
Don't bother
coming home, Kirk!
Aw!
See what your
greed has done?
Ow!
Anybody want
to give me a ride home?
Going once?
Going twice?
Sold! To the lonely auctioneer!
Ah!
Thanks for
taking me in, man.
I guess I can't help but feel
fully responsible.
Oh, Luann, I'll never gaze
from my thick eyeglasses
into your thick eyeglasses
ever again.
What you need, my friend,
is a Canadian Duff.
Beauty, eh?
So... why does that chick think
she owns the painting?
Oh, Dawn and I went
on a vacation
to a resort island
called Isla Verde.
I bought the painting
in a café,
but that night she ran off
with a parasailing instructor.
Not your fault, man.
Those parasailing guys take
whatever they want.
It was never her painting.
That woman will
say anything
to keep herself in
electric cigarettes.
And I'd go back to that
Café Artiste to prove it,
but nothing's gonna
get me Luann back.
Okay, all I gotta do is take
a quick ferry to Isla Verde,
find Café Artiste,
and they'll back up Kirk's story.
That will prove the painting
was his-- and now ours.
Oh, Homer Simpson, that painting
has torn the town apart,
destroyed Kirk
and Luann's marriage,
and everyone's very worried
about Milhouse.
He's been playing
Dancing Revolution for hours,
but the TV is off.
But our cushion!
That picture has brought out
the worst in everyone!
Please! Just let it go!
You're not gonna
let it go, are you?
I wish I knew how.
This is so exciting!
My first time
establishing provenance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just remember,
if your mother asks,
I took you to a wine tasting.
That's a terrible thing
for a father to do.
That's why
she'll believe it.
Hmm, this quaint artist
community
has gotten a little touristy.
Excuse me. We're trying
to find Café Artiste.
Ah, yes.
Top of the hill.
Three discos up, four
gelatos on the left.
You can't miss it.
It's right between the disco
and the gelato place.
Mmm. Hmm.
Mm-mm!
Mm...
Welcome to Café Artiste!
Would you like
a glass of Strupo?
It's a liqueur made
of fermented capers,
the official drink
of the island.
Mmm! Sounds delicious.
It's not.
Hey, a friend of mine,
uh, bought a painting here.
Oh, yes, I remember
that painting.
And that is the man
I sold it to.
And that man sold it to me!
That proves the
painting is mine!
And nothing can stop
me from selling it
and keeping all the money!
I love art!
Art?
What do you know about art?
You don't even know
who painted that picture.
Yes, I do.
It's a Johan Oldenveldt.
Wrong! It's a me!
A what?
I painted it!
Me, Klaus Ziegler!
Who?
Mm!
Oh!
This is where I painted
your so-called Oldenveldt.
Prove it.
Aw, crap!
You're a forger?
"Forger" is such
a cruel word.
I'm an art forger.
Your painting was
an early, clumsy effort
which I gave to the café owner
to pay off my Strupo tab.
Whew!
Then why did the auction house
say it was real?
I have fooled galleries
around the world
with my loving imitations.
Ziegler! Ziegler! Ziegler!
Ziegler!
Ziegler! Ziegler!
What you do is horrible...
ripping off geniuses
who spent years
perfecting their styles.
Perhaps you are the one
who is horrible.
What?!
You only cared about that
painting when you thought
it was created
by someone famous.
Well, no, but now when I look
at it, all I see is a fraud.
Beauty is beauty.
My forgeries give pleasure to people
all over the world.
The only real question
to ask about art,
whether it's in the Louvre
or on a freshman's wall
at Cal State Fullerton
is, "Did it move you?"
But, you still, I mean...
Oh, I suppose you're right.
What if I never liked
the painting
and only wanted it for money?
Then you, I respect.
Oh, great.
The painting is worthless,
this was all for nothing,
and when Marge finds out,
she's gonna kill me.
Well, on that front,
perhaps I can be of assistance.
If there's one thing
art is good for,
it's to melt the frost which
often hardens a woman's heart.
While you're at it...
could you make me
a couple more?
I'll pay you in Strupo.
Perfect.
Oh, now that's art.
Rocking.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
The Gray Troll,
Brine of Madness,
Angel's Urine,
all names for the mysterious
elixir known as Strupo.
Though this fermented caper
solution was originally used
to dissolve seagull corpses,
local alcoholics
soon found Strupo
to be a palatable drink
of last resort.
The noxious liqueur causes
powerful olfactory
hallucinations,
gender confusion,
and wandering mouth.
So if you visit Isla Verde,
be sure to say "ahoy" to the
crushing addiction of Strupo.
lose everything.
Shh!