25 cars line up to start
the last Grand Prix
of the most extraordinary season
in the history of Formula One.
'This, then, is the clincher -
'the World Championship decider.'
As heavy rain pours down,
two drivers prepare for the race
that will decide
which one of them
becomes World Champion.
'James Hunt in his McLaren.
'Niki Lauda in the Ferrari.
'The flag is down...'
The two men could not be more
different. Britain's James Hunt
is a fast, flamboyant showman
who parties as hard as he races.
James is the driver of the old time.
The gentleman driver,
the flamboyant...
That has the natural talent to go
fast in a car.
There is a race going on, dear boy.
His rival is the steely Austrian
Niki Lauda who drives
with cold, hard logic.
Niki was the scientist,
the counterpoint -
he was the ultimate... The first
really technical driver.
This is the story of Formula One's
legendary rivalry - told by those
who witnessed it first hand.
James got out of the car,
pulled off his crash helmet,
started to rant and rave at them...
'And Brambilla spins!'
The tension was just amazing.
His face was a mask of blood
and I was saying, "My God,
how can he race?"
With previously unseen footage
and exclusive interviews,
this film charts the epic duel that
would change the lives of both men
and the sport forever.
You couldn't make it up.
You could not make up this season.
It was just unbelievable.
'It's going to be a fantastic race.'
Fans line the streets to see
Austrian Niki Lauda crowned
World Champion of 1975.
Lauda drives for Ferrari -
the greatest racing car
constructor in the world.
But Lauda's thoughts
and those of his team are already
turning to next season.
Ferrari's team manager
Daniele Audetto is confident that
Lauda will retain his crown in 1976.
Niki Lauda was a very
professional driver.
He can see the strategy,
he can really understand when was
the moment to push a little more,
a little bit less,
and was extremely fast
and so consistent.
But in Britain
a new challenger has emerged.
Ladies and gentlemen, James Hunt.
APPLAUSE
James Hunt has signed for British
team McLaren -
Ferrari's arch rivals,
but he has yet to prove
he is championship material.
British drivers and British cars,
for that matter,
have dominated Grand Prix racing
and our domination had
dropped off a little bit now
and I just feel very ambitious
to take up the cudgels.
I think James was hugely popular
because he was an attractive
character.
He was a Brit
and loved in this country already.
But I don't think people thought
he had anything like
the chance that Niki Lauda had.
Hunt is better known for his
romantic exploits than his driving.
I once talked to Jackie Stewart
who had this thing about the car
being a woman.
And you drove the car like you
made love to a woman.
Do you have
the same poetic turn...?
I'd sooner stick to the women.
LAUGHTER
With his last team,
his cavalier style had earned him
the nickname "Hunt the Shunt".
Now, McLaren team manager
Alastair Caldwell
has reservations about Hunt
joining the team.
The '76 season got off to
a very interesting start for us.
James didn't have a drive
and we didn't have a driver,
so we were thrown into bed with him.
He rang me up and said,
"I think I'm your new driver."
I said, "I guess you are."
One of the first things
you noticed is
when the car was
switched off on the grid,
he was so wound up,
the whole car was shaking
with his nervous energy.
He had a lot of adrenaline in him,
that's for sure.
But that's one of the reasons
he was a good racing driver.
He was always competitive.
And always very focused on something
he wanted to do,
be it budgerigars as a teenager,
or train sets or Scalextric
or something as a small boy.
James was a sportsman,
through and through.
He never played team games,
his sports
were all solitary.
He was very single-minded
and he knew what he wanted.
He wanted to be World Champion.
The 1976 season will
consist of 16 races over 10 months,
running from January to October
at locations across the world.
It is not just Lauda
and Hunt that are in competition -
15 different teams,
each with two drivers,
are in the fight for the title.
But Ferrari and McLaren
are the leading contenders.
Ferrari were my arch enemies.
Daniele Audetto
was their team manager,
so I was at war with them.
Ferrari has a history
much bigger,
much longer than McLaren.
We couldn't compete with them
on money
but we could compete with them
in style and in efficiency.
They're a lot bigger team
and incredibly Italian.
I think we respect each other
professionally
but I don't have a beer with him
in the pub,
if you want an example.
Race one is in the scorching heat
of the Interlargos circuit
in Brazil.
Each race will cover
a distance of 200 miles in
approximately two hours but first,
each driver races against the clock
to set the best possible lap time.
The driver with the best
time will be rewarded with
first place on the starting line.
Pole position.
In the thick of the action is pit
lane reporter, Peter Windsor.
In the distance,
you'd hear an engine note,
and four minutes later,
the car would reach you
and all four
wheels would be off the ground.
And you'd think,
"Wow, this is Formula One."
The news on the track in Brazil is
that Hunt is fast.
To everyone's amazement
he makes the best lap time
and gains his first-ever
pole position.
What I remember most is Niki Lauda
looking up the pit lane and thinking,
"What's going on here?"
Because nobody really knew,
including Niki,
how good he would be.
Do you just want to get a level?
If I say "shucks" and BLEEP
and all that sort of stuff...
Oh, dear. I'll cancel it, then.
Can we rub that out?
He might have had some good lines
for the microphones,
he might have had
a roving eye for the girls,
but in the cockpit,
he was very serious.
Hunt takes his place at the front
of the starting grid,
just ahead of Lauda.
The World Champion's car carries
the coveted number one,
but all eyes are on the Hunt
in car number 11.
Lauda gets the best start, with
Hunt's McLaren chasing hard behind.
Sadly, in the race, part of the fuel
system or the engine fell off,
so he flew off the road,
which wasn't his fault.
So it wasn't a fairy-tale beginning,
but everybody left Brazil
very pleased
that James was obviously quick.
Lauda has seen off Hunt's challenge
and collects nine points to start
building his score.
The points scoring system was
disarmingly simple.
Nine points for a win, six for
second, four for third,
down to sixth place where you
got one point.
We didn't know it would become
so complicated.
In an age when Concorde is
taking its first passenger flight
and synth music is capturing
the imagination, Lauda's highly
technical approach perfectly suits
a time falling in love with
technology.
MUSIC: "Autobahn" by Kraftwerk
Lauda is a complete driver -
preparing his Ferrari
meticulously before every race.
He could stay in the garage
until maybe eight
o'clock in the evening
to stay with the mechanic,
to make sure he does the job
properly
and to understand what
they are doing.
Because Niki is a perfectionist.
What he's doing,
he want to do it to his best.
At Lauda's side is his wife,
Marlene.
Marlene was a fantastic young lady.
She was a beautiful lady,
but for Niki she was also a big
moral supporter,
and I think was a big
part of his success.
Lauda knows how to get the best
out of his team.
Niki Lauda had really learned
how to make Ferrari work for him.
An awful lot of very good drivers
went to Ferrari
and never quite made it work.
It had a terrifying presence
of Enzo Ferrari,
with his dark glasses,
looming over the whole thing.
Incidere senz'altro, perche...
After nearly five decades
in motor racing, the 78-year-old
Enzo Ferrari rules his family
business with an iron fist.
Mr Ferrari lost his temper and say,
"I am the boss here,
you have to do what I want."
He did have his favourites
and Niki, clearly,
had got close to Enzo
Ferrari in that way,
and I think the bottom line is Enzo
Ferrari liked to win.
He loved winners.
He cared about the results.
And Lauda delivers, pulling further
and further ahead of Hunt
with every race,
but at the fourth round in Spain,
Lauda has worrying news for Audetto.
"Daniele, I have a problem."
"What happened?"
"I fell off from my tractor
"in my house, in my garden
"and I broke two or three ribs."
I said, "My God -
two or three ribs?!"
He had a gardening accident,
I think.
I think he was mowing his lawn
in Austria with a garden tractor
and it rolled on him, which is
quite a common occurrence
with garden tractors.
James had this approach to it all,
which was,
"He's no problem.
Halfway through the race, his ribs
"will give up and I'll pass him and
win the race." It's exactly what
happened!
# There was something
in the air that night
# The stars were bright
Fernando... #
'His first win for Marlboro McLaren.'
You're still extremely fast.
How do you do it?
Big balls.
# Though we never
thought that we could lose
# There's no regrets... #
But Hunt's victory is short-lived.
In the scrutineering area
afterwards,
there was this unheard-of situation
where the car was disqualified
and that was something nobody in
Formula One really was prepared for.
Teams are allowed to modify the car
to suit each circuit,
but they must work within
strict regulations.
One centimetre in a Formula One car
makes such a big difference.
In Spain, Hunt's car had been found
to be just over a centimetre
too wide.
Before the race, the car was
measured by the organisers,
and every day,
they didn't say anything.
I'm pretty sure
they were talking to Ferrari
cos there was kindred spirit there -
the Spanish-speaking Catholic
country.
Ferrari were saying,
"Sh! Keep it shtoom. Say nothing."
I was never involved
with the scrutineering.
I was involved with MY
scrutineering, with my cars,
because I want that my car respect,
100%, the rules, because otherwise,
Ferrari kill me.
Hunt's points are given to Lauda -
and it looks like McLaren will
leave Spain empty-handed.
We immediately appealed
cos we thought
the penalty didn't fit the crime.
It was like being hung for
stealing a loaf of bread.
They pretend in the appeal to say
that this was difference was
not affecting
the performance of the car.
BLEEP.
Had you any idea that the car
might be thrown out?
No. I don't know,
I just drive the damn thing.
Although their teams are at war,
both drivers are trying to steer
clear of politics, but despite
their different characters,
their passion for racing is a bond.
Niki spent time in our pits.
He was always visiting us and his
grasp of English was very good.
He was always known as The Rat,
cos he looked like a rat.
So he was called Rat to his face.
James said, "Hello, Rat."
They meshed well,
because they weren't actually
directly in competition from looks.
MUSIC: "Tear The Roof Off The Sucker"
by Parliament
The wild side of '70s
Formula One is revealed in this
recently discovered
footage of an after-race party.
Hunt is the star -
with Lauda in the wings.
For sure,
Niki was in awe of James' good looks
and personality.
James was the good-looking playboy
and Niki was the small Austrian
who looked like a rat.
They were good friends,
though on the racetrack, of course,
no quarter given.
The race driver persona can change
completely - once on the racetrack,
all this is forgotten.
All successful racing drivers
are invested with an enormous ego.
They all think they're the quickest.
They can't imagine they're not the
fastest racing driver in the world.
To admit to anything else but that
would be ludicrous.
Niki and James both though they were
the best racing driver in the world.
As the season approaches halfway,
and even when the points from Spain
are reinstated, it's Lauda who still
dominates with double Hunt's points.
MUSIC: "More Than A Feeling"
by Boston
When the Grand Prix circus moves
to Britain, the country is
sweltering in temperatures
reaching 35 degrees centigrade.
Skirts were getting shorter.
It was getting hotter.
England was baking, the whole
of Europe was. It never rained.
We slept in the garden for months.
It was quite a remarkable year,
in more ways than one.
But behind the sunny mirage,
Britain is in the grip of political
uncertainty and economic upheaval -
inflation is rampant
and for ordinary people,
the future is anything but certain.
We all know how hard
the employment market is just now
for new entrants
and I know how much harder it is
and has been for many of you
to get your first job.
# More than a feeling... #
The return of Hunt
is a welcome distraction.
I think the British public saw James
as a sort of hero figure...
Hello, girls.
..somebody they could admire
who was giving two fingers
to the Establishment.
It looked good in what might be
a rather austere time for other
people.
MUSIC: "Get It On" by T Rex
He had a sort of freedom about him.
He didn't really care what
people thought.
Hunt's unpredictable
personality is a potential
problem for the team's sponsor,
Marlboro cigarettes.
HE COUGHS
Excuse me, I've been
training for my new sponsors.
JACKIE STEWART LAUGHS
Image is everything for the American
brand and John Hogan, the man
from Marlboro, has been tasked with
keeping the young sportsman in line.
He was this very brash figure
with a trail of destruction
behind him.
That was going to be
new for McLaren,
which was quite a straight-laced
organisation
and also for his sponsors -
which were also straight-laced
organisations.
In the year colour television sales
overtake black-and-white, Hunt's
car flashes Marlboro's distinctive
red-and-white brand across the
screen - and with it, he brings
his own unique splash of colour.
Turning up to a dinner party
in black tie and flip-flops
was, to James, pretty normal.
Because he had this...I don't know
what the British call savoir-faire,
he was able to carry it off.
James changed the way
Marlboro looked.
It was the first
and probably only example
of a sponsor being moulded
by the driver and not vice versa.
'This is Brands Hatch, just outside
of London in the Kent countryside.
'Today is British Grand Prix day.
'The biggest day on Britain's
motor-sport calendar.'
The race is sold out.
Britain is in the grip
of Hunt Fever.
A record 80,000 spectators fill the
circuit and all eyes are on one man.
Brands Hatch is packed.
Every grandstand is packed,
every grassy bank is packed.
The reason - because they're hoping
to see the first English victory
in the John Player British
Grand Prix
since Peter Collins won,
in a Ferrari, of course,
way back in 1958.
At Brands Hatch, what you had was
a front row, after qualifying,
which looked as though it was
setting the race up perfectly,
because you had Niki Lauda
and James Hunt
on the front row,
Clay Regazzoni behind
in the other Ferrari.
There is drama right from the start.
Clay Regazzoni managed to
drive into the back wheel
of Lauda,
so the two Ferraris actually
collided.
Complete mayhem began.
'Laffite sends Hunt flying.'
James' car landed
on the left front corner,
but being a McLaren, didn't break.
And being James, with the two pints
of adrenaline, he didn't stop.
He charged off with the front wheels
splayed out, like this.
'Drivers who escaped the pile-up
'are soon flagged down
and the race called to a halt.'
James was immediately thinking,
"I've got to get back to the pits
and have the car mended."
I got out of trouble completely.
I never hit anybody.
I stopped on the left.
And they BLEEP came and piled
into me.
Can you tell us what happened?
There's a race going on, dear boy.
The race has ground to
a complete halt.
The organisers want to restart
immediately
but Hunt's damaged car is
not on the grid.
In the chaos, in the pit,
he comes running up to me.
I said, "What's the car like?"
He said,
"The car's destroyed, a write-off."
I wandered down to have
a look at the race car
and realised the race car was
repairable.
James explanation that it was
a "write-off" was not true.
Caldwell and McLaren will have to
act quickly. There are only minutes
to spare.
It was thought that James Hunt
would not be allowed
to take the restart.
And the crowd got behind James
as a driver they wanted to see
in that restart
in a way that you don't see
outside a soccer match.
SLOW HANDCLAPPING
The slow handclap which ran
from the start/finish line
all the way up to Paddock Bend
and all the way round South Bank
and round to Westfield Bend
and then it became boos
and then it became catcalls.
CROWD: We want Hunt! We want Hunt!
Then, the marshals had to
rush onto the track,
to pick up beer cans and coke cans
and even bottles.
I've never seen, at a motor race,
quite such an extraordinary
display from the public.
"We want James Hunt,
we want James Hunt."
A mini riot was going on...
which was not very British.
McLaren were delighted that there
was this confusion and delay
because it gave them a little more
time to mend James Hunt's car.
'When they return to the grid,
the crowd goes wild.
'Now James Hunt is certain
to start again.'
Ferrari, you could see them,
their faces fell
cos they knew instantly what
had happened -
we had fixed the race car.
What I remember most of all
is Niki Lauda in a rage,
getting back into his car.
He had suddenly realised how
much time had passed
and that McLaren had had
time to repair
their race car again
and get it onto the grid,
and he was absolutely livid.
'Back to the grid,
and off they go again.'
After another chaotic start,
Lauda storms ahead, with Hunt
chasing hard on his tail.
'The battle's really on now
between Niki Lauda and James Hunt.'
Niki Lauda in the Ferrari leading,
James Hunt,
cheered on by the British crowd,
gradually winding him in.
As we went past half distance,
the cars go round
Paddock Bend,
down to the bottom of the hill,
up the hill and behind the trees.
As the cars then came back
into our sight,
the McLaren was in front.
And that's when the crowd erupted.
# It's more than a feeling... #
'Britain's James Hunt, in a Marlboro
McLaren, wins the British Grand
Prix.'
And we did win the
British Grand Prix, fair and square.
James, how much does this
victory mean to you?
Nine points, $20,000
and a lot of happiness.
Can I grab that cigarette off you?
Thanks.
CHEERING
But Ferrari is about to
spoil the party...
I think Ferrari appealed
straightaway after the race
that we didn't comply
with the rules.
We couldn't work out what
kind of rule they thought
we hadn't complied with.
The rule says, and I am surprised but
I am not surprised Alastair doesn't
know well the rules,
that is another example,
that you have to complete
the racecourse, even if the race
is suspended.
Instead of completing a lap,
as the race was stopped,
Hunt had taken a shortcut
back to the pits.
In cutting behind the Paddock,
he didn't complete the race distance.
Simple than that.
For now, the race winning
points are Hunt's, but the result
hangs in the balance, waiting on a
hearing scheduled for months later.
The next race is at the notorious
Nurburgring in Germany.
The Nurburgring was a frightening
but fantastic racetrack.
It's 14.7 miles round,
goes up and down thousands of feet,
it's got hundreds of corners.
It was generally hostile to
fast racing cars,
which was part of its appeal.
Three-times World Champion Jackie
Stewart had driven the course to
highlight the dangers of a track
that had claimed more than 50 lives.
Every time I see this,
it frightens me.
There's no barriers
on the right-hand side,
there's just a rock face
and trees.
You have a left-hand-side barrier
but that's not where you'll
go off the road.
I think if I were to walk round them,
I would he horrified and never drive
round the place again.
The faster you drive round the ring,
the less you know,
and maybe that's
the best thing to do.
For a quick lap at the Nurburgring,
you probably experience
more in seven minutes
and six or seven seconds
than most people have
experienced in all their life.
It was a pre-health-and-safety era.
Motor racing was dangerous.
It said so
on the back of every ticket.
And it was part of what it was.
Nearly every year in Formula One,
a driver had been killed.
By this stage, I'd lost
my brother in a racing car accident.
After that, I thought,
"I won't befriend racing drivers.
"I'll have them
as people who work for me,
"but I won't become their friend,
"because I don't want to go
to their funeral as a friend.
"I want to go
as their team manager."
For Lauda, the Nurburgring isn't
worth the risk.
He calls a meeting of the drivers
in an attempt to have it stopped.
But his fellow drivers don't agree.
He loses by one vote,
and now has no choice but to race.
For the first time in the season,
it is raining on Race Day -
but the track is
so long that not all of it is wet -
the choice of tyres will be crucial.
Wet tyres, they're quite tall -
they have
big tread on them like a road tyre,
unlike the slicks,
which are smooth, no tread at all.
Like most of the field, Lauda starts
the race on wet weather tyres
but quickly discovers he is losing
too much speed on every dry
section of the track.
After the first lap,
many drivers come into the pits
to change the tyres,
it was really chaos.
The pit stop was a little bit slow.
When Niki started
for the second lap,
with the slick,
he was about maybe
in tenth position.
For a driver, it's not good
psychologically to go to
race on a circuit
that you judge is too dangerous.
It puts you in a condition
that you are afraid.
When he restarted on the second lap,
it was not the cool Niki
that we know.
Lauda will not complete the lap.
His helmet comes off in the impact.
He is trapped in a fire burning
at over 400 degrees centigrade.
It will be nearly a minute before
Lauda is pulled from the flames.
I put his head on my lap.
Didn't want him to lie flat.
But he was conscious
and talked all the way through.
He said, "Is my face burned,
is it burned?"
I replied, "Don't worry, it's OK."
In fact,
his forehead was badly burned
and his scalp was actually charred.
rather than telling him all this,
we tried to keep him as quiet
and composed as possible.
Lauda is rushed to hospital.
Amongst the drivers who arrive just
after the crash is James Hunt.
We weren't aware Niki was in trouble
because there were racing
drivers at the scene
and he was conscious
and talking to everybody
so the drivers came back to the pits
and said,
"Niki's burnt but he's OK,
he's fine."
With the track cleared, the race is
restarted and Hunt is victorious.
He is now just 14 points
behind Lauda.
Then the news came
through that he was
gravely ill,
so that cast a shadow over
the whole thing.
I can remember it now and thinking,
"He isn't going to live,"
and I felt absolutely horrendous.
I felt like the bottom had
fallen out of my world.
When we arrived at the hospital,
Niki was, little by little,
losing consciousness.
Whilst Lauda battles for his life,
Ferrari are already
looking for another driver.
I was speaking with Ferrari
all the time about the accident
and Ferrari said to me,
"Ferrari will live,
with or without Niki.
"You don't need to stay
in the hospital.
"We need you to go
back to the circuit
"and find another driver,
"because if Niki will not drive,
"Ferrari will not stop."
Once he had been the protege
of Enzo Ferrari, but for Enzo,
giving up on the World Championship
is not an option.
Press and the public like to
concentrate on the driver as being
the most important member
of the team, but he's not at all.
A driver is very much replaceable.
The unfortunate idea of the two
McLaren drivers
being involved in a motorway
accident together
and dying -
do you think their team would be
in the back
row of the grid at the next race?
No, they won't be,
cos they'll just hire
two more hot shoes
and they'll be right up there.
Hunt takes full
advantage in the next two races,
closing the gap to just two points.
With Niki Lauda, his main opponent,
likely to be in hospital
for some time,
his chances of winning
the title are pretty good.
Lauda has second and third-degree
burns to his face and hands.
Part of his scalp has been
burnt away.
He has lost half of one ear
and his lungs are barely working.
I was suddenly aware,
through the accident,
how quickly you can die.
I remember my wife coming
and she burst in tears,
so she was very much affected
when she saw me there.
I said, "BLEEP, if she's crying,
I must be in a bad stage."
But in racing, the risk
and taking chances was
exactly the same
as it was before,
because this was part of the game.
'Just 40 days after doctors had
given up hope
'and a priest had
knelt at his bedside,
'the Austrian ace climbed
back into the cockpit
'of his glaring red Ferrari.
'His friends and colleagues claim
'that his miracle recovery had more
to do with his iron will
'than with master surgery.'
With five races left and everything
still to play for, Lauda is back.
When I came to the hospital,
you feel a kind of...
you feel you are very tired.
And you would like to go and sleep
but you know it's not just going
sleeping, it's something else.
And then you just fight
with the brain.
You hear noises
and you hear voices
and you just try to listen
to what they're saying
and try to keep your brain working
and to get the body ready to fight
against illness.
I think this was very good
that I did that
because in that way, I survived.
Niki Lauda
was recovering so fast
that he proposed to Ferrari
to race in Monza.
Ferrari said, "No, don't,
"because if we lose the championship
at the end of the year,
"it's better you don't start
so early,
"because then
we can say you had an accident.
"This was exactly
the opposite of what I was thinking."
At Lauda's side is his wife,
Marlene.
She has been with him
throughout his recovery but
Monza is the last place
she wants him to be.
Monza, Italy.
Home to Ferrari and their fans.
After coming within
seconds of being burnt to death,
Lauda returns to a hero's welcome.
When we went to Monza,
the focus was on Niki -
110%.
We took him inside
the garage,
he took out the balaclava
and his face was a mask
of blood.
I said, "My God, how can he race?"
It was pouring with
rain on his return.
This is the Nurburgring carrying on,
almost, you know,
the gloom of the Nurburgring.
Is there any psychological
after-effects from this
accident for you at all?
I don't think so.
Everything looks good.
Lauda prepares to go
back on the track to
race against the clock for his place
on the starting grid.
The pressure was on. Ferrari called.
Should I race or not race?
It was a huge pressure on me
for that particular race.
The physical scars have begun to
heal but the mental ones run deeper.
I came to the circuit,
wanted to drive out of the pits
and couldn't drive.
And I suddenly was hit by the whole
four weeks' accident problems -
all these kind of things.
And I just couldn't drive.
I did one slow lap,
went back into the pits.
I said, "I go back there
and I drive for myself."
And in the end of the day,
I was quickest Ferrari
and was right back like before.
Just before the race begins,
Hunt's team, McLaren, are having
problems of their own - their fuel
has been ruled to be illegal.
We were made to pump the fuel
out of our cars,
fill up with standard
fuel at the racetrack
and start on the back of the grid.
So we were shafted by the Italians.
But they're very good at this.
The Italian Mafiosi
managed to get us on the back row of
that grid.
How is it feeling,
fighting against Niki again?
Hard work.
When he first met him, James said
straightaway,
"Niki, you're the only person I know
who could be in a fire and come out
better looking."
For Niki,
this race is life-or-death.
"I finish and I go in the points
or I lose the championship
"here in Monza."
Stuck at the back of the grid,
Hunt makes a charge on the first
lap, but as he tries to fight his
way through,
he almost immediately spins
out of the race.
'The partisan Italian crowd
cheers for only two things today -
'a Ferrari competitor
'or their most serious
challenger for the World Championship
'in trouble.
'Here it is - the latter.'
Poor James didn't enjoy
the walk back
past the Italian fans.
Actually, knowing James,
he probably loved it.
Lauda's wife, Marlene,
can only watch.
Incredibly,
Niki finished not only the race,
but finished fourth.
That was something incredible.
CROWD: Niki Lauda!
Hunt and McLaren jet off to practise
for the Canadian Grand Prix,
but their troubles
are far from over.
In Paris, Ferrari presents its case
for overturning McLaren's
win at the British Grand Prix.
There were gentlemen in blazers
wearing old school ties
who were meant to decide on matters
of whether people should be
disqualified,
drivers should start or not start.
None of them really seemed to have
read the rule book very clearly.
These three old boys turned up
and were introduced to the saintly
Niki before they went in,
which was all part of Ferrari's...
..psychological warfare.
So they all went in, going, "We've
touched the hand of Saint Niki..."
The verdict goes against McLaren
and nine vital points are deducted.
So we didn't win
the British Grand Prix,
and there's no appeal to
this appeal.
That's the end of it.
With so many points lost and only
three races to go, the odds are
heavily against Hunt, and the strain
is showing between him and Lauda.
I hope that on the other
end of this telephone
we have James Hunt, who's a very
long way away in Toronto.
Hello, James. Good afternoon to you.
'Afternoon, Frank.'
Disappointed with this decision
but are you really surprised?
'Yes, I was very surprised
'because, as far as the rules were
concerned,
'there was no question -
Ferrari had no case.'
We've just pulled off the tapes
here in London
as I've been talking to you
a quote from Niki Lauda.
He has reacted to the news,
quite understandably, by saying,
"I'm madly delighted,"
and he goes on to say that,
"I am satisfied, not just
because this will be good for me,
"because at least a positive
decision has been taken
"in the interests of the sport."
What do you say to that?
'Well, it's the sort of rubbish
you'd expect.
'The guy has, you know,
had a very bad accident.
'He's been very brave
and done every well.
'But he'd do well to
considerate it as a sport.'
I see. You are very critical
about the way he behaves, are you?
'Niki isn't a sportsman -
Niki's interested in one thing,
and that's Niki.'
I don't want to discuss
if the decision was wrong or right.
At least, I expected James to
react in the same way -
to respect me as a driver.
And fight
if he wants against Ferrari.
I decided we couldn't possibly
win the World Championship
from this position now
without these points
and stopped trying to control
James' excesses,
which became quite excessive.
MUSIC: "Rhiannon" by Fleetwood Mac
We were staying in a great, big
motel
on the side of the freeway
in Toronto
and there was a live
band in the bar.
And the lead singer was a bit like
Stevie Nicks - blonde,
little dynamite creature,
so James managed to pull her.
We had to get up early in the
morning to go out to the warm-up
and he came down, dishevelled,
with this lady -
obviously...anyway..
"dishevelled" might be the best
way of putting it, staggered off
to the racetrack,
won the race!
# You can go your own way... #
Sex - the breakfast of champions.
In this particular case,
it worked out.
The win in Canada gives Hunt
nine vital points
and in the next race,
he remains on form.
He storms through to another victory
and takes the podium.
But Lauda is still
ahead by three points.
After 10 months and 15 races,
the championship has come
down to the very last Grand Prix.
For the first time ever,
the final race is in Japan.
Excitement about the season has
reached fever pitch -
only three points separate
Hunt and Lauda.
This will be the first race ever to
be broadcast live by satellite
across the world.
Determined to win it,
so in order to do that,
the best way for me
to do it is to the win the race here.
But on race day,
the weather threatens to bring
the season to a premature end.
'It couldn't be
worse at the Fuji circuit.
'Pouring rain, thick mist
and it's a delayed start,
'so is the Japanese Grand Prix
on or off?'
All the drivers got together
and said,
"This is ridiculous."
Not only was Niki Lauda saying that,
James Hunt also said,
"This race should not take place."
Being nice and wet again.
James and Niki were both
on the Drivers' Safety Committee,
so they were in the tower, arguing
that the race shouldn't be held,
so we had this direct confrontation.
I said to him, "If we don't race,
James, you can't win the World
Championship."
"No, Jack, we can't race -
it's too dangerous."
All very above board
but a bit irritating when you're
trying to win the World Championship
and you can't if you don't race.
The race has now been
delayed for nearly two hours.
The rain continues to fall
but the race organisers have
reached a decision.
The race director came in and said,
"We have to start."
We all looked out and said, "Excuse
me? It's the same rain as before.
"Why?" "Because of television."
In two hours, it will be too dark.
And we have the satellite TV that
cost a lot of money.
And we have a contract with
the organiser
to at least start the race,
otherwise we lose money.
The teams, the drivers,
I lose the money
if we don't at least start the race.
'But the race is on.
'James Hunt, in his McLaren,
'getting ready for a lap
of the circuit
'and next, out comes Niki Lauda
'to join the grid with
the rest of the competitors.'
The drivers have been forced
onto the starting grid
by the demands of the vast TV
audience they have created.
'This, then, is the clincher -
'the World Championship decider.
'Three points separate the leader,
Niki Lauda, in the Ferrari,
'and Britain's James Hunt
in the McLaren.
'It's going to be a fantastic race.'
In Britain, it's three
in the morning.
Hunt's parents and friends
are watching the live satellite
broadcast in a TV studio, but his
sister, Sally,
is at home, glued to the radio.
We switched on the radio very
early in the morning
and I can remember walking
round the house
with the radio clamped to my ear.
The tension was amazing.
'Who is going to reach
the corner first?
'James Hunt takes
the lead in the Japanese Grand Prix
'and fifth, that's Niki Lauda.'
Hunt takes the lead
but for the other drivers following,
the water spray is dangerously
reducing visibility to almost zero,
and all the cars are skidding
and sliding in the heavy rain.
'Brambilla going through and Hunt has
leapt round. They haven't let him
through.
'Side-by-side, and Brambilla spins!
'And he missed Hunt by inches.
'And Niki Lauda has
pulled into the pits in front of us.
'The world champion has
gone into the pits.'
Niki stopped -
"It's too dangerous, I stop."
'Yes, this amazing 1976
World Championship series
'is maintaining its drama,
'because Niki Lauda,
leading the World Championship,
'is out of the race,
'but, amazingly enough,
there's nothing wrong with his car.'
I tell him,
"Niki, what you have to say
"is that you have a technical
failure or something."
"No," he said to me, "tell them
that it is too dangerous to race."
When you are a normal racing driver,
and you are not affected
by an accident,
you have reserves.
So that means your level
of risk-taking
is higher
than, like in my case,
you've just come out of death
and had everything happening to you.
Then, a couple of races later,
you have to face this
more-difficult situation
with the water and rain and risk
going up,
and at that time, I was not prepared
to take this extra risk,
because of the accident.
Emotionally, for me,
it was impossible to tell Niki
to go back to race,
because you see his eyes were
really terrorised.
Lauda is out of the race.
But he will still become
World Champion
if Hunt fails to score
enough points.
Then the rain stopped and the water
disappeared on the circuit
and the circuit got better -
by coincidence, basically.
But I was not racing
and I would still do the same today.
Hunt must finish third or higher
to take the championship,
but as the track dries out, his
wet-weather tyres begin to overheat.
One of the techniques you could do
was cool them down
by running in puddles
deliberately on the straits.
So we put this sign out -
"cool tyres",
but James refused to
acknowledge or do this.
"Cool the tyres! Cool the tyres!"
And he's down the middle
of the road, oblivious.
Eventually,
he wore all the rubber off them,
all the canvas, down to the air.
And he had TWO flat tyres.
With five laps to go,
he came into the pits.
We thought perhaps it would all
go wrong for James.
'And Hunt is in the pits
in second place,
'and if he drops below fourth,
'if he goes out,
'his World Championship will
be in danger.
'What an incredible
change of fortune...'
Because he had two flat tyres,
we couldn't jack the car up
very well,
so the car was too low to get
the jack underneath,
so a mechanic and I had to pick up
the left front of the car,
so it took us
24 seconds or something
to change the tyres.
'And James Hunt gets away.
'And now he is in fifth position
'and out of the contention.'
With the championship
seemingly beyond his grasp, Hunt,
the sportsman, throws caution
to the wind and makes his charge
for the finish.
'And James Hunt is passing Jones!
'Hunt is fourth and Regazzoni
is out of the race,
'so now Hunt moves up to
third position.
'And James Hunt IS going to
win the World Championship
'if he just keeps
going in the place he's in now.
'And he does it.'
James Hunt finishes third.
James Hunt is champion of the world.
THEY CHEER
We were all whizzing about
sort of cheering
and excited because James was
now World Champion.
'I think the scenes in the McLaren
pits will speak for themselves.'
But right now, Hunt himself has no
idea the championship is his.
James Hunt came into the pits
in a rage
and as the McLaren team
gathered round,
James got out of the car,
pulled off his crash helmet,
started to rant and rave at them,
and Teddy Mayer was holding
up three fingers
saying, "James, you're third.
"You're Champion."
And gradually, the penny dropped.
It was an extraordinary moment.
There was a lot of excitement and,
"Does he know yet?"
and, "Is it true?"
Suddenly it was true
and he was World Champion.
Hunt has won,
despite ignoring team orders.
I was not best pleased with him.
You won't see me
in any of the photographs.
I'm nowhere near him,
cos I just want to punch him
in the mouth.
Even though he IS
the World Champion.
'I feel really sorry for Niki
'in that I feel sorry for everybody
that the race had to be run
'in such ridiculous circumstances.
'Quite honestly,
'I wanted to win the championship
'and I felt I deserved to win
the championship.
'I also felt Niki deserved
to win the championship
'and I just wish
we could have shared it.'
I said at the same time,
at the time there,
if anybody should get
the championship,
then I'm happy it's James.
Because I liked him
and we were not buddies
but we are at least sympathetic,
so I think we took
care of each other
from the heart in a very nice way,
which in these days, the heart was
never shown in Formula One.
MUSIC: "Young Hearts Run Free"
by Candi Staton
'Hunt, who came into Heathrow
early today, said,
'"I don't think I've stopped
celebrating since the race."'
We met James coming home.
There was James looking
slightly dazed,
he was probably
so completely out of it.
He'd drunk quite
a lot on the way home.
Very tired and somewhat hung over,
thank you very much.
What was the party like?
It was long. But good.
Then we all went off to a party.
I have to say my memory's
a bit hazy after that,
because I think I drank more
champagne for breakfast than
I ever had before.
Hunt and Lauda would never have
such a close race again
but the legacy of the first
superstars of Grand Prix
helped shape Formula One into the
global TV sport it is today.
The excitement of that season meant
that no self-respecting country
could allow its television service
not to cover Formula One properly.
So suddenly,
Formula One was available everywhere.
We had James
and Niki coming out of this
as these two titans of their time.
Who could have predicted that?
It was just the most amazing season.
'In life, you need a certain
amount of luck.
'The question is how much
luck you need.
'I think the luck is the minimum.
'I think human beings can
do much more
'for themselves than they think.'
We have to remember only
the good things.
That was a good fight.
I don't think I thought of him
as my little brother then,
although that's what he was.
I just thought,
"It's James, who I love,
"and my friend, and he's achieved
what he wants to achieve."
That was very exciting.
'How do you want to do it?
'Go at a steady pace for 70 years
'or flat-out for ten years
and then relax,
'and I rather like doing it
that way.'
At the time, you said,
"If you wrote this as a film script,
"people would say,
'That's ridiculous.
"'You've got to have something
believable. You can't have this
farcical story.'"
But the farcical story is true.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd