[Man narrating]
During the Warring States Period,
China was made up of
dozens of nations.
Countless fights between states.
Society was in devastation.
The 7 largest states were known as
Qi, Chu, Yan, Han, Zhao, Wei and Qin.
The rest was nearly wiped out
a hundred years before the unification.
Qin then conquered Han and Zhao
subsequently.
Year 227 B.C.
When Wei's troops marching towards
the state of Liang.
they were ambushed by Liang
at Mt. Phoenix.
Both sides suffered heavily.
Death toll reached 3,000.
SDH/Translation: Arigon
[Crow gargling]
[Wolf howling]
[Crow continues gargling]
[Spring bouncing]
Third bro.
You're not lucky as I am.
[Crow gargling]
Big soldier: General!
Man: Who are you?
Liang's soldier.
[Man gasping]
[Yelling]
[Spring bouncing]
[Groaning in pain]
[Both yelling]
[Groaning]
[Groaning in pain]
[Big Soldier singing]
One main road leads to homecoming
My home is right at
the foot of Mt. Liang
Soils are rich there
5 acres of farms
Pretty good.
5 acres of farm
What to grow?
[Big Soldier]
Let me tell you something.
When I was a boy, I caught a boar.
My dad had me let go of it.
You know why?
There were boys
inside that belly.
You have boys, huh?
You know what,
you're my captive now.
Hey, hey.
[Groaning]
You've lost few blood.
Not a big deal.
This is the drug developed
by my family.
Don't spare this to anyone.
You hurt, huh?
Now it gonna hurt more.
[Groaning in great pain]
You're welcome, young man!
Big Soldier: You'll live, you know.
Wei's General: X+@#?
And don't curse.
My dad said,
Scratch when you're itchy,
Smile when you ain't lucky!
Pretty good.
Mmm?
[Yelling]
[Moaning]
[Blood splashing]
Ah!
General.
Deputy General Yu.
Yu:
Yes, I am.
Wei's General:
Hang on a sec.
Why you're here?
Yu:
In pursuit of Liang's men.
Wei's General: In pursuit?
How many have you killed?
Wei's General:
Speak.
Yu: One.
- My men must fight hard.
Yu: Liang's came hard on us...
Wei's General:
Defend our nation with our lives.
Yu: Please, for the sake of...
- AWOL personnel must face penalty.
Yu: General, my company was
all gone last night.
Wei's General:
Gone? I was there last night.
In fact, we were ambushed.
And you were the traitor.
You're so cruel.
He saved your life, and you took his.
Hey, hey, hey,
what you gonna do, huh?
He was right.
You're all dead.
Kill me.
I don't kill POW.
Now, keep begging. I might let
you go, if you tried hard enough.
Wei's General:
Just kill me.
You really want to die?
Here, let me help you.
Too bad,
I failed my mission.
[Big Soldier chuckling]
Want to die, huh?
Die another day.
Prince Wen, we've accomplished.
Like he said, to die with
dignity in a battle field.
You're AWOL.
Big Soldier:
Not exactly. Just playing dead.
My dad said, no shame for
living to fight another day,
only for being dead in vain.
Poor Third bro didn't listen to me.
He refused to play dead.
- How much am I worth?
- It doesn't hurt to tell you.
General alive: 5 acres of farm land.
5 acres, eh.
I have a jade medal in possession.
How much is this broken thingy worth?
A lot.
I'll keep it as a gift.
But I don't believe you.
Wei's soldier:
He's one of us. Still alive.
We were ambushed...
[Groans in great pain]
[Thundering]
Big Soldier:
Anybody home?
[Gasping]
[Moaning]
Somebody, bring me meatloaf and liquor!
Hey.
A big shot like you,
what would you say now, huh?
"Absurd!
Take him outside for beheading."
Big Soldier:
Nothing to eat in here.
Whoa! Hmm...
[Yelling]
Woman:
General, spare me.
[Sighs]
Wu: Liang's archer and infantry unit;
2,000 men in total.
Ambushed our 1,000-strong elite unit.
Both sides were totally wiped out.
Prince Wen:
This is the sword I gave him.
But where is he now?
Wu:
I believe we will find him.
Prince:
Wu,
only if he's still among the living.
Big Soldier:
War is everywhere now,
where else you can go?
Woman:
General, have you heard of Shen Shu?
The one in Mt. Phoenix?
A fortunate-telling tree.
Is he your captive?
He's my good luck.
Hang in there.
We're almost there.
Wei's General:
How far?
2 days.
[Groans]
Small potato.
Don't make me do this.
Don't.
Don't push your luck.
Wei's General:
Give me liquor.
- No can do.
- Liquor.
Woman:
You've fought many battles, haven't you?
Big Soldier: Many.
You can say I'm a big time warrior.
[Wei's General whispering]
Untie me.
Woman:
Then you must have killed a lot.
Big Soldier:
Just too many.
Fought against 8 men at a time.
Like yesterday.
[Door falls]
[Raining]
Woman:
General, would you take me too?
I'd like to become your captive.
Okay.
I know some musical.
General, keep drinking.
I'll entertain you.
[Woman singing]
Man: If he turns out to be alive, what then?
Wu: Keep in mind that he's already dead.
[Woman continues singing]
[Groaning]
[Slapping]
[Big Soldier whispering]
Why?
[Woman speaking softly]
General, you've killed so many.
[Mumbling]
I'm not a General.
My family were killed by yours.
And I live to sing against my will.
I'm supposed to give you a good time
and serve you, General.
I didn't take pleasure in
drinking with you.
[Groaning]
Hey, no more fight.
Big Soldier:
Huh?
[Instrumental music playing]
Big Soldier:
Hey! Open the gate. I'm a soldier.
I have taken a Wei's General...
[Gate opens]
[Music stops]
[Instrumental music playing]
Man in wagon:
Stop.
Guard:
Whose this head?
Big Soldier:
A General of Wei.
[Crowd whispering]
That's him. I'm sure.
That's a head of Wei's General.
[Clears throat]
Reward him.
Man:
Just a sec.
Who killed him?
I did.
You? Really, huh?
He must be an AWOL.
Cut off a dead man's head.
Man in wagon:
Behead him.
That's not true!
[Yelling]
[Sword slashing]
[Water dripping]
Where's the horse?
[Breathing heavily]
[Yelling]
Wei's General: You gonna have to
kill me if you don't let me go.
Or I'll kill you in a heart beat.
Big Soldier:
Kill, kill, kill.
I grow farms.
I don't kill and I don't want to kill.
Big Brother:
You're getting me mad.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Big Soldier: Can't believe
I just got fooled by some woman.
I gave her food to eat,
and she gave me pill to swallow.
Wei's General: You deceived her first,
so it sounds fair.
Big Soldier:
She should have hit you instead.
Stupid helmet.
What did she say to you last night?
[Chuckling]
You small potato.
[Instrumental music playing]
Prince:
Who's stronger, me or him?
Wu:
He's a natural.
Prince: So I'm nowhere to compete with him?
Wu: You're too soft and he got the heart.
To become the King,
you must learn from him.
Wu: I'll take a unit and head for Liang's.
Why don't you go back...
Prince:
I won't go back until I see him.
Big Soldier:
You know what,
I've been looking forward to
life of peace and farms to grow
for 20 years.
[Instrumental music playing]
[Music stops]
Soldier: The wagon is not here.
The rope was cut off.
[Sighs]
Hey.
Hey. Hey?
[Instrumental music playing]
[Spitting]
Big Soldier: Stop playing dead.
I'm too smart for that.
[Music stops]
[Horse running]
We better stay away from the main road.
Let's take a detour.
Like this track.
Just don't lose the map.
Strong liquor. Must be Liang's.
[Big Soldier singing] One small track
leads the way to home.
Wei's General:
What now?
Like my dad said, step in shit.
Something good awaits me.
Wei's General:
It's an ambush.
Big Soldier:
Yeah, right.
Bum leader:
What's loaded on that wagon?
- Nothing particular.
- Rip him.
Rip him off!
[Instrumental music playing]
Big Soldier: Wait, wait...
Bum leader: Who are you?
[Music pauses]
A General.
Says you.
Beat him.
Wei's General: Hmm?
Beat him down.
[Instrumental music playing]
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Sorry.
Please... stop.
[Music stops]
Take whatever you want,
just let us go.
What possibly do you have,
besides this piece of junk?
Bum:
I want revenge!
Shut your mouth!
Bum leader:
Who's this guy?
He?
He... he's my son.
No! I'm not his son...
You little prick!
He's crazy. He thinks he's going to war.
I'm taking him back to grow farms.
Grow farms? There's nothing left
to grow because of the wars.
- Revenge!
- Get lost!
I'm in charge here.
I say we take the wagon.
Woman bum:
Unfaithful prick!
Bum leader: You got a death wish?
This helmet will get you killed.
Bum: How about this?
Bum leader: This? Will you ever learn?
Let's go!
[Shield drops]
Bang!
Bunch of fools.
They had no idea you're the MVP
"Most Valuable Package", huh.
[Instrumental music playing]
Your son?
I'm gonna treat you good!
So tie me up and
take me back to your farms!
[Music pauses]
[Groaning]
Hmm?
[Instrumental music playing]
[Roaring]
[Whispering]
Don't move. Don't breathe.
[Music pauses]
[Licking]
[Sniffing]
[Swallowing]
[Exhaling heavily]
[Bird trilling]
Ah!
[Groaning]
You were trying to
strangle me to death?
If it wasn't me...
[Groaning]
[Groaning in pain]
[Instrumental music playing]
Prick!
[Gasping]
It's not Dim Mak.
My dad was right.
I stepped in shit.
Pretty good.
Don't hurt us. I'm begging you!
Prince:
Hold it there.
I could kill him,
or I could spare him.
I just have the power.
Big Soldier: 1 acre for growing beans.
1 acre for melons.
How about 2 acres for beans,
2 acres for white grains?
No! 3 acres for beans.
[Gasping]
Tell me,
what I should do with
5 acres of farmland?
Wei's General:
I can offer you a thousand acres.
That's too much.
I couldn't handle that much.
White grain or bean,
what to grow, huh?
Wei's General:
I'd say rice. I love rice.
White grain and rice are
the same thing, fool!
You tired?
Feeling comfy, right?
Wei's General: Hmm-mmm.
[Yelling]
[Groaning]
Now I'm relieved.
5 acres, I'd be working
my butt off.
Right, I'll need some buffalo.
One male, one female.
The male will work in the farms.
The female will give milk.
I'm dying to know how you're gonna
drag me all the way to Liang's.
Wait, I can't milk a cow.
So I'll need a wife who can do that.
My eldest brother was a great warrior.
He fought till death.
My second brother was a honest person.
He died on the battlefield as well.
I'm the last seed of the family.
General, do you have any siblings?
- Wish I hadn't.
- Hmm?
[Instrumental music playing]
Why are you taking me here?
I couldn't find 'em.
The Mt. Phoenix is huge!
There's a lot of grounds to cover...
Was he being tied up?
Yes, his dad tied him up.
Said he's crazy or something...
They both appeared to be crazy...
Can I go back now?
[Bow shot]
[Moaning]
[No dialogues]
Revenge...
They want to take you back from me?
It's not gonna be easy.
I've been in battles for years,
never seen an
elegant arrow like this one.
I've seen this.
It's someone not friendly.
People like you just asking this
for yourself.
You know, they have you
and you'll die.
I have you and you'll live.
You are right.
I don't want to die in vain.
I'll come with you.
Turns out General is afraid of death.
If I die, I'll die with dignity.
This way, or that way?
Wei's General: Even if we make it to Liang's,
I could make a truce
with one condition: your execution.
Don't fool me.
Nobody fools me.
Except that woman who drugged you.
You have lots of women, huh?
Wei's General: Let's talk about you.
What type of women you like?
We have the lustful,
and the educated.
Big Soldier:
I like the honest ones.
But I'd probably take the educated.
She could teach me how to read.
You don't have a woman, right?
That woman, what did she say to you?
I'll tell you, if you can make it
back to Liang's.
Wu: You guys, go down there.
Back to where we came.
Keep a lookout.
Prince:
Who is that?
The Others.
They're bound to their own rules.
Go make your acquaintance.
Wu:
They don't speak our language.
They are passionate people.
Good fighters too.
Better stay away from 'em.
[Relaxing music playing]
Big Soldier:
Hurry up, you don't look that tired.
Wei's General:
Birds are gathering around,
but Phoenixes don't go with the flow.
What chicken and ducks
are you talking about?
If a phoenix lost its fur,
it'd make a chicken look elegant.
Wei's General:
Huh?
You're good at throwing rocks.
I used to hunt wild chicken
with rocks when I was a boy.
Hey.
You know why our troops camped
at the Mt. Phoenix?
How would I know?
Nevertheless, we had hidden there
for 2 days waiting for you.
That's what I thought, a set up.
If it wasn't an ambush,
my elite unit would have
crushed you majorly
and conquered Liang.
Stop the nonsense.
We are not that weak.
Anyway, an AWOL like you,
it's a shame to Liang.
[Music stops]
[Bird trilling]
Big Soldier:
Now, see how you elite you are.
General versus AWOL private?
Liang versus Wei. Fair and simple.
You want fair?
Keep your hands off my wound.
You have your wish.
[Instrumental music playing]
Wei's General:
Mmm?
You're dead.
Ha! You're dead too.
We're both dead.
Pervert.
[Groaning]
[Spring bouncing]
Huh?
Ouch!
War is over. Wei won.
Oww!
[Horses running]
[Horses whinnying]
Oww!
War is over. Wei won.
Wars have been around these years.
More people have joined the military.
He kills him, and he gets killed by him.
What's the attraction?
Liang wins. Liang wins.
You call this fair?
It's war.
No such thing as being fair.
[Horses whinnying]
We'll soon have meat to eat.
Now, have some appetizer.
[Relaxing music playing]
Lost your appetite?
Fine by me.
General, what do you eat when
there is no war to go to?
Meat and seafood.
Any good food you can
possibly think of.
Now I get it.
You people constantly go to war
just because of digestion problems.
Didn't you say you can't read, huh?
My dad taught me these 2 words.
They are the easiest to write.
These 2 words are not easy
to write at all.
Why don't you go to Wei with me.
I can offer you a high position.
I forgot to tell you one thing.
General alive, the rewards will be farmland
and money. No more serving in military.
There will be no more killing for me.
Just me and the farms.
When there's a war, there's a winner.
A winner of unification of China.
Only that will put an end to wars.
Only that will give you small potato
a normal life.
You know what,
we could have
lived our normal life,
if you had just left us alone!
You really don't want a bite?
Frankly, I'm a bit hungry.
Here comes our meat!
[Chuckling]
Wonderful meat.
Hmm.
Hey! I'll get you firewood.
[Sighs]
You have babies. Can't eat you.
My dad said...
[Big Soldier whispering]
Let's go. Let's go!
Someone is coming. Let's go!
Wei's General:
Why the panic? He's alone.
[Horse whinnying]
[Sword scrapes]
Big Soldier:
Huh?
It's our guy.
Hey, bro... Hmm?
Huh?
[Wei's General chuckling]
Huh!
Bastard!
[Gasping]
Man:
You. Go that way.
[Gasping]
Man:
A Liang-made sword.
[Exhales heavily]
[Chuckles]
[Arrow impacts]
On your Knees.
I'm a Liang's soldier.
I only knee to Liang's superiors.
[Groaning]
Liang's scout: Now what?
Wu: You are a scout from Liang's.
Yes.
Wu: What about you?
Big Soldier: I'm a scout too.
What are you scouting for?
I'm going to the battlefield
at Mt. Phoenix. No...
Big Soldier:
No survivors found.
Wu:
Why taking small track?
Liang's scout:
Your convoy is taking the main road...
Big Soldier:
Track is faster... pretty fast.
Liang's scout: I don't know him.
Big Soldier: What?
He's got lightheaded
after falling off from a horse.
Liang's scout:
No... Yes, I fell...
- Either way I don't know you.
Big Soldier: What?
You don't kill scouts.
That's agreement during wars.
Wu: Is this your sword?
Big Soldier: Yes.
Why you're carrying
a General type sword?
Big Soldier: I borrowed it...
Wu: You're not a scout.
Big Soldier: No, I'm not.
Wu: Where is the Wei's General?
I don't know.
Wu:
Don't you lie to me!
[Gasping]
I know, I know.
I've got your General.
You got balls.
Big Soldier: I got no balls!
Wu: Where is he?
- He's fled.
- You're no use to us then.
No. No. I-I hid him.
Take us to him.
- He really is gone.
- Are you messing with me?
Big Soldier:
Back off! You all back off!
Back off!
[Gasping]
Stay back!
- If I die, you won't get anything.
- What do you want?
Rewards.
- I can give you that.
- Shame on you.
[Loading crossbow]
Prince:
One of you is useless to me.
Oh...
[Bow shot]
Hmm?
Huh?
Liang's scout:
Now what?
[Instrumental music playing]
Wu:
Mount on! Get him!
[Breathing heavily]
[Sword Scrapes]
[Horse whinnying]
Wu:
Huh?
[Horse whinnying]
Defense!
[Sword scraping]
Oww! Oww!
Oww! Aww!
Big Soldier:
Pardon me. Aww!
Prince:
Wu.
Wu:
Stand down.
[Speaking foreign language]
Prince:
Let them through.
He's still alive, isn't he?
[Horse whinnying]
[Horse gasping]
[Sighs]
Big Soldier:
Pretty good.
Just a General, not a big deal.
Maybe I'd capture their King later.
Am I really a shame to Liang?
Am I?
Wei's General:
Come on.
[Wei's General yelling]
Come get me, huh?
I'm not dead yet.
Didn't expect that, right?
Because of your conspiracy,
1,000 brave men got killed.
They'll haunt you
for the rest of your life!
[Wei's General continues yelling]
And you.
A pity man.
A dishonorable AWOL.
One main road leads the way
to homecoming
empty-handed!
[Sighs]
[Sparrow trilling]
Huh?
Where you come from?
Where's your home, huh?
[Bird trilling]
Wei's General:
When I fulfill the conquest
I'll start building my big boat.
Yeah. I'm gonna sail off
on the night of the full moon
and travel the whole world.
Prince:
My father said,
paint a dragon on the big boat,
and it'll attract a phoenix.
Wu: Prince, the day you are crowned,
you'll get anything you want.
To become a King, me and him
we'd never be the same again.
Wu: Take some rest, Prince.
My dad said, a sparrow could
one day become a phoenix.
Pretty good.
Hey!
Big Soldier:
Why did you trick me?
And I've also hit you.
So kill me, General.
I'm not a General.
I'm a private.
What's the difference?
You just kill.
Big Soldier:
Hey, you're lost, right?
You really think that when you get to
Shen Shu, everything will be all right?
I'm a small potato.
Wait, um...
this map I have here,
will get you to Shen Shu.
You'll get a lot of grounds to cover.
Take this horse with you.
I give this back to you.
You're hungry, huh? Me too.
Need to find something to eat.
[Big Soldier singing] At the bottom
of the mountain. Soils are rich.
5 acres of farmland
5 acres of fine land
What to grow?
Student #1: You're wrong.
Student #2: You're wrong.
Teacher:
Stop arguing.
If you want to be a successful diplomat,
you still need one more thing.
Both student:
What's that?
Patience.
Wei's General:
Mister,
please tell me which way is Wei.
Student #1: That way.
Student #2: No, that way.
Wei has geographical advantages,
with Liang acting like a front shield,
and Chu like a shield on the back.
You can run, but you can't hide.
[Horse whinnying]
Man: Yeah!
[Crowd cheering]
Woman:
There.
This is your new home now.
I'm going home too.
You live a good life.
Pretty good.
[Breathing heavily]
Man:
Ah!
[Gasping]
[Man screaming]
[Weapong swinging]
[Yelling]
[Weapon swinging]
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Man:
Whoo!
[Horse whinnying]
Man:
Whoo-hoo!
[Cow mooing]
[Chuckling]
[Cheering]
[Goats bleating]
[Dog barking]
[Groaning]
[Man yelling]
[Cheering]
[Chuckling]
[Big Soldier singing]
One main road
leads to homecoming
My home is right at
the foot of Mt. Liang
Soils are rich there...
[Cow mooing]
[Goats bleating]
Pretty good.
[Speaking in foreign language]
Man:
Easy, easy.
I should have killed you in that inn.
Wei's General: I should have let you
be the black bear's lunch.
Don't get too tight, you understand me?
Teacher:
They're taking us to a tomb.
Student:
Tomb?
Teacher: Get us buried in mass grave.
Student: Buried?
[Speaking foreign language]
Whoa!
Big Soldier:
How far is Liang from here?
Villager:
1 day if you take the river.
What village you come from?
Three Legs Cave.
Wei's General:
Looks like your plan isn't going well.
We'll see. You're still my captive.
Wei's General:
Hey, I'm not your captive!
I'm his captive!
[Speaking foreign language]
Trade him with a horse.
Ah!
Man:
Aah!
[Sword slashing]
Man: Ah!
Guard:
Prince, look out!
Line up.
Defense!
[Speaking foreign language]
- How to take this thing off?
- I'm about to ask you the same question.
[Speaking foreign language]
Aah!
Wu!
I have an idea.
Just say it.
Remember, we're in the same boat.
Yes, like my dad said,
Whether it's a an eagle or a chicken,
they are just meat once placed in a hotpot.
Figured.
[Horse whinnying]
[Whip smashing]
Need help.
Not a perfect plan...
Aah!
[Bamboo cracking]
but still a good idea.
[Swords scraping]
Come on.
Man:
Help me, help me...
Wei's General: Wu.
Wu: Yes.
- You finally fight me with a real sword.
- Sorry, you're no longer my master now.
[Swords scraping]
What a pity,
you're my best student ever.
[Cow mooing]
Big Soldier: Aah!
Wu: Aah!
[Cow mooling]
Aw!
Get on it.
Buffalo, faster.
[Goats bleating]
[Metal scraping]
Huh?
[Goats bleating]
Prince, make your way out.
[Man crying in distance]
[Man crying]
[Man continues crying]
Whoa!
[Gasping]
Aah!
- This way.
- That way.
Big Soldier: Hey, you know what,
I didn't want to save you.
This buffalo just lost his temper.
Was this buffalo too power
or the wall was too weak?
Not matter what, thank you.
Pretty good. Pretty good.
What's with your waist belt?
My secret.
Before we go separate ways,
I'll have a secret to tell.
You want to know why those people
wanted to capture me?
No, I don't want to know.
People like you are so complicated.
Wei's General: Since the day we met,
everything has become complicated.
Small potato!
You're still my POW.
Can't let you walk out on me!
- You've delayed my business.
- You're my business.
Huh?
Wei's General
I know, I'm your farmland.
Big Soldier:
Yes, 5 acres of it.
Wei's General:
And the reward money.
Big Soldier:
Yes, a pocketful of it.
[Cow mooing]
Wei's General: Stop!
- Why?
- I'm ordering you!
- You can't trick me!
Thanks for the warning...
[Both]
Aw, aw, aw...
[Both yelling]
Ah!
[Wei's General yelling]
Big Soldier: huh?
Big Soldier:
This can't hold any longer.
Get off of my back.
Wei's General:
Not a chance.
- I'll grab you after you let go of me.
Wei's General: You think I'd buy that?
Let's find out.
[Screaming]
[Splashing]
Wu.
Prince.
Prince:
Why?
He's still alive. Is that fate?
Prince, let's head back to Wei.
Prince:
No! You don't how I feel.
[Groaning]
[Groaning continues]
Wei's General:
You really are some piece of work.
Go ahead. Tie me up.
Just take a look around.
Take a look around at this hell hole!
Big Soldier:
Where are we?
[Groaning]
Wei's General: Save your breath.
We're gonna die down here.
[Singing in distance]
One main road
leads to homecoming
[Big Soldier singing]
My home is right at
the foot of Mt. Liang
Soils are rich there
Wei's General:
You're loosing it.
Pretty good. My dad said,
as long as you still alive,
it's pretty good.
Must I become the King?
You'll be a good King.
It's a good thing for Wei.
Are you trying to convince me
to kill him without a blink of an eye?
Wu: We've gone this far,
this is the only way out.
Okay, how can he die
with dignity?
Wei's General:
What are you thinking?
Rapeseed flower.
I'm thinking about growing rapeseed.
Why?
Why what?
Why am I being stuck
in a place like this?
I should be the one who brings
all the Dukes to their knees.
And then have a huge tomb
made for me.
Have my own treasure
buried with me.
Now they can't even
find my corpse.
Yeah, the rest of reward money
would go to my new pharmacy store.
To be honest, your drugs worked.
I'm appointing you as
The Minister for Health.
[Chuckling]
You know what, if it wasn't the wars,
we could have been buddies.
Perhaps.
If you make it out alive,
will you promise me one thing?
Shoot.
Never invade my nation, Liang.
[Sighs]
I give you 10 years of truce.
[Chuckling]
Sounds tricky.
You have an agreement.
And you need to promise me one thing.
Shoot.
If you ever make it out alive,
you must tell them that
I died fighting.
I died fighting for my people.
I've done nothing disgraceful
to Wei.
We all bite the dust,
but not our flag.
Don't lie to me,
you small potato.
Being a small potato...
sounds pretty good.
[Sighs]
[Crowd cheering in distance]
[Crowd chuckling in distance]
[Sighs]
Ha!
[Pulling bow string]
[Gasping]
[Sparrow trilling]
[Exhales heavily]
Hey! Hey!
Ow!
Wake up.
[Splashing]
[Breathing heavily]
[Cheerful music playing]
[Gasping]
Big Solider:
Dad, I'm alive!
Thanks Heaven!
You know what, this is
Three Legs Cave.
There is a fisherman's village nearby.
I'll go get a boat.
It'll take half a day to get there.
To where?
To Liang, where else could it be?
Don't think about running away.
You can't survive an hour without me.
Big Soldier:
Quick, quick!
Go hide!
Hide from what?
Just hide.
[Horse whinnying]
Hold me up.
Wei's General:
Little brother.
Big Soldier:
Little brother?
He's your brother?
You've been chasing me for days.
Don't you get tired?
Prince.
Big Soldier:
Prince?
Why the mourning bandana?
It's for our father.
Wei's General: He was very sick
when I left for battles. It's you.
It's fate. You just cared about
waging wars to please the old man.
If I hadn't upset him by making
peace arrangement with Liang,
I would have been the Prince.
You set the ambush to make sure
I'd get killed.
Something going on between you two
and we Liang paid with 2,000 lives.
You're not authorized to talk to me.
- Leave him out of this.
- But he's the enemy.
He wants me to live,
but you wants me to die.
Come on. Use that crossbow I gave you
and claim the throne of Wei.
[Sighs]
Wu:
You're still too soft-hearted.
Your sword.
Wu:
If you don't kill him, he will kill you.
Only one of you will become the King.
Um, that's doesn't make any sense,
why one of you brothers must die?
- It's none of your business.
- You guys are complicating things.
- I said "it's none of your business!"
- It's all because of that nosy baldhead.
I'm done talking.
[Horses whinnying]
[Instrumental music playing]
[Speaking foreign language]
He really looks upset.
Maybe we should go now.
I'm really messed up big time.
You do what you got to do, Master.
[Arrow cracks]
Aah!
[Speaking foreign language]
Hey, can we go now, eh?
[Sword slashes]
[Pounding]
[Sword scrapes]
Aah!
Huh?
[Sighs]
General!
Behind you!
[Chuckling]
It's none of my business.
[Moaning]
What a pity.
[Gasping]
Whoa!
[Groaning]
[Weapon swinging]
Ouch!
Not even one small rock?
[Gasping]
Ow!
Don't get any closer,
or you'd get blind.
Big brother!
[Screaming]
[Yelling in anger]
[Yelling in distance]
Whoa!
[Gasping]
Stop!
[Music stops]
[Gasping]
I'm the one you should kill.
Me and my brother,
only one will walk out here alive.
You don't understand
what I'm saying, do you? huh?
How about this, huh? Ah!
This is what I got to do.
Little brother!
Big brother,
am I dying with dignity?
Sorry about our big boat.
We can never build it together.
[Breathing heavily]
Do me a favor.
Help me bury him.
We must carry on, General.
We got half day.
Sorry, I mean Prince.
Your Wei's liquor is not strong enough.
I know what you're thinking.
I also know what you're thinking.
- Pretty good.
- We're still alive.
You two reminded me
of my own brothers.
Wei's Prince:
They were good soldiers.
Big Soldier: In fact,
I wanted to be a good soldier.
The first time we enlisted,
we 3 brothers got no choice.
The first tour lasted for 3 years.
When we came back,
our village had been burnt to ground.
We became homeless.
Before my dad died, he told us
[Slow music playing]
we had served our country.
But when the wars will end?
And he said, "kids, listen,
one of you 3 brothers must live,
in order to raise kids for our family."
[Sobbing]
Now I'm the only one left.
Having you is my biggest luck ever.
[Sobbing continues]
I can't say the same thing about my luck.
[Woman singing in distance]
[Singing continues]
Wei's Prince:
Don't ask.
What she said to me the other night:
"kama".
[Sighs]
What a little potato.
[Singing continues]
Shen Shu, Mt. Phoenix.
"Peace"
"Mt. Liang"
You know what,
after this turn is Liang's soil.
My brother wanted to befriend
Liang, maybe he's right.
If Liang's Duke spare my life, may be we could
work something out for allying each other.
Maybe, maybe.
Maybe it's too late.
Maybe.
[Breathing heavily]
Nothing feels like home!
That's your secret belt...
I was wrong about you.
Never thought you could make
this journey for both of us.
Now, am I your captive or enemy?
[Sword scrapes]
Neither. Just go.
Hurry. Before I change my mind.
Why?
You 2 brothers...
one must live.
[Grunting]
Can I count on your word?
What you mean?
10 years of truce!
Absolutely!
You have my word!
Don't forget...
that medal you took from me,
it's worth a fortunate.
It can get your farmland and money.
I found it.
[Sighs]
I might not live long enough...
Now I'm empty-handed.
Pretty good.
Boy:
Run.
Run away now.
[Soldiers cheering]
[Cheering continues]
[Horse whinnying]
Officer:
Ask him to surrender.
Liang has been destroyed.
Knee down and surrender.
Liang is gone?
How could that possible?
Officer: Liang refused to surrender.
So we, from Qin, destroyed it.
- Your units have been completely eliminated.
Qin's soldier: On your knee. Last chance.
Big Soldier:
All units wiped out?
No more Liang.
"Qin"
This is not happening.
[Pulling bow string]
[No dialogues]
[Bow shot]
[Grunts]
[Qin's soldiers chuckling]
Liang is history.
I really got nothing left now.
Qin's officer:
Put the flag down.
[Prince singing]
One main road
Qin's officer:
Your units have been wiped out.
Big Soldier:
That's not entirely true.
Qin's officer:
Drop your sword.
I'm still standing!
Give your best shot!
[Singing]
My home is right at
the foot of Mt. Liang
Soils are rich there
5 acres of farms
5 acres of farm
Sorry dad,
guess I'm not gonna raise
any kids now.
[Singing]
One big river
leads to my home
My wife, my kids
and my big house
Chickens and ducks are fat
Cattle is strong
Grow some bean
white grain
and rapeseed flower
[Spring bouncing]
[Sparrow trilling]
I ain't a shame to Liang, am I?
"Liang"
SDH/translation: Arigon
[Man narrating]
Qin conquered Liang.
The General has returned to Wei
and claimed the throne.
Since then he gave up waging wars.
When facing the invasion of Qin,
Wei's Duke complied to surrender.
Soldiers and civilians
were left to life in peace.
During the last few years of
the Warring States Period,
one China was nearly shaped.
Qin united all states of China
in 221 B.C.
[Music playing]
You're hungry, huh?
Ow! Ow! You bite me!
We're gonna hit the rock.
Back up the boat.
- [Speaking Mandarin]...be your "hotpot"
- "Hot pot" is for cooking meals.
- It reads "captive!"
- "Captive!"
You're hitting me for real, huh?
[Chuckling]
You're doing for real?
I've haven't finished my line!
[Chuckling]
Jackie: I don't know what I'm saying.
- You're messing with me?
I'm Wei's Pince...
I've speaken the wrong country...
You could kill someone with this bun.
This nose is too big.
[Man over PA] Jackie,
you're already dead. Stop moving.