The Wall street journal
is better than ever
Did you bring the milk ?
This concludes our service.
Go now in the peace
of the Lord.
So long, suckers!
Move it, move it,
move it!
Do you want to be second
out of the parking lot?
Do you?
Leave her!
We left her last week,
and she didn't make
it home for dinner!
You'll never catch me, Lord!
Oh, man, that church
service was so boring.
I did a whole book
of Find-A-Words.
Dad, all you circled
were the "I"s and "A"s.
Those are words.
Well, where should
we go for brunch?
Griddler on the Roof?
Thank God
It's Fried Eggs?
Luftwaffle's?
Bodacious Frittatas?
Buffet the Hunger Slayer?
I want to say one.
Be my guest.
Denny's.
Every place has
such a long line.
Don't worry.
We'll just go home.
Your mother can cook.
I just want a simple salad
with pine nuts,
haricots verts,
seasonal heirloom tomatoes...
Forget it!
One day a week, I should be able
to put on nice clothes and
have someone bring food to me.
There's a place...
with no line!
Woo-hoo!
Bart, that's not a restaurant,
it's somebody's house.
Lisa's right, son.
Your mom is way too classy
a lady to crash a private...
I'm not cooking!
And you can cut
your own meat!
Everyone just act cool.
If anyone asks, tell
them we're plumbers,
and then start plumbing
until they go away.
Hi...
you!
Dude! You don't think,
you know me, but you do!
Oh Homer, you've got to try
this roast beef au jus.
Mmm! Au jus!
Not quite gravy,
not quite blood.
Look at the crowd
around that table!
It must be a make-
your-own sundae bar!
Watch it.
Oh, I can't wait to
taste that hot fudge,
and caramel and crushed nuts
all slathered over a delicious...
elderly corpse?!
We crashed a funeral!
Oh, my God!
Quick, everyone,
put on their long faces.
Longer!
We should get out of here.
Come on!
Where's Bart?
Mahogany.
Great movie,
great casket.
I miss my Pop-pop.
I miss him, too.
What's your name?
Donny.
You're Donny?
Pop-pop said that
after he died,
you should give me
ten bucks a week.
Starting now.
Okay.
Um, listen,
I'm out of town next week, so...
Come on, we're leaving!
Ooh. After one more mini-quiche.
Excuse me.
My brother twisted his ankle
setting up the chairs.
Will the tragedies that stalk
this family never cease?
Would you like to
be a pallbearer?
Of course.
I thought she said polar bear.
Please, sir, a little
respect for the dead.
Oh, yes, of course.
Oh, my back!
It hurts,
and not in a good way.
Well, time to move on with our lives.
Oh, stop it!
Help me !
I'm down here.
Homer, you have a mild back sprain.
And you also ingested
a dangerous quantity of grave dirt.
Well, you're always telling me
I should eat more dirt.
Not dirt. Vegetables!
Which grow in what?
Oh! Look, I just need to make sure
your vertebrae are properly aligned.
This should take only a minute,
and cost about a thousand dollars.
D'oh!
That doesn't sound like Homer's
usual annoyed grunt.
D'oh!
D'oh.
Fascinating.
When Homer's on his back,
his stomach lodges perfectly
under his diaphragm,
giving him a powerful singing voice.
Is that a real thing?
It is!
Tenor Andrea Bocelli
recorded an entire song on his back.
You know, Homer,
your singing could help alleviate patient suffering,
and save us a fortune in Demerol.
My pleasure.
If ever I would leave you
It wouldn't be in summer
Seeing you in summer
I never would go
Your hair streaked with sunlight
Your lips red as flame
Your face with a luster
That puts gold to shame!
But if I ever leave you
It shouldn't be in autumn
How I'd leave in autumn
I never will know
I've seen how you sparkle
When fall nips the air
I know you in autumn
And I must be there.
Ah, nothing lifts my spirits like shopping.
Let's see, I'll take his liver,
a case of Adam's apples,
that motorcycle man's moustache.
Oh, the money you've
contributed to anti-helmet
laws has really paid off, sir.
Well, young people are my future.
And could I leave you
Running merrily through the snow...
That beautiful voice!
It's making my heart race!
- Knowing how in spring...
- It's coming from down the hall.
To the Betty and Herbert Weinstein Pavilion!
Oh, no! Not in springtime
Summer, winter or fall
No, never could I leave you...
At... all!
Excellent, excellent!
The Springfield Opera House,
of which I am founder, artistic director,
and standing ovation starter,
is producing La Bohème.
I want you to sing the lead.
But I can only sing lying on my back.
Uh, we'll cover it with a rewrite.
Places, everyone!
Oh, oh, I just have one question:
what is this movie about?
For the last time, it's not a movie!
Excuse me, "film."
It's an opera
and you are in it!
Good luck.
Rodolfo, perché lete che vi trovate gio?
Ho danneggiato il mio piede.
Nei cieli bigi
Guardo fumar dai mille comignoli parigi.
- Homer's fantastic!
- Yeah.
But these seats are terrible.
Mimi! Mimi!
Bravo! Bravo!
Bravo! Belisimo !
Encore! Encore!
My boy, you are a star.
Woo-hoo!
An opera star!
Dad, you were great!
And you contributed to our culture!
Well, I didn't mean to.
No, no. It's a good thing.
Oh, good.
This makes up for me showing up drunk
to the father-daughter dance.
The dance isn't till next week.
Sorry, Lisa.
Can't change the future.
And the home
Of the...
Bra-aave !
We're free !
Figaro, Figaro, la, la, la
Nice set, Homer.
That was a hot one.
Wow, praise
from Placido Domingo.
Just call me P-Dingo.
Eh, I'll think about it.
You know, Homer,
there's one thing about opera
that has always bugged me:
everyone sings instead of talking.
But you mademe believe
I was in a magical world
where singing is talking.
Thanks !
You know, of the three tenors,
you're my second favorite !
No wait, I forgot about
that other guy.
Sorry, you're third.
Wait, Homer, before you go,
there is a new note
I've been working on.
Tell me what you think...
what if you gave it a little
more of this flavor...
Like this ?
Keep reaching for the stars, kid.
Happy anniversary, sweetie.
You know, it might be
a little more romantic
without your entourage.
But I need my childhood friends
to help me keep it real.
Would you have me keep it fake ?
Homer, can't weplease be alone ?
It's our anniversary.
We'll move to another table.
Yoko.
See ?
Isn't it nicer,
with just you and...
Excuse us.
Would you mind signing
autographs for my mother and me ?
Oh, my pleasure.
To the hottest girls in the room.
What is he saying ?
I said you look hot !
Ay Chihuahua !
- Ay chi-what ?
- Hua-hua !
I want you to stop
flirting with women.
No problem.
Sir, may I say I thoroughly
enjoyed your performance.
May I say
I'm enjoying the calm waters
of your deep, blue eyes ?
Oh, well...
What ?
That's how guys talk.
You are out of control !
The late nights, the eating !
You've actually
outgrown your cape !
Oh, Homie...
I miss our alone time.
I miss you.
Need some help, H ?
Want us to take Marge shopping ?
You guys go on,
we're gonna walk home.
Great call, H,
walking's the best.
I really want to
hook up with Homer.
Now we both know
that ain't gonna happen,
but, uh, I'm right here.
Marge, when I'm on stage,
I can only sing those love songs
by picturing your beautiful face.
So in a way, my groupies
are really our groupies.
Aw, you're sweet.
Oh, my God, it's him !
Use your opera glasses, Dorothy.
Switching to thermal imaging.
Target acquired.
Oh, we're trapped.
Your fans will rip us to pieces.
Not me, they love me.
Get on.
Sir, thank youfor saving us.
Do you want
to come in for coffee ?
That's right, I'm a woman.
A lady motorcycle driver ?!
What is this, The Twilight Zone ?
It's a shame a few out of control fans
can make the rest of us look bad.
I couldn't agree more, Julia.
Listen, I love opera,
but I hate the way these people
treat your husband.
Why don't you make me president
of Homer's fan club
and I'll keep the
crazies in check.
That's a great idea.
To celebrate, I'll go whip us up
some Chex Mix pie.
So did you see the show tonight ?
Remember the part
where I forgot the words
and I just sang
"Uh-oh Spaghetti-os" ?
I'm hoping they send me a case.
Now listen, Homer.
You can have meany
time you want me.
Marge !
But if you say
one word to your wife,
I'll tell her you attacked me.
What is it, sweetie ?
Um... everyone's
wearing clothes in here.
That's nice.
Mr. Simpson will send you a photo if
you send him a self-addressed envelope.
Mr. Simpson can not sing
at your daughter's birthday,
but he will come for cake.
Dedicate your shopping center ?
What's the anchor store ?
I don't think so.
She's perfect !
For the first time since you became
an opera star I can finally relax.
Well, uh, I'm not sure
she's working out.
That's it !
Let me make
something very clear:
my heart belongs to Marge
and you can never, ever have it.
This opera's over
when the fat man sings.
All right, Homer.
I understand perfectly.
You shall never be mine.
That's good.
You've calmly accepted
that you will never have the
only man you could ever love.
Now, I think it would
be best if you left.
- Julia, wait !
- Yes ?
Before you go,
could you hire your
own replacement ?
But make sure she's
not crazy like you.
Die, you stupid cobra !
Die ! Die !
Dad, I think someone's
trying to kill you.
Who could it be ?
A disgruntled former employee ?
Whoever it is, the cobra
is their symbol.
D'oh, d'oh, d'oh,
d'oh, d'oh, d'oh, d'oh
Woo, woo, woo,
woo, woo, woo-hoo
Stu, stu, stu,stu-pid Flanders.
Why the crescendo,
my dear, old friend-o ?
Get lost you waste
of a moustache.
Okily-dokily.
Chief, I think we should
cancel the performance.
No can do, Marge.
My first duty is to the
season-ticket holders.
But don't worry, I've got the entire
opera house on a complete lockdown.
I got sharp shooters on the gares,
inflatable Homer decoys in the seats,
and to take out
the biggest threat of all,
we're pre-crashing
the chandelier.
Se il mio nome saper voi bramate
Dal mio labbro il mio nome...
I'm so tense.
I can't enjoy Count Almaviva serenading
the intended bride of Dr. Bartalo.
I just can't.
I don't see anything suspicious.
Except someone is loudlyun
wrapping their candy.
It ain't candy, it's a lamb chop
wrapped in foil.
Hey, Mom, do all
conductors carry
poisoned blow-darts
in their pocket ?
Well, Arthur Fiedler used to,
but I'd better take a look.
Chief Wiggums !
The maestro is the killer !
All right, I'm going in.
Allegro ! Allegro !
I mean, andante. Andante !
Ah, yeah.
Snipers, take the shot.
Okay, that's a wrap, people !
Luckily, the sniper bullets
stopped her heart
from pumping the poison
through her body long enough
for the chandelier
to squish it all out of her.
With any luck, she'll be up
and stalking within a week.
I'm sorry you got hurt,
but you learned
an important lesson.
No one comes between
me and my Homie.
I'll get you for this, Marge,
if it's the last thing I do.
And I scheduled the cable guy to come
on Wednesday between 10:00 and 2:00.
Oh, but Wednesday's
not good for me.
I know, Marge. I know.
Let's go, Hagliacci,
or should I say,
Madame Butterface ?
What ? What ?
I had two.
Well, that's it.
I'm retiring from the opera.
It's just too popular.
And I know something much more
fun I can do on my back.
Transcript : Raceman
Traduction : Skualler, Rassman
Singing opera made me
good at painting.
- Is that a real thing ?
- No.
Synchro : Job22, Daffy
www.forom.com