D'oh!
What the...!
Hmm?
Ew, cheap PVC smell.
Oh, no.
I'm an action figure!
And I hate action.
Hiddiley-ho,
articulated neighborino.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
Why, it's practically
mint on card.
Shut up, Flanders!
This reality ain't all bad.
Pastry power, activate.
Whoa!
Beep, beep, beep.
Homer, give me a yank.
I'm lonely.
Typical.
Homer, this isn't
the way to the mall.
The mall?
I thought you said Badass City!
Tokyo drift.
♪ The Simpsons 24x20 ♪
Fabulous Faker Boy
Original Air Date on May 12, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
I'm fatality.
All right, Dad!
Hey, put the
chicken one back on.
Urgent message
from Nelson Muntz.
Go on.
Haw. Haw.
Well, I am going to write
a note back to Mr. Muntz.
Sorry about that.
So, Mrs. Simpson,
the reason you're here...
Let me guess.
You need a field trip mom.
A library volunteer?
Someone to Purell the CPR dummy?
Resusci-Kate is just fine,
thank you.
We're here to talk about Bart.
What did he do now?
Oh, today, I'm not here to talk
about what he did.
I'm here to talk
about the future.
What did he do in the future?
I'm not sure
what he's planning,
although there is a lot
of Internet chatter.
I want to change
his character:
less Dennis the Menace,
more Casper the Ghost,
if he were still alive.
What if Bart took music lessons?
Music classes could channel
his destructive impulses
into artistic expression.
I myself have been taking
flamenco lessons.
Got it, music lessons.
Mother!
Right. Right.
Inside.
Oh, stupid clog.
My head hairs!
I'm bald!
Get... get...
get in there.
D'oh!
Aw, damn it!
Welcome back...
to America's Most Tattooed Baby.
Now, if the Lindblads can fit
just one more tattoo
on baby Jennifer--
and she's getting pretty full,
I can tell you that--
they win the grand prize
of $100.
So what'll it be?
Walk away! Walk away!
TV's gotten so lousy.
Did you ever wonder
if hippopotamuses
think that rhinos
are unicorns?
TV's not so bad.
Sweetie...
did you ever think
of doing something
a little more creative
with your time?
If you're worried about
your Mother's Day present,
it's in the works.
I was thinking something
more artistic.
Something musical.
You could take advantage
of a fantastic musician
living right here.
That's the kind of riff
you can aim for
after years of practice.
We start off with the
fun stuff: music theory.
Don't worry,
music theory's
just a fancy word
for music math.
My dear boy,
you undoubtedly think
of the slide whistle
as merely a whistle
that slides.
Let me disabuse you
of that misperception.
Pass.
Do you have any idea
how difficult...
Bye, now.
Behold!
From the pages of Dune
and Dune Messiah,
Gurney Halleck's beloved zither:
the baliset.
Pass.
When I die,
you will carry on the tradition
of... the Frink-e-min.
Pass.
Ah, Mr. Homer.
I see you are wearing
the bald man's beret.
Is it that obvious?
Oh, yes.
The only thing that screams
"I am hiding hairlessness" more
is a goatee.
I'm as smooth as jazz.
Oh... my wife has never seen
my head naked.
Maybe I should wear
a cowboy hat.
A cowboy hat means
"I'm ashamed of my small penis."
Don't even ask me
what this means!
Yee-haw!
I'm a-compensatin'!
New student.
Sit at piano.
My daughter teach you.
You, mother!
Come to kitchen and see
picture of my dead wife.
That's okay. I...
No, no, no, no.
She is not dead in picture.
Uh... she is dying.
Let's go, Bart.
So, you want lesson?
Yes. I want lesson.
I accept your whip.
A girl who likes candy?
Wow.
So, how much are lessons?
I give you something you want...
you give me something I want.
I'm sorry,
did my voice go all evil?
It is common
with Russian accent.
You'd better be asking
for something PC:
pie or cake.
Here's my offer:
my daughter give lessons,
you teach me to drive car.
There might be
some nagging involved.
Deal!
Now we toast with vodka.
Ah.
Now we drive!
Huh?
Homer, I recommend
getting drunk
on my most
expensive beer:
Duff Platinum.
Hey, what the...?
But I used the best label paste.
Those two hairs were what
was left of my youth, Moe.
Hey, come on, there's
sexy bald, like, um...
Babar, king of the elephants.
I read his books as a kid.
He married his cousin, Celeste.
That was my takeaway.
Those royal elephants have
trainers to keep them in shape.
Average schmoe like me,
forget it.
Well, let me see
how bald you are.
Whoa... whoa!
Dear Lord.
Here. Oh.
You need this more than I do.
Just... just what exactly
is this good for?
It's nice when something
you plan in your head
for so long
comes to fruition.
Where you going, Bart?
Piano lesson.
Ooh, piano lesson.
We put two of
those guys up there
just for using
a big word.
"Caché" is not a big word.
Clickety clack!
Wait, wait.
I'm not learning anything.
I'm just going
'cause the teacher's pretty.
Okay.
But you'd better steal bananas
for all of us.
I will!
Let me go.
I have a swim lesson
with a gorgeous lifeguard.
What gender?
You're not allowed to ask.
Okay.
Check your mirrors.
Hands at 10:00 and 2:00.
Slowly back out
of the driveway.
Aah!
Mmm...
Daddy said I was
a accident.
Okay, let's try again.
That is so beautiful.
Did you write it?
These are scales.
Now, memorize:
Every good Boris deserves farm.
Let me try.
Every good booger
deserves flicking.
Your tongue is nimble,
unlike sausage fingers.
Sausage fingers!
Do what I do.
♪ Druguyu nevestu
♪ Drugoi iyunya
♪ Drugoi solnechni
♪ Medovyi mesyats...
♪ Yeshche odim sezon
♪ Yeshche odna prichina
♪ Dlya vupi makin'...
Ah...
♪ Dlya makin'...
♪ Whoopee...
Scales!
Lesson over.
Aah!
What are you doing?
I want to go backwards.
Like Russian economy,
under Putin.
Stop making Putin jokes.
You sound like police...
under Putin.
Ugh. Speaking of police...
I'm sorry, Officer.
I believe my license is, uh...
...somewhere in these pairs
of easy-fit blue jeans.
Eh? Eh?
That's not the way
American police do things.
Finally.
Someone who knows
what a traffic stop
is really all about.
Uh, Chief, don't you think
those jeans are a little tight?
We're all not high-waisted
like you, Lou, okay?
I'm just gonna lie down
in the backseat here.
Okay.
All right, the blue knight
is ready for action!
What's wrong?
Every note you play
sounds like dying animal
writhing on keys.
Awesome!
I just want to get more students
and help my father
with his dream.
Buying a limo.
He could tell big shots
in the back that,
no, they cannot smoke.
Seriously,
I'm gonna make you proud.
I have hidden talents.
Oh, Bort, if only you make
such a miracle happen...
I would love your
hands forever.
Wait a minute.
You can't hear.
I am so proud.
I would've been happy
if Bart was just a piano mover.
Thank you.
I owe it all to Zhenya.
Can you teach my boys?
But no tickling
the ivories.
You treat them
with respect.
Can you teach my monkey?
Then I can deal
with the Musician's Union
instead of the Humane Society.
Much easier to muscle.
Zhenya, I couldn't have
done it without you.
And you.
Bart!
Bart, I've never been
so proud of you.
Never, never, never!
And now I'll always be
at home in a saloon.
Something smells fishy.
Yar, that would be me.
But I agree.
There's something
funny here.
Is it me?
No!
Oh...
Hey, your baseball cap's one
plastic bump tighter than usual.
What gives?
Okay, guys, here's the deal.
I've gone bald.
Then again,
who cares?
Yeah, you already
landed a hot wife.
That's the only reason
men evolved hair.
What are you talking about?
You lured Marge in
with your hair.
You trapped her
with marriage.
You skinned and field-gutted
her by having kids.
Now she's mounted on
your wall for good,
with fake glass eyes
and a rubber tongue.
The way you put it,
it sounds so perfect,
but it's not.
You sound seriously depressed.
Why don't we talk
about it over at Moe's?
It's not even noon.
Yeah, I've got
a watch, egghead.
I couldn't help overhearing
your predicament.
Mainly because
my hearing is so great.
Who are you?
The answer to your prayers.
Are you my guardian angel?
If so, can you turn a
pumpkin into a chariot?
Even a used Camry would be okay.
No, just a regular
hairless Joe like you.
Been bald since I was 23.
With the money I've saved,
I bought a yacht.
Whoa...
You're cool with it?
I haven't even told my wife.
You wait for
the right moment,
you show her
that glorious dome,
and then you rest it sweetly
on her bosom
and let the kisses
flow like rain.
Wow, is that what
your wife did?
No wife.
I just slept with
thousands of bald women.
Caught your recital, Bart.
Lisa, isn't it great
to have a musical genius
in the family?
Helen Lovejoy,
you always have to stir the pot.
Unlike you, when you make
your lumpy clam chowder.
I guess Bart must be
a musical genius,
because frauds are
always found out.
Always.
My work is done.
Now to reward myself
with a case of wine.
Hi, Zhenya.
I'm here for my lesson.
Good to see you, my love.
Sit on porch.
Are there other
people in here?
Because of your performance,
I win many new students.
♪
me on. I got to learn my mom's
stripper music by midnight.
But if I got you
all these students,
shouldn't you be grateful?
Oh, of course I'm grateful.
Here is cushion for porch chair.
Go to "bata boom."
Mopped myself into a corner.
Oh...
Mom,
you'd still be proud of me
if I couldn't
play the piano, right?
Of course.
But very, very, very angry
at all the time I wasted.
Gulp? Was that a gulp?
Are you getting
a sore throat?
Let me give you
some castor oil.
Hmm...
You'll need your voice
to say, "Thanks, Mom,"
after your next recital.
My wha...?
I signed you up for
the 10-And-Below Talent Show
next week. Huh?
You know, I'm almost 11.
It's not really fair.
Bart, when you were
on that stage,
it felt like you were
pouring those notes
right into my heart.
Hey, one of those notes
could go to your brain
and kill you.
Are you sure you want
to take that chance?
A proud mother
always does.
First of all,
you're over ten years old.
Second, you're clearly
Justin Bieber.
That's another 25 bucks
we'll never see.
Gosh!
♪ Who can make the sun rise?
Why won't anybody tell me?
Oh...
I'm sorry.
I was faking it.
I lied so I could see Zhenya.
Zhenya. Oh, Zhenya.
Everyone knows Zhenya.
But there's really only one girl
whose opinion matters to me.
My mom.
I'd like to go home now.
And to think you'd do this
on Mother's Day.
Is it too late to make you
breakfast in bed?
Uh, Mom?
I'm sorry I pretended
to be good at piano.
And I'm really ashamed
that I lied.
Excuse me.
Mrs. Marge, I took
my driver's test.
Did you pass?
More or less.
If I eat an orange wedge,
the whole thing's gonna blow.
Well, I'm glad your side
of the deal worked out.
What are you talking about?
Your boy is genius!
No, he cheated.
Marge, in Russia,
everyone succeeds by cheating.
Even Russian dressing
is just Thousand Island.
But your son is a good boy.
He cheated for love,
and he cheated for you.
Thank you!
All right.
A chance to make a new friend.
Listen, sweetie...
it was wrong of me
to force my dreams on you.
Yeah, your generation won't have
any dreams come true.
Sweetie, you're just
gonna be who you are.
Well, who am I?
You are unique,
you are special,
and at some point,
that's gonna come together
and work for you.
I know it.
Thanks, Mom.
And that means
no punishment, right?
Wrong.
You have to walk
all the way over to Grampa
to take a plate
of cookies I baked.
Here's your
new plate, Grampa.
Oh, boy!
There's crumbs on it!
Marge...
I have something to show you.
Is it your impression
of Mr. Burns eating soup?
Because I'm not in the mood.
No, it's something else.
So?
I've always wondered
what you were hiding
under your curly locks,
my beautiful yellow melon.
Hair, no hair...
I don't really think
about it.
Confidence is so
attractive in a man.
Tell me about it.
Oh, Marge, when you
hold me like that...
Thank you, God.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Shh!