[ Camera shutter clicks ]
What if we got married on the Cyclone?
The roller coaster at Coney Island?
Come on. How much fun would that be?
And talk about an appropriate,
if not slightly on-the-nose metaphor...
a bride and groom together,
side-by-side,
as they go through the ups and downs,
the twists and turns,
and the loop-de-loops of life.
Castle, I love you,
but I will not marry you on a ride
or up in space or on a slide.
Bet Dr. Seuss got married somewhere fun.
Yes, his wife's living room.
How many people do you think can fit
in one of those
roller-coaster cars, anyway?
20? 30?
You know, that's a good point.
We should determine exactly whom
we are going to invite.
Yeah, good idea.
That way we can determine
exactly how big
a roller-coaster car we need to build.
Or how big of an actual venue we need.
Either way, I'll go and get the paper.
[ Cellphone ringing ]
I'll get a pen.
And I will get the phone.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Beckett.
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
You know, there's a good argument
for keeping the list really small.
Just immediate family.
This argument doesn't have
something to do with
a certain amusement park ride, does it?
I'm being serious.
Getting married is an intimate act,
and our ceremony
should reflect that intimacy.
And that way,
we could all fit into one car.
Ryan, how do you feel
about roller coasters?
Ooh, make me nauseous. Why?
No reason. Who's our victim?
Peter Cordero, 26.
According to the super, he lives alone.
He's a future's trader at JP Harding,
the Wall Street investment firm.
And how was he killed?
Uh, single GSW to the chest.
Looks like his own future got traded.
Yeah, not without a fight first.
Who found the body?
Well, that's an interesting question.
At 10:03 P.M., a woman made a 911 call
from a pay phone down the block,
but she refused to leave her name.
A pay phone down the block?
But how would she know
he was dead unless...
Unless she was in the apartment.
Well, lividity places the time of death
between 8:00 and 10:00,
so if the 911 call came in at 10:03...
She could be our killer.
Esposito's checking
security-cam footage.
Hopefully, we caught her on tape.
Now, is it just me, or is it odd
that our victim is wearing
a suit jacket, tie, pants,
shoes, but his shirt is unbuttoned?
It's odd, all right. And look at this...
his shirt was on and buttoned
when he was shot.
So our killer unbuttoned
his shirt after he was dead.
Yep.
The killer was looking for something.
A pricy necklace or...
oh, a bunch of cash
taped to his chest
like "Wolf of Wall Street."
There's something else.
I didn't find any defensive wounds,
so if there was a fight out there,
I don't think this guy was in it.
Esposito: Yo, Beckett.
There are no security cameras
in the lobby,
but I found one in
a liquor store down the street.
It got a shot of that pay phone
right when the 911 call came in.
Okay. Canvas the neighbors.
See if anyone saw her in the building.
Did you talk to next of kin yet?
Well, the guy didn't have
any immediate family,
but he did list a cousin in Queens,
a Maria Cordero,
as his in-case-of-emergency.
All right, bring her in.
Let's see if she recognizes
the woman in the photo.
Castle and I will go
to his place of work
and see what they know there.
All right.
[ Camera shutters clicking ]
No. No. I'm sorry. I don't know her.
Maria, did your cousin say anything
about having a girlfriend?
No. He said he didn't have time.
Work was his life.
Were the two of you close?
Peter was like my brother.
[ Sighs ]
When he was 10, his parents died
in the big earthquake in Venezuela.
My parents adopted him
and brought him to the States.
Did Peter say anything
about having any enemies?
No. Peter was a sweet guy.
He never forgot where he came from...
not like those privileged,
silver-spoon types
he worked with.
He was a scholarship kid,
so everything he got
was through hard work.
When did you talk to him last?
A few days ago.
And how did he seem?
Stressed, actually.
Did he say what about?
No. I... I don't know.
When I asked him, he said
something happened at work,
but it wasn't anything
he couldn't handle.
Beckett: JP Harding Investment Bank.
This place is either
the engine of capitalism
or the poster child
of greed and corruption,
depending on which paper you read.
Maybe the invisible hand
of the market killed Peter.
It would explain
the lack of defensive wounds.
You know, prep-school buddy of mine
came to work here out of college.
He made a quarter of a billion
dollars before he was 30,
retired, and bought an island.
Wait. He owns his own island?
We should definitely invite him
to the wedding.
Excuse me. Hi, I'm detective Beckett.
We need to speak
with Peter Cordero's boss.
Jamie Berman, I believe?
Can I tell him what it's regarding?
Berman: Killing...
are you capable of it?
Because if you are,
I will make you rich.
Goldman just poached
Consolidated's pension account
from us this morning,
so I am offering a bounty.
Neal?
A million dollars to the first
son of a bitch at this table
to poach an account back from Goldman.
It's open season, guys...
open-hunting season.
I want you to make them bleed!
[ Cheering ]
Excuse me.
All right, let's go!
Excuse me, Mr. Berman.
Detective Beckett.
Could we have a word, please?
I told you S.E.C. pricks
to talk to my lawyer.
I'm not S.E.C. I'm NYPD... homicide.
Homicide?
I apologize for the theatrics,
detective,
but in this world, it gets results.
And here I thought the stories
of Wall Street excess were exaggerated.
[ Chuckles ]
Mr. Berman, I understand
that Peter Cordero
reported directly to you.
Yes, he was my best commodities' trader.
And one of the nicest guys
you'll ever meet.
In this part of the world, anyway.
Do you have any leads?
Uh, just one.
Do you recognize this woman?
No. I'm afraid I don't.
Well, according to
Peter Cordero's family,
he was having some trouble here at work.
Do you have any idea
what that might have been?
No idea.
In fact, he was having
one of the best months he's ever had.
And what about his clients?
Any problems there?
Well, Pete was a rising star.
His clients loved him...
But...
But what?
Last week, I was taking
the stairs to the 65th floor...
my version of exercise...
and I saw Peter in the stairwell
with this guy
who looked like a gangbanger.
All tatted up his neck,
big scar on his cheek.
Not the kind of guy
you ever see down here.
And he was handing Peter
a package about yea big.
When Peter saw me,
he looked guilty as hell.
So I just kept walking.
And you didn't ask him about it?
Yeah, I did later,
but he said it was nothing,
so I just let it go.
You saw a gangbanger in your stairwell,
and you just let it go?
This is a high-stress
environment, detective.
We don't ask a lot of questions
about what our people do to...
to get through the day.
Okay.
Do you think you can
describe him to a sketch artist?
I think so.
[ Cellphone beeps ]
Great.
I need the names of all of
Peter's associates here at work.
Of course.
Lanie's got something for us.
Lanie: Still no indication
of defensive wounds,
but I did find this when
I checked his nails for DNA.
Castle: Numbers.
"7, 2, 3, 5, 9, 8."
He wrote it in pen
I'd say four or five days ago.
But that's not why I called you.
Look at this.
On his chest, next to the "Y" incision.
- Look at what?
- It's subtle...
so subtle, I almost missed it.
But I think it explains
why his shirt was ripped open.
- You see this grainy material?
- Yeah.
It's adhesive residue.
In fact, there's a residue pattern
from his belly to his chest.
Adhesive?
Mm-hmm.
Looking at the pattern,
I'd say your Wall Street wolf
was wearing a wire.
Gates: A wire?
Beckett: Yes, sir.
We believe our killer removed it
from the victim's body
after shooting him.
Do we know who
he was wearing a wire for?
Well, we're checking
with other branches
of law enforcement right now.
What about this woman
who called in the murder?
Have you been able to identify her?
You know, no one in Cordero's life
seems to know who she is,
and we have no idea where to find her.
I... think she just found us.
Oh, Lord.
I'd say your case
just got a lot more complicated.
What is it, sir?
They're from the U.S. Attorney's Office.
You know them?
Uh, not the woman from the photo,
but the woman with her
is Elizabeth Weston,
the U.S. Attorney
for the Southern District.
She also happens to be my sister.
Castle 6x19 - The Greater Good
Original air date March 24, 2014
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com
Victoria. Been a while.
Yes, it has.
And who is this?
I'm Stefanie Goldmark,
Assistant U.S. Attorney.
We're here about the Cordero murder.
Oh, well, that's funny,
because we have a few questions
about that ourselves.
Beckett: Starting, Ms. Goldmark,
with why you didn't identify yourself
when you made that 911 call
from the pay phone.
Because I instructed her not to.
I couldn't afford to
compromise our investigation.
What investigation?
Is there somewhere private we can talk?
All right, Elizabeth,
what's this all about?
Your victim was a confidential
informant for my office
in an ongoing criminal
investigation of JP Harding.
Which is why Cordero was wearing a wire.
Yes, and since JP Harding
is on the 65th floor,
we couldn't monitor it live.
Cordero put it on every morning
and turned it in every night,
along with the attached
recording device.
Only last night, he didn't.
I went to his apartment
to see what happened.
That's when I found him,
and the wire was gone.
We think that there was something key
to our investigation on that wire
and that's why he was killed.
So where are you on leads?
[ Sighs ]
Well, uh, ballistics
is running the slug,
but right now the only lead
is this sketch,
provided by Mr. Cordero's boss,
Jamie Berman.
It's of a man he saw with our victim.
Well, I wouldn't put
much credence in that sketch.
Why? Why is that?
Because Berman is the target
of our investigation.
Jamie Berman, head of JP Harding?
We've been trying to mount
a case against him for years...
insider trading, securities fraud.
We know he's doing it.
We just haven't been able to get proof.
Not without getting inside.
Berman's too careful.
Then, last month, we caught a break.
Peter Cordero was found
with a baggie of cocaine
during a stop-and-frisk.
With his priors for possession
when he was a teen,
he was facing 5 to 10.
You got Cordero to play ball.
He jumped at an immunity deal.
He'd already gotten valuable information
on his wire recordings.
But yesterday, he was scheduled
to meet with Berman one-on-one.
He was gonna push him to open up
about some of his deals.
Cordero may have pushed too hard.
We think Berman made
Cordero in that meeting.
So you think Jamie Berman's
somehow responsible
for Cordero's death?
Well, if Berman knew
he had incriminated himself on tape...
He'd go to any lengths to get it back.
Victoria, this investigation is ongoing,
and exposing it to Mr. Berman
or anyone at JP Harding
would break federal statutes.
But I thought that this was something
that you and your team needed to know.
I'd certainly say so.
So I trust that you will keep
my office in the loop
if there are any...
significant developments.
Is that clear?
Of course.
Sir, I didn't...
I didn't know you had a sister.
Oh, well, now you do.
U.S. Attorney for the Southern District?
That's a really big deal.
Why hasn't Gates
ever mentioned her before?
I don't know, but there was
definitely a subtle chill
between the two of them.
"A subtle chill"?
More like a polar vortex.
I'm guessing something happened
between them in the past...
something deeply personal
that Gates does not want us
to know about.
I'll give you a dollar if you ask her.
- No way.
- Come on. Aren't you curious?
Yeah, but I like my job too much.
Hey, so, uh, there may be something
to the U.S. Attorney's theory.
I checked Cordero's calendar.
He was scheduled to meet with Berman
at 5:00 P.M. yesterday.
And whatever they talked about,
it got heated.
How do you know that?
According to building security,
the two of them left shortly after
and seemed to be
in the middle of a fight.
Yeah, Peter and I had words yesterday.
So what?
So, you didn't tell us about that
- when we talked this morning.
- 'Cause it wasn't relevant.
Castle: How is it not relevant?
The video shows you leaving together.
Two hours later, he's dead.
It's not relevant
because I didn't kill him.
Honestly, detective,
what would be my motive?
What exactly were the two of you
arguing about?
A business deal.
You looked pretty worked up
for a business deal.
There was a lot riding on it.
What was the deal?
Client confidentiality, detective.
I'm not at liberty to discuss it.
You had a meeting
with Peter before that.
What were you speaking about then?
Other financial matters.
What kind of financial matters?
Sensitive ones, any discussion of which,
even with law enforcement,
would be considered insider trading.
So unless you have a subpoena...
Who else was at the meeting?
Just the two of us.
And what did you do
after you left the lobby?
Oh, we walked up Lafayette
and parted ways around Spring.
What time was that?
Around 6:15.
Where were you between 8:00 and 10:00?
At my usual table at Le Cirque.
[ Knock on door ]
Feel free to check.
It's time.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a conference call with the Fed.
Oh, and if you want to talk
to me again, detective,
call my lawyer.
[ Receiver slams ]
Le Cirque confirms that Berman was there
from 8:00 P.M. till 10:25.
Couldn't have been him.
'Cause a guy like Berman
isn't gonna get his hands dirty.
He's gonna hire someone.
No, your sister's right.
Berman is behind this.
And speaking of your sister...
Let's not.
If Berman is behind this,
he will do everything he can
to protect himself.
Knowing that the feds are watching him,
he would be careful to cover his tracks.
[ Chuckling ]
It's gonna be next to impossible
to trace this back to him.
So, all we're really sure of
is that the sketch he gave us
is a load of fictitious crap
meant to send us in the wrong direction.
It's not as fictitious as you think.
I just got the ballistics back
on the bullet that killed Cordero.
Striations match a slug that was pulled
from a robbery shooting at a bodega
in the Bronx three months ago.
The detectives couldn't make a case,
but their three best suspects
were gang members,
including this guy.
Same guy. Same gun.
Hector Nunez?
Yeah, runs the South Bronx territory
of Los Caballeros gang.
Priors include assault,
attempted manslaughter,
and conspiracy to distribute cocaine.
Maria: No, you're wrong.
Peter had nothing to do with cocaine.
He hated drugs.
Do you know he was arrested
last month for possession?
That's impossible. I know Peter.
He'd never use that stuff.
Are you sure, Maria?
Because he was seen receiving
a package last week from this guy.
No.
[ Sighs ]
It... it can't be.
Do you recognize him?
Hector Nunez.
He was Peter's best friend growing up.
But then he got mixed up in a gang,
and he tried to drag Peter in, too.
Afterwards, Hector changed.
He became dangerous.
Peter cut ties with him
over a decade ago.
Can you think of any reason why
he'd be back in Peter's life?
Hector was a devil.
Peter would have never gotten
mixed up with him again...
...unless he didn't have a choice.
[ Latin dance music playing ]
This is a long way from Wall Street.
This doesn't make any sense.
If Peter was into drugs,
he had enough money
to get them from downtown.
Why would he risk getting them
from someone that he knew was dangerous?
There it is... El Baile Club.
Yeah, unofficial headquarters
of Los Caballeros.
Stick close.
If Hector's as dangerous as advertised,
things might get a little hairy.
"Hairy's" my middle name.
That sounded a lot better in my head.
[ Latin dance music playing ]
Are you sure this is the right place?
Those guys don't look very dangerous.
What about those guys?
Ah, you mean the heavily-armed ones.
We're looking for Hector Nunez.
Beckett.
Hector Nunez?
Detective Beckett, NYPD.
Detective, you shouldn't be here.
You could get hurt.
It's a dangerous neighborhood.
Yeah, well, maybe I should take you
down to my neighborhood.
Let me save you some time.
Whatever it is, I didn't do it.
[ Chuckles ]
And I suppose you've never heard
of a Peter Cordero, either.
What about Peter?
He's dead.
Who did this?
Well, we were thinking you...
...might... be able to... tell us.
I'd never hurt Peter.
He was my best friend.
When we were kids
and the gang wanted to take him,
I wouldn't let them.
I knew he could do better.
So how did he end up
shot and killed with your gun?
Something was going on with him.
He called me last week...
first time in years.
Said he was into some deal
that was gonna make him rich,
but it was dangerous.
In case something went wrong,
he needed to protect himself.
He said he need a weapon.
You're saying you gave him that gun?
Well, he said
he couldn't buy one himself
'cause he was being watched
all the time.
Was that what was in the package
you gave him in the stairwell?
Yeah.
That deal that he was into...
was it drugs?
Not drugs, money.
Something to do with bank accounts.
"Bank accounts"?
Last Thursday night, he came to me,
said he needed one last favor.
He wanted me to take an envelope
to a manager at some bank in Midtown...
Suisse Federal or something.
Castle: Why couldn't he
just do it himself?
Why would he need you?
Said he couldn't afford
to be seen at the bank...
was too risky.
What was in the envelope?
He said something
about transfer instructions.
It was sealed, but there was
a bank account number
written on the outside.
Do you remember the number?
Wrote it down
in case something went wrong.
I guess it did.
Not the same six-digit number
that was on his hand.
After I took the envelope to the bank,
I called Peter at work
to confirm it was done.
That's the last time we talked.
Beckett: Hector's alibi checks out.
He was at Lady of Mercy nursing home
visiting his mom when Peter was killed.
Mysterious financial transactions,
a deal so dangerous he needed a gun...
seems to me there's a lot more
to your sister's star witness
than she knew.
"Than she knew" or than she
chose to tell us about?
Sir?
Yo. Talked to the manager
at Suisse Federal.
He confirmed that a bank account
with those numbers exists,
but he refused to give out
any information on it.
Did he at least acknowledge
it was Peter Cordero's account?
He couldn't,
because he didn't know himself.
It's a numbered account
set up for privacy,
so the only way that anyone can
access it is with a password.
So there's no way to know
what Cordero was doing.
No.
Unless...
Six digits?
Seems kind of password-y to me.
Okay, read it to me.
7, 2, 3, 5, 9, 8.
Come on.
We're in.
Castle, you've done it again.
What's it say?
The balance is zero dollars.
Zero dollars? That doesn't seem
very dangerous.
Feels like the end of a treasure hunt
where you open up the chest
and it's just full of sand.
Wait. Go to the day Mr. Nunez claims
he did the transfer, March 21st.
Oh, my God. $25 million.
Whoa. That's some expensive sand.
Looks like it came into the account
the day before at 8:34 in the morning,
and then Hector transferred it out.
A secret $25 million transfer
that got him killed.
What the hell was Cordero into?
- Right.
- Any luck?
No. I just talked to
the head of Suisse Federal Bank.
Given international banking regulations,
there's no way to tell
where that money came from
or were it went.
Of if the money's even Cordero's.
He could have been moving it
for someone else.
Sir, if this transaction
was somehow responsible
for Cordero's death
and we can't track it,
then we may never be able
to find his killer.
There may be another way.
$25 million?
That's right.
And your informant went
to a great deal of trouble
to keep it secret.
And you have no idea
where the money came from?
No, but odds are
it's what got him killed.
Elizabeth, if you know
anything about this...
Of course I don't know
anything about this.
[ Scoffs ]
You don't believe me.
Do you blame me?
I didn't know.
And given the lengths he went
to hide the transaction,
he clearly didn't want me to know.
Okay, fine.
Then I'm gonna need access
to Peter Cordero's wire recordings.
For what?
Because there may be
something on those tapes
that's relevant to his murder.
We went through them. If there was
anything on there, we would have heard it.
Not if you weren't listening for it.
I'm sorry, Victoria,
but those wire recordings
are a privileged part
of a confidential investigation.
I can't give you access.
"Can't" or "won't"?
Do you think I'm blind?
Bringing down someone as big as Berman,
you'd be able to write your own ticket.
The Mayor's Office, Attorney General...
everything you always dreamed of.
But you need Cordero's testimony,
and if he was involved in anything dirty
while acting as a witness,
it'd jeopardize your whole case.
That's why you won't
give us those tapes...
because you're afraid
of what we might find.
Taking down a shark like Berman
would send a signal
to every fraudulent actor
in the financial market.
I have to think about the greater good.
Oh, is that what you tell yourself
so you can sleep at night?
You could never play the game,
could you?
It's why you're stuck behind a desk
instead of running
the entire force down at 1 P.P.
I am not stuck anywhere.
And I will never, never apologize
for doing my job
to the letter of the law.
Now, I'm gonna need
those wire recordings.
Or do I have to go over your head?
Anything that you find,
you bring it to me first.
Do you understand?
I will not have you screw up
another one of my investigations.
[ Doors slams ]
Let's not put her on the list.
Yeah.
[ Indistinct talking ]
[ Sighs ]
I feel bad for Gates.
My sisters could never work together.
I tell you, when the two of them
went at it... whoo!
I wouldn't mind
going at it with Gates' sister.
Oh, yeah?
How'd you like having Gates
as your sister-in-law?
What?
I think I got something.
So, on March 21st, Peter Cordero's wire
picked up a phone call from Hector Nunez
to confirm that the transfer was done.
The call came in at 9:25 A.M.
That's pretty much what Hector said.
Yeah, but listen to the next
two calls that Peter makes.
[ Clicks ]
[ Cordero speaking Spanish ]
He's saying, "I'm calling
on behalf of Armando Garcia."
"I want to make sure
that his money was received."
"Can you confirm the amount?"
Then he says, "thank you,"
and then hangs up.
Who's Armando Garcia?
I checked with JP Harding,
but they don't have
any clients by that name.
So it wasn't company business?
No. Now listen to the second call.
[ Clicks ]
Cordero: Is he in?
It's Peter Cordero calling.
Hey, everything's taken care of,
but we're running out of time.
We need to get this done
in the next couple days.
Is that gonna be a problem?
Good.
"Everything's taken care of"...
that must be about the $25 million.
But what exactly was getting
done in the next couple of days?
And how did it get him killed?
We need to find Armando Garcia.
Yeah. Unfortunately,
it's a pretty common name.
There are hundreds of Armando
Garcias in the U.S. alone.
It's gonna be hard to narrow it down.
Unless we can find out
who he was calling.
At 9:25, Peter would have been at work.
He would've made those
phone calls from his desk phone.
If we can get those phone records,
they could tell us
what he was involved in.
I'll put in for a warrant.
Hopefully, we'll get it by morning.
You know, I was thinking
about Gates' sister,
and it got me wondering...
do you have any family
I don't know about?
[ Chuckles ]
I don't think so.
Good. Because this
"intimate wedding" of ours...
Oh, no. You too?
- How bad is yours?
- I've got over 100.
I'm at 300 over that.
400?!
Well, to be fair, I am world-famous...
...ish.
Uh, look, it's a first draft.
It just needs some editing.
[ Sighs ]
Brutal, ruthless editing.
Castle, Michael Connelly?
You haven't seen him in over a year.
Do you not remember what
he wrote about your last book?
No. I think we got our first edit.
Uh, well, I have to invite Connelly,
because if he finds out
that Jonathan Kellerman made the cut...
and I have to invite Kellerman
because I have to invite
Wes Craven and Stephen King.
Yeah, but we got to start somewhere.
Well, I think I know where.
Aunt Theresa?
Really?
After what she posted
about me on Facebook?
She took it down.
Fine.
What are we gonna do?
We can't have 500 people at the wedding.
Hello, you two.
Ah, help has arrived in the form
of a neutral third party.
Someone who was born
to be brutal and ruthless.
Thank you. Thank you.
Aha!
[ Chuckling ] Oh, still working
on the invite list, I see.
Yes, actually.
And would you mind joining us?
Love to.
Let me get my list.
Oh, you know, I had no idea how
many people I needed to invite
until I wrote them all down.
Mm.
[ Sighs ]
[ Elevator dings ]
Good news.
I crossed-referenced
my mother's list with my list.
We have three names in common.
Wow, three names. That's... great.
That takes us from, what, 585 to 582?
There's got to be
a better way to cut this down.
Ryan, you guys kept your wedding small.
What was it... like 100 people?
Yeah, that's all we could afford.
How did you contain the list?
[ Inhales deeply ]
I have a lot of relatives
who hate me now.
So, the warrant on Cordero's
phone finally came through.
Whoever this Armando Garcia is,
it has something to do with Venezuela.
That's where Peter was from.
Yeah, that first call
confirming the $25 million?
It was made to a bank in Venezuela.
The second call
was to the Venezuela Consulate
right here in the city.
It was the direct line
of a senior official there...
a Luis Delgado.
Beckett: Clandestine wire transfers,
a high-ranking consulate official,
all circling around
the mysterious Armando Garcia.
What was Cordero doing?
I don't know,
but I can't wait to find out.
Swiss bank accounts,
secret money transfers...
it's got international intrigue
written all over it.
It was just a simple passport request.
A passport request?
Yes, that's why he called.
Well, what about the money?
I'm afraid I don't know
anything about any money.
Really?
I suppose you've never heard of
Armando Garcia, either?
Armando Garcia?
Yes, of course
I heard of Armando Garcia.
Both: You have?
That's who I got the passport for.
Wait, I thought that the
passport was for Peter Cordero.
Yes, Peter Cordero, Armando Garcia...
...it's the same guy.
He changed his name to fit in.
But his birth name was Armando Garcia.
He was sending the money to himself.
You said he was requesting a passport.
A Venezuelan passport?
Yes, of course.
Cordero applied to re-establish
his Venezuelan citizenship,
and we were more than happy to oblige.
Under the name "Armando Garcia"?
That's right. But, uh...
there was something odd
about his request.
He asked to pick up the passport
in Mexico City.
Mexico City? Did he say why?
No, but he was supposed to
get it yesterday
at our embassy there.
He had booked a flight
from Mexico City to Caracas that night.
Gates: He was running away?
Not just running away,
changing his identity completely.
He never intended to testify.
He was just stringing my sister along
until he could escape.
All he had to do was drive to Mexico.
Once he boarded that flight to Caracas
under his new identity,
paid for with a new credit card,
Peter Cordero would cease to exist.
Your sister would never find him.
Beckett: But he wasn't
gonna leave empty-handed,
so he made one last desperate deal.
Castle: The night he was killed,
he was preparing to disappear forever
along with the $25 million.
You don't just conjure
$25 million out of thin air.
It came from somewhere.
And, given the circumstances,
nowhere legal.
If you're right,
it'll destroy my sister's case.
All his testimony will be tainted.
Sir, what do you want us to do?
Find the truth.
In order to do that, we need to know
where the money came from,
and there's no way to find out.
Ryan: Uh, maybe there is.
You know that secret
Armando Garcia credit card?
You know, the one he used
to buy the plane ticket?
We found another charge on it
for a computer station
he rented at an Internet cafe.
He was there the exact same time
that $25 million showed up
in his account.
So whatever he was doing there
was related to the transfer.
That cafe has security video.
If we can get a look
at the computer screen
or Peter's fingers on the keyboard,
maybe we can figure out
where that money came from.
And why he was killed.
Sir, uh... you okay?
Oh, just trying to figure out
how to tell my sister
her case is compromised
without her blaming me.
Why would she blame you
when you're just doing you job?
There's a history.
Mm.
1998.
I had just been made
head of Internal Affairs.
Elizabeth was in the D.A.'s office.
We called ourselves "the dynamic duo."
At the time, Elizabeth was closing in
on a heroin ring in East New York,
and they had an undercover inside.
His testimony was key
to the case, but...
He was dirty?
He skimmed a few eight balls
off the very bust
Elizabeth was building her case around.
And when my office
caught him re-selling it,
she came to me,
begged me not to file charges,
asked me to think of the greater good.
[ Inhales deeply ]
I did my job that day, too.
Hasn't been the same between us since.
[ Knocks on door ]
Esposito: Security video is in.
There's Cordero.
Castle: But the angle
is over the monitor.
- We can't see the screen.
Beckett: - Or the keyboard.
There's no way to tell what he's doing.
Wait a minute. Wait. Who is that?
Take a look at the time code.
It's right around the moment
the $25 million got into
Cordero's Swiss bank account.
It's him. He transferred
the money to Cordero.
A covert transfer from
an untraceable I.P. address,
paid for under an alias.
These people took extraordinary measures
to keep from being discovered.
Zoom in.
Freeze it.
Wait. That's Cordero's boss.
That's Jamie Berman.
Why would Berman secretly pay
Cordero $25 million?
Only one reason.
Cordero must have told Berman
about the U.S. Attorney's investigation.
And Berman was paying him
to throw the case.
If Berman was paying Cordero
to throw the case,
then the recordings
from his wire were all lies.
Berman was feeding
the U.S. Attorney's Office
false evidence.
And if Elizabeth
was building her case on that,
she would have been torn apart
by the defense.
Keeping her out of Berman's business
for quite a while, if not forever.
All this time, my sister thought
she was taking down Berman
when he was really trying
to take down her.
The one thing
it doesn't explain, though,
is why Cordero was killed.
Berman's up to his eyeballs in this.
You bring him in here
and find out what he knows.
Yes, sir.
Berman: I'm afraid
you're mistaken, detective.
I didn't transfer any money
to Mr. Cordero,
certainly not $25 million.
And yet, the moment
that you press that button,
$25 million showed up
in Cordero's account.
You have no evidence that
account belongs to Mr. Cordero,
just as you have no evidence
that money came from my client.
Then why were you with him
in that Internet cafe?
They have good coffee.
I think there's a reason
why you went out of you way
to keep that transfer a secret.
I think Cordero told you
that he was being forced
to be an informant
for the U.S. Attorney.
And knowing that he would never
be able to work again,
he struck a deal with you.
$25 million in exchange
for providing false evidence
to undermine the investigation.
What investigation?
You know exactly what investigation.
And when you found out that he
wasn't gonna finish the job...
that he was gonna leave town
and take your money with him...
you had him killed.
And then you took the wire
that you knew he was wearing
to cover up any recorded
evidence of the murder.
That's all wild speculation.
Not to mention,
you have your facts wrong.
You said Peter was wearing
his wire when he was killed.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
So you knew about the wire?
You admit you were in on it with him.
Jamie.
It's not illegal to know.
And I guarantee you
you will never link me to that payment,
so you'll never be able
to prove witness tampering.
But, yeah, I knew about the wire.
And Peter wasn't wearing it
when he was killed
because he had already left it
for the feds
at the dead drop
at Lafayette and Spring.
How do you even...
The walk that you took together.
You were with him.
I saw him go into the Mailbox door
and put it into one of those boxes.
Thank you for coming.
Of course.
There's been a break in the case?
Beckett: Yes, actually.
New information has surfaced
about Peter Cordero's murder.
In fact, it seems someone
in the U.S. Attorney's Office
lied about Cordero not leaving his wire
at the dead drop the night of his death.
No one lied.
I went to the drop myself.
It wasn't there.
Elizabeth?
Tell her.
Stefanie, if Peter
never turned in his wire,
how did that day's recordings
end up on your computer?
See, even though you erased them,
the tech department here
was able to recover...
everything.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Standard procedure was to turn them over
for analysis the next morning.
But you listened to
those tapes that night,
and you heard something
you weren't supposed to,
at least not until Cordero was gone.
Cordero: I came to the U.S.
believing in the American dream.
So I worked hard and tried to
be honest in a corrupt world,
working for corrupt and greedy people,
because I still believed.
But when you, the U.S. Government,
plants drugs on me,
threatens to destroy my future,
all because you need someone to testify,
how am I supposed to still believe?
I did everything I could
to play by the rules,
but no one else does.
So by the time you hear this,
I'll be gone.
We brought in the cop
that busted Cordero.
He confessed to planting
the cocaine... on your orders.
Why, Stefanie?
You said you needed someone
on the inside,
to make the case against Berman,
for the greater good.
No.
[ Sighs ] Not like this.
When you heard that recording
and found out Peter was leaving,
you knew it would all come out.
So you went to his place.
I... I went to try and talk to him,
but he wouldn't listen.
And then you saw his gun,
and you made sure that his story
would never get out.
And then you made it look like
he was killed for that recording.
Detective Beckett, Mr. Castle.
I would like to commend you
for your exemplary work
in the face of head winds
from me and my office.
Oh, thank you.
But, I mean, we were just
all doing our jobs,
following our Captain's lead.
Did you manage to track down
that $25 million?
Yes, it turns out that Mr. Cordero
donated a large portion of it
to rebuild his hometown...
the one that was destroyed
in the earthquake
that killed his parents.
Are you gonna try to recover it?
Well, it's very difficult
to reclaim funds
once they've left the country.
Think that we have better uses
for our resources.
I should be going, but thank you again.
What about Berman?
Do you still have a case?
Well, not the one that I thought,
but at least I won't embarrass
myself in court
presenting evidence that's untrue.
Then Berman paid
$25 million for nothing.
Bet that hurt.
Probably, but it's not enough.
We will build our case the right way.
It may take some time,
but we'll get him.
Thank you, Victoria.
For what?
For doing your job so well.
So, I know it's... it's late
and you probably want to get home,
but after today,
I could really use a drink...
...and a sister.
Me too.
You know, in the end,
Gates' sister wasn't that bad.
Does that mean we have
to invite her to the wedding?
Yeah, what about that... our lists?
Castle, we can't have
that many people coming.
Agreed. So, what do we do?
I think we have to decide
why we're actually having this wedding.
I mean, are we doing this
not to insult hundreds of people
or are we doing this for us?
Well, for us.
Well, then, why don't we
just take a minute
and write down the names
of all the people
that absolutely, positively
have to be there,
no matter what, to make us happy?
One minute.
Yeah.
That's not much time.
What if we forget someone?
Then they shouldn't have been
invited in the first place.
Let's do it.
Okay.
All right.
- Are we ready?
- Yep.
One minute.
And go.
You stopped writing.
So did you.
[ Both chuckle ]
Of course...
I'm going to have to invite
my mother and Alexis.
- Yeah, and my dad and aunt Theresa.
- Right.
Espo and Ryan, who will bring Jenny.
Mm-hmm. Lanie.
Lanie.
I'm gonna have to invite
the poker group.
- Yeah, Maddie.
- Gates.
Ooh! And Gates' family.
Sync and corrections by atrn97g
for www.addic7ed.com