HENRY: Come on, come on.
DANNY: Oh, oh. Got it.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Aah! Aah!
What? Come on.
(whistle blows on TV)
- Hands of stone. - Come on.
Not again?!
Got to catch it like...
That's the third pass he dropped.
I know.
Where's Frank? It's getting kind
of late, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
he slipped away after mass.
Said something came up.
Come on! Go for it!
Fourth down. Let's go.
Fourth and one.
They got to go for it.
They got to
go for it.
On behalf
of Jets fans everywhere,
I'd like to thank
the three of you
for becoming cops
and not coaches.
(laughter)
What do you mean?
They get the first down here,
they win the game.
Or they lose it
if they can't convert.
The smart play
a coffin corner kick.
A what?
HENRY: No.
What's that?
Punt inside
the five-yard line.
Mom, you are so weird.
Well, I grew up
in a house full of guys.
What do you expect?
Great, they're punting.
Oh. See?
See? See? What did I say?
Coffin corner kick.
Hey, Francis.
Hi.
There you are. Guys, it's time
to wash up for dinner.
Ah, let 'em watch
the end of the game.
You're missing a hell
of a game, Dad.
Heard it on the radio.
You've been gone a long time.
Is everything okay?
I'm fine. Where do you get
a beer around here?
SPORTSCASTER:
Fumble! Fumble! Fumble!
Touchdown!
(screaming and cheering)
(whooping)
(chanting):
J-E-T-S. Jets! Jets! Jets!
DANNY:
Let me hear you guys!
DANNY, JACK, SEAN & LINDA:
J-E-T-S. Jets! Jets! Jets!
That was a great dinner
tonight, wasn't it, guys?
Yeah.
Lively conversation as usual.
Yeah, I particularly liked the
way you so subtly worked in
our little neighborhood
halfway house situation
into the discussion.
I thought
your father should know
that the state of New York
put a home for criminals
a few blocks from where his
grandchildren play, that's all.
He knows,
and you know he knows. Come on.
He's the police commissioner.
He's not the governor.
There's nothing
he can do about it.
What was with
your father anyway?
He seemed quiet.
Babe, he does the same thing
every Sunday.
He sits there, he groans,
he grunts, and then he
says one little thing.
Danny! Danny! Danny!
What? Come on.
He's always quiet.
Well, I know. Just more so
than usual, you know?
That's him. I didn't notice anything.
I can't believe you...
Danny, look out!
(tires screeching, man groaning)
What was that?
(gasps)
You all right? All right, all right.
Are you guys okay?
- You okay? - Yeah. Listen.
- Everyone stay here, okay?
You sure?
Stay put.
LINDA:
You guys okay?
JACK:
Yeah.
You sure you guys are okay, right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Hey.
You all right, buddy?
Still breathing.
All right.
Hang in there, all right?
Step away!
Get the hell out of here!
Why don't you take it easy
with that, all right?
I said go!
Okay.
Listen, we got an injured man
here, all right?
Why don't you just take it easy,
let me help him, all right?
And then, we'll deal with it.
Do it!
All right.
Police! Drop it!
(gunfire)
(groans)
LINDA:
Danny?
Danny!
Danny! Danny?
Danny.
You okay?
Danny, I don't know.
I don't know.
Are you okay?
You okay? Is anybody hit?
No, but it's right here, Dad.
We're okay.
(crying):
Oh, my God, Danny.
You all right?
SEAN: Yeah.
Oh, my God, Danny.
♪ Blue Bloods 2x10 ♪
Whistle Blower
Original Air Date on January 6, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Hey. Boy's asleep?
Look, you're going
to be all right.
Tell you what, as soon
these guys are done,
we'll get out of here,
all right?
You okay?
Hey, guys, come on!
Come on, guys.
Come on, guys...
I need two minutes with Jack;
I'll be right back.
Hey, Jack.
Hey.
Look, thanks for coming in,
dropping everything
on your night off.
Stop sucking up. You know
you'd be my first call, too.
How we doing on the blood? I'm
pretty sure I creased his arm.
Well, there's not
a lot of blood,
but there's enough
for a DNA profile.
All right. Remind those lab rats
where they got their playoff
tickets from, all right?
And tonight, the blood,
the slug from my car--
everything jumps the line, Jack.
I got it, Danny.
All right.
Go ahead, go take care
of Linda and the kids.
I got lucky, you know.
I got him in the arm.
He left some blood at the scene,
which means I got his DNA now.
It's gonna make it
real easy to catch
this son of a bitch.
I notified every hospital
in the city.
Any gunshot wound shows up
anywhere in the city,
in any of the five boroughs,
and I am the first call
they're gonna make.
Odds are, a guy like that
is in the system, you know?
My money says he gets popped
tomorrow, and if he does...
Danny. Danny.
...I'm gonna pop
him real good, too.
Don't worry, babe.
- Just stop. - Don't worry.
Just stop talking.
I promise you
I'm gonna get him.
Stop talking.
What do you mean, stop talking?
(scoffs)
(crying):
Just stop talking, please.
Just stop.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What is wrong?!
(sighs)
(sobbing)
How you doing?
LINDA: I'm good.
I'm good.
But the boys,
you know, they, uh...
They were right there, Frank.
They-they saw the whole thing.
Yeah, I know. Danny told me.
How are they now?
I don't know. Um...
Stunned, I think.
Jack has been quiet.
Well, give it some time.
It'll tell you what they need.
Yeah.
Can...? I'm sorry, Frank.
Can I ask you a question?
I just...
I want to know, uh...
Would you have done
anything differently?
Not a thing.
Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
Where were we?
Chief Hunter's authorization
request to run his
undercover across
the river in Newark.
It'll have to wait.
I'll be down on 13 with Garrett.
Well, what do you mean,
he's not in the system?
And I'm telling you,
you're missing something,
so run him again.
Danny, they ran it three times.
There's no DNA match.
What is the holdup
with this hospital?
Why can't I speak
to my victim?
(sighing): They're checking
with the doctor now.
Tell them that it is
an urgent NYPD matter, okay?
You don't think
I told them that already?
Well, then, tell them again.
Okay, we got
no DNA match.
We got no surveillance video.
There's one way
we're gonna find the shooter.
If their patient--
my victim-- tells us
who the hell was trying
to hunt him down
like an animal
in the street last night.
I will tell them that...
as soon as I'm off hold.
Great. You at least get a name
on the victim?
Carl Patrick.
Good. Can you run him?
No, I didn't run him.
I just got it.
Can you give me a break, please?
Kick him in the shins, Jackie,
like I used to.
Hey, Erin.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
It's nice to see you,
too, Daniel.
It's been a tough
one, okay? Forgive me.
I heard. How are you doing?
I'm fine.
Fine. You look fine.
What brings you down here?
Took a statement off
a robbery collar downstairs.
Buy you a cup of coffee?
Yes.
I'll be back.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry. He's in a meeting.
May I take a message?
He in?
No, he's with you.
Baker, one of us needs glasses.
He said he was going down
to your office.
I haven't seen him all day.
It's Detective Baker
in the commissioner's office.
You got a 20 on the PC?
Okay, thank you.
The commissioner
has left the building.
Let me ask you
a question, Erin.
When did you become a
supervisor in the DA's office?
A couple of years ago. Why?
No. It was
three years ago.
In those three years,
how many times
you come down to the
squad to take a statement
from a D felony
robbery collar?
You never done it.
So, what's going on now, huh?
What, did Linda tell you
to come talk to me?
No, she didn't.
Okay, she just told me
what was going on
between you guys.
I thought maybe I could help.
We're fine.
Danny...
We're fine!
Okay, you're not fine,
and even if you were, she's not.
Look, do you really want in
the middle of this right now?
I'm your sister.
Yeah, and you should
know more than anyone
that if someone takes a shot at
my family, I'm taking him out.
End of discussion.
Danny, I know.
Okay, but you need to look
at it from her perspective.
Those were her babies
in the back of that car.
They're my babies, too.
I know, but you're a cop, okay.
You're used
to bullets flying around.
She's just a mom out there.
(phone ringing)
And I'm a dad out there.
Yeah?
Something came up
you're not gonna like.
The guy you ran over--
he's a resident
at the halfway house
in your hood.
What, he's an ex-con?
Uh, released from prison
last week.
Well, was it a hit?
Is he a mob guy? What?
Worse. He's a child molester.
(sighs)
Unbelievable.
(elevator bell dings)
(elevator doors open)
(elevator doors close)
Shouldn't I know you?
I don't think so.
(elevator bell dings,
doors open)
I was working at a boys
soccer camp Upstate when I...
Look, I'm not proud
of what I did,
but I'm better now.
I got help inside.
I'm healed.
Yeah? And what about Wyatt?
The little boy you raped--
you think he's better now?
You think he's all healed?
I don't expect you
to understand.
I don't understand.
But I paid my debt to society.
Yeah, well,
someone out there thinks
you shouldn't have your life,
and I can't say
I disagree with him.
Now,
you said you believed
that the guy chasing you around
with a gun last night was
this boy Wyatt's dad.
Bruce Richmond, yeah.
Bruce Richmond.
But you also said,
when you left
the halfway house,
you saw someone come chasing up
behind you with a mask on.
So, how can you be sure
it was Bruce Richmond?
Every day I was in prison,
he sent me a letter,
saying he was going to kill me
when I was released.
Mm-hmm.
This morning, he sent those.
DANNY:
"Time's up. Love, Bruce."
Oh, I think it stinks.
Being a public figure?
I would think you're used
to being recognized.
I don't think I'll ever
get used to it.
Or accept it.
You've been a cop all your life.
Cops aren't public figures.
They're public servants.
And I'm not a cop anymore,
I'm a civilian employee.
When I became
police commissioner,
I had to resign from the NYPD.
How do you feel
about not being a cop.
I miss it.
That's a lot to handle
in five years.
You lost your wife,
you lost being a cop,
to become commissioner,
then you lost your son.
This isn't about that.
If you say so.
That's not why I'm here.
Why are you here?
You tell me.
Sorry, doesn't work that way.
You under a lot
of stress lately?
What I meant,
as I think you well know,
was: are you dealing
with more stress than usual?
Well, let's see.
We have a rapist targeting
teenage school girls,
unexplained rapid rise
in subway crime,
and another threat level
increase out of D.C.
No, no more stress than usual.
Have you tried
any sleep medication?
We don't do that.
Who doesn't do what?
Reagans don't take drugs.
Oh.
Is there anything else
Reagans don't do?
This.
Frank, you are
an intelligent man,
and I have no doubts
you are capable
of successfully
deflecting any of my questions
for as long as you wish,
but in 20 minutes,
your hour will be up,
as I suspect you
will be tonight.
Where were you on 9/11?
Here in the city.
Where were you when
the first tower came down?
I was sitting in this chair.
Everybody remembers where
they were at that exact moment.
Where were you, Frank?
I was in the North Tower.
This isn't gonna work.
(children laughing in distance)
"Time's up. Love, Bruce."
You write that?
I did.
Black roses?
(sniffs)
Two years ago, you obtained
a premise permit for a 9mm.
You still own that gun?
It's in my closet.
You understand anything you say
can be used against
you, right Bruce?
(kids shouting playfully)
BRUCE:
Wyatt used to love it here.
Every morning,
I'd bring him out here.
Then again right after school.
Now look at him.
He begged and begged us
to send him to soccer camp,
but his mother wouldn't have it.
I always said she was
too overprotective.
"What harm could... one
week could do?" I said.
I'm gonna need you
to roll up your sleeve
and let me take a look
at your right arm, Bruce.
Maybe I should talk
to that lawyer.
Look, my heart aches
for you and your family.
Honestly, it does, Bruce.
But if that was you last night,
then you took a shot
at my family.
So, I'm gonna ask you
right now, was it you?
I read about the
shooting in the paper;
I wanted that son of a
bitch to think it was me.
Wish I had the balls.
(sighs)
JACKIE:
Well?
It's not the guy.
Huh, you look relieved.
You know what, as bad as I want
to nail this son of a bitch,
the last thing in the
world I really wanted
was for Bruce Richmond to
be that son of a bitch.
The poor guy.
Heartbreaker, huh?
The worst.
All right, why don't
we start over, okay?
Walk it through from the
beginning, see where we're at.
Well, I was thinking,
why don't we
just take a ride
to Staten Island?
What do you mean, Staten Island?
What if Carl Patrick
got into a beef
with one of the other cons
inside the halfway house?
Or someone
outside the halfway house.
Good thinking, partner;
we should go.
BAKER: Where were you?
Urgent police business.
I've been looking
all over for you.
We've been trying to cover...
Thank you, Baker. Carry on.
Where have you been?
Mrs. Reagan.
You've gained some weight.
You left without telling anyone.
I went out.
I can do that,
you know, Garrett.
Not without your
detail, you cant.
I looked both ways
before crossing the street,
and I didn't talk to strangers.
Where's your pin?
In my pocket.
Frank?
Your spin is not necessary here.
My spin is not all
I'm good for, Frank.
I know that.
Look, you're talking to a guy
who's on wife number three.
I know how the start
of an affair can be
logistically challenging.
Boy.
I never could get one past you.
I can help you.
Going forward, I can
put out your schedule in ways
that won't raise any questions.
Thanks, Garrett, but I'm
not sure it is going forward.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
What can you do?
Just curious-- why not?
Too young? Too old?
More like the type that asks
too many questions.
Been there.
Baker...
where were we?
(door closes)
CROWD (chanting):
Halfway, no way!
Our neighbors have been going at
it like this for about a month
ever since they turned this
joint into a halfway house.
I got to tell you, Reagan,
I got kids,
and they put murderers
and molesters next door to me?
I'd be right out there
with them.
You and my wife both.
Well, there's nothing like
a mother protecting her young.
Halfway, no way!
So how is she?
(sighs)
All right.
So you really think one
of your neighbors here
is the shooter?
I don't know.
Crime's up ten percent since
they opened this place.
Look at them.
They've clearly had enough.
Staten Island, you know,
not exactly known
for turning the other cheek.
Mm.
Yeah, well, why don't we
swing by the local precinct.
See if any sector car
took any complaints.
(phone ringing)
Good idea.
Hold on.
Hey.
O-Okay, slow down, slow down.
What happened?
He what?
Okay, I'm, I'm on my way.
All right.
What happened?
(car starts)
Hey.
How's Jack?
He's okay; he's fine.
What do you mean, he's okay?
You said he was crying.
He came home from school;
he never comes home from school.
He just, he wanted to come home.
Because of last night?
Yeah.
The nurse said that
he just keeps...
seeing the flash from the gun.
(exhales)
Always point it in
a safe direction.
Number two?
Never touch the trigger
unless you're ready to shoot.
And rule number three?
Assume every gun is loaded.
That's right.
I was just a little bit
younger than you
the first time my dad
let me hold his gun.
But he trusted me
to be responsible and safe.
The same way I'm trusting you.
You understand?
(quietly):
Yeah.
Okay?
Mm.
All right.
Chamber's empty.
Gun's clean.
Okay.
Give me your hand.
Get your thumb under
there, right there.
Watch the trigger.
Keep your finger outside
the trigger guard.
Support it with your other hand.
Keep it aimed down.
Okay.
Down is safe 'cause no
one's below us right now.
All right?
It's kind of heavy.
Yeah, it's heavy.
It's not a toy.
Jack, what you saw
the other night...
There are times in life
when you're gonna have
to stand up for yourself.
You're gonna have to defend
yourself and your family.
I'm so sorry you
had to see that.
But you did.
You gonna be all right?
Yeah.
What's going on?
Hey.
Jack, give that back
to Daddy right now.
Linda, it's fine.
You heard me, Jack.
It's all right.
Go on upstairs.
Go ahead.
(gun clicks)
Linda, he was afraid.
He was curious.
He asked if he could see it.
So you said yes.
It's time.
Two days after he's almost shot
is-is time for him to play
with your gun?
He wasn't playing
with it, Linda.
I'm teaching him about it.
Look, we-we can either
make him a part of it
with my supervision,
or we can wait.
We can wait until him
and his kid brother
are snooping around
in the closet
one day when we're not home,
and then God forbid.
Those are wonderful
options, Danny.
Look... the biggest
mistake we can make
is to pretend that my gun
does not exist in this house.
Okay. Listen to this.
Cops at the 1-2-5
took a robbery complaint
just three hours
before the shooting.
Oh, what do we got here?
An irate father threatening
to kill somebody
after a 16-year-old girl
was held up
at gunpoint for an iPhone?
What's the connection?
Keep going.
Why would a guy pissed off
about a robbery
want to hunt down Carl Patrick?
Look at the description
she gave of the perp.
Six-two, male, white,
reddish hair.
That's Carl Patrick to a tee.
What do we got here?
A case of mistaken identity?
Well, I'm thinking the guy's in
such a rage that he goes after
the first person he sees coming
out of that halfway house
that fits the description.
(tapping on computer keys)
Come on, give me a name.
Unbelievable.
I know this schmuck.
A friend of yours?
No. Our boys were on the same
football team together,
that is,
until he yelled at my son,
and we almost came to blows.
Oh, so this
should be fun.
(thud, grunts)
Come on, harder, harder.
Square your shoulders up.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
I don't know
the meaning of that word.
Come on, let's go.
Be a man.
There!
Welcome to the NFL.
Come on, get up.
Hey, Wayne.
How's it going?
Reagan?
This is my partner,
Detective Curatola.
I see Dylan still
hits like a bull.
Yeah, well,
practice, practice, practice.
Uh-huh.
You got a second?
Go on, take a blow.
What's up?
We understand
your daughter
was the victim
of a crime the other day.
Yeah. Jennifer.
One of those
halfway house dirtbags
mugged her
right on Richmond Avenue.
I'm sorry to hear
about that.
She did get a good look
at the guy though, right?
I thought you worked
in Manhattan.
What? You get bumped down
to Staten Island now?
I take a special
interest in cases
close to home, you know?
Yeah. Well, what do you
want to know?
I-I already told the cops down
at the precinct everything.
Yeah, sure you did.
We just want to know
if you or Jennifer
have seen the guy since.
No.
No? You didn't
go after him,
go looking for him?
Try to find him?
Yeah, well, you told the cops
down at the station
you were gonna find him
yourself.
How'd that work out for you?
No. No, I, uh, had something
to do that night.
Mm-hmm. What'd you have
to do that night?
Dinner.
Dinner? Where'd you go,
locally, restaurant?
HOLLIE: No, it was
here at home.
Hello, Hollie.
Hey, Danny. How's Linda?
She's good.
Will you tell her
that I said hello?
I will.
So, Mrs. Rivano, you had,
uh, dinner here on Sunday?
That's right.
And who was here with you?
The kids.
Anyone besides a family member
who could
corroborate your story?
Corroborate my story?
We're just trying to sort out
what happened that night.
Yeah, well, one of those animals
from the halfway house
stuck a gun
in my daughter's back.
That's what happened.
Yeah, told us that already.
Do you own a gun, Wayne?
What's going on here, Danny?
Do we need to call a lawyer?
I don't know, Hollie.
Wayne, do you need a lawyer?
You know what?
This conversation is over.
Get the hell off my lawn.
As you wish.
Well, if it walks like a duck,
talks like a duck...
Must be a duck.
ERIN:
But I'd have to prove it,
which I can't.
Not with what I got,
which is nothing.
It's just a warrant.
Let me run his DNA
against the blood
I found at the crime scene.
I promise you it'll match.
Based on what?
Based on he took a shot
at my kids.
Your nephews.
That is a low blow,
even for you.
(sighs)
You're right. I'm sorry.
Can I get the warrant?
I'm sorry.
(slams shopping cart)
Hey, Hollie,
nice to see you.
I wish I could
say the same.
One phone call from
your father-in-law,
that's all it
would have taken
to shut down that
damn halfway house.
I'm sorry, you know,
but that's not exactly true.
You Reagans...
you-you walk around like you're
big shots, but when it's time
for you to put that
big name of yours to use,
you don't lift a finger.
You know what, Hollie?
I don't have a clue
what you're talking about,
but, as usual, it just sounds
like a bunch of trash.
Excuse me.
You think you're so much better
than the rest of us, don't cha?
No, Hollie. Just you.
You tell your husband
the next time he steps foot
on my property,
he'd better have a warrant.
Or a Swat team.
It's 4:00 in the morning, Pop.
You should be asleep.
I was about to tell
you the same thing.
I know you were.
I got a full day
tomorrow.
Knock it off.
We live in a
hundred-year-old house.
You think I haven't heard you
working the floor every night?
Francis...
why do you still wear
your wedding band?
Old habit.
Mary got sick.
That wasn't your fault.
Pop, you sound like a shrink.
It wasn't your fault
when the mayor offered you
the PC job a month
later either.
The department needed
you to step up.
She wanted me to take the job.
You never told me that.
What she didn't want
was her youngest
joining the family business.
Oh, yeah, she was so proud
when he graduated law.
And relieved.
Francis, that was
Jamie's choice.
Well, I still see it as my job
to worry for both of us.
When Tom Costello
took that bullet
standing next to you,
how'd you feel?
Every cop's worst nightmare:
their partner dying
in their arms.
Did you ever ask yourself,
why him and not me?
Every day.
Was there a moment
you were glad it wasn't you?
John McKenna's not doing well.
Oh...
You guys went through
a lot together.
Competed
for different promotions.
I lost touch.
I hadn't seen him
since he went on disability.
We were side by side
in the North Tower.
When the South Tower went,
we just looked at each other,
and we knew that twice
as many people were trapped
above the impact
in our building.
(sighs)
We lost almost 3,000 that day,
but it's not over.
People are still dying.
Son...
(sighs)
I don't know why Chief McKenna
got sick from the air
down there, and you didn't.
Just like I don't know why
he took Mary and Joe
from us too soon.
But I see God's light
in this family every day.
And though I may
not understand it...
I trust in His plan for us all.
LINDA: Heavenly Father,
we thank you for this food
we are about to receive, for the
love that you show our family
and for the wisdom
that you grant us in making
the right decisions. Amen.
OTHERS: Amen.
What a beautiful blessing, Aunt Linda.
Really nice.
Yeah, especially the bit there
at the end about making
the right decisions.
I'm just saying
grace, Danny.
Yeah, and Erin's
potatoes aren't soggy.
Beg your pardon?
Everything all right down there?
Everything's fine, Gramps.
Fine, my ass.
You two still fighting?
Could we talk about this
another time, please?
You brought it up.
Grandpa never misses
family dinner.
Why isn't he here?
Well, he just said that
something came up,
and he didn't have time
to explain, that's all.
I'm waiting, Detective.
Honestly, Gramps,
it's nothing.
Just because your father
isn't here doesn't mean...
that the rules have changed.
Everything has been fair game
at the Reagan
family dinner table.
Always has been. Always will be.
Yeah.
So... what's going on?
Well, Linda wants me
to drop the case.
I didn't ask you
I asked you to hand it off.
Same difference.
No, it's not.
Oh, great, you're
lawyered up now.
No, she didn't
lawyer up.
I just happen to
agree with her.
Oh.
Danny, no one wants this
guy who shot at our kids
nailed to a wall more than I do,
but, you know, this is just--
this is too much.
It's too close to home.
What, is there 300 other
first-grade detectives
who could take the case?
Yeah, but none of 'em are
as good as Uncle Danny is.
Nicky.
I'm sorry,
but it's what I think.
Thank you.
Isn't that another rule
at family dinner?
Everybody's opinion counts.
That's right.
It's my opinion, too.
Danny's the best we got.
You got to let him
see it through.
You know, I...
I'm done playing second fiddle
to the NYPD.
FRANK: The only thing harder
than being a cop
is being married to one.
What'd you used to say
about Danny?
He is cursed
with the gift for the job.
I'll tell you this,
he's got the Reagan temper.
Yeah, I know, now that
I'm a big-time diplomat,
I got to sit
on mine,
but... I see myself
in Danny every day...
...and it makes me proud.
Worry about Erin-- the divorce.
(sighs)
Raising kids by yourself
can be rough...
and daughters are special...
as you well know.
Oh, here's one for you:
my youngest,
my Harvard lawyer is a cop--
something Mary didn't want.
John, I'm sorry
I haven't been around for you.
When you went out
on three-quarters, I...
I'm not gonna blame it
on the job.
(sighs)
Life plays tricks on you.
(footfalls,
door opening)
(sighs)
Bye, old friend.
(sobbing)
(garbage truck stopping)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on.
This belong to that house?
Yeah.
Okay, great, know what?
Leave it with me,
I'll take care of it.
All right?
Hey!
You stay right there, all right?
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Reagan?
I said don't move.
Get the hell out of my trash.
You leave trash out on the curb,
and it can be searched
without a warrant,
Wayne.
I'm calling
a lawyer.
You go do that.
What are you gonna do with that?
I'm gonna lift the DNA off it
and match it to the blood
you left at the crime scene
when I shot you in your arm.
You're out of your mind.
I'm out of my mind?
You say I'm out of my mind?
Hey, take it easy, all right?
You could have killed my kids,
and I'm out of my mind?
Hey.
Take it easy, would you,
Reagan, all right?
What's the matter?
Not so tough
without your mask?
I didn't do it,
all right?
Good, prove it.
Come on, roll
up your sleeve.
Just listen to me.
I'll give you three seconds
to roll up your sleeve.
Ho, ho, ho,
just take it easy.
Three...
Listen to me.
Two...
All right, all right, all right.
One!
All, all right.
This is for my family.
(screaming)
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a court of law.
I still remember the first time
I saw you in your dress blues.
That was outside
of Pizza Amore.
Yeah... and you were
in trouble with me, then, too.
Why do you think I
wore the uniform?
Now I only ever
see you in it
when we're going
to a funeral.
I was going to
wait till later...
...to give this
to you, but...
What is that?
Open it.
Danny.
I love being a cop, Linda--
it's always been more
than a job to me--
but nothing on this planet
is more important to me
than you and those boys.
(sighs)
I do not want you
to stop being a cop.
I just need you to
know that I would.
(sighs)
Oh, Danny.
I love you.
I love you more.
(bagpipes playing
"Amazing Grace" inside church)
Where were you on 9/11?
That question has become
part of the fabric
of our lives
as Americans.
On 9/11, I was with a hero.
I was with John McKenna.
On that beautiful,
cloudless morning
that seemed to promise
nothing but goodness,
John and his dear wife Molly
were about to pull
out of the driveway
for a much-needed
and long-overdue vacation,
but when news of the attack came
over the radio...
...they both knew
that Montauk would have to wait.
Molly kissed him good-bye,
urged him to be careful,
as she had done every day
for the almost 30 years...
that he served and protected
this city.
And then John headed
for Ground Zero.
Where were you on 9/11?
On September 11, 2001,
John McKenna saved
more than 100 lives.
You see this?
It's worn by
the first responders that day.
John could wear it as proudly
as anyone who was there.
Why them and not me?
As a cop, I've asked myself
that question...
many times.
But I have come to realize
that just about...
any New Yorker...
...could ask themselves
the same question.
And some questions
have no answers.
(sniffs)
All that is left
for we, the living, to do
is honor them,
take care of them...
(sighs)
...and rededicate ourselves
to the cause for which they gave
the last full measure
of devotion.
FRANK: John...
...may the road rise up
to meet you.
May the wind be always
at your back.
May the sun shine warm
upon your face,
the rains fall soft
upon your fields,
and until we meet again,
may God hold you
in the palm of his hand.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==