Okay, gather round,
everybody, gather round.
Gather round, please.
I have a, uh, a presentation.
Now, because of everyone's
A.D.D., I know I'm gonna
lose your attention in
about three minutes,
- and, uh, Frank's gonna fall asleep.
- No way.
I slept 26 hours last night.
You still seem very sleepy.
Can I start my presentation?
Where's the easel? No, no, I'm not
using an easel... don't interrupt.
You want me to go get the projector?
No, I don't want the projector.
And I don't want the easel.
What are you gonna point with?
Don't want whatever the
hell you're gonna say.
'Cause it's all gonna be old
and outdated, all right?
Let me start my presentation,
which is actually about that.
It's about innovation.
Not taking questions. Goddamn.
Let me do my thing, okay?
Stop interrupting.
Okay, so, um, as we all know,
um, tomorrow is St. Paddy's Day,
traditionally our
most profitable day.
However, recently, profits
have been declining.
Every year.
And we need to change.
We need innovation.
We need to move Paddy's
from the past and into...
the future,
a mobile Paddy wagon.
Now, these days, people like
to have things on demand.
So instead of having
to go to a bar,
we will bring the bar to you.
Ooh, is that, like, a car
service type of thing?
Where we pick people up and
take 'em around from bar to bar
and jack up the prices?
That's actually a really good idea.
Uh, no.
The Paddy's wagon is the bar.
No, Dennis.
If we want to make money,
we need to honor ancient
Irish traditions,
like serving an irresponsible
amount of booze to people
who are genetically predisposed
to having alcohol problems.
- Right.
- You see,
St. Patrick started
that tradition,
and that's why we
celebrate him today.
Yeah... No, that's
not what he did.
No, he-he played
the flute for some kids,
and then he lured them
into a cave somewhere,
- and he diddled them.
- Nah.
You got him mixed up with the Pied Piper.
Right.
St. Patrick didn't
play the flute.
He drove the kids
out of Ireland.
And then he molested 'em.
No, no, if-if St. Patrick
molested kids,
he would be regarded as a scoundrel.
No, no, no.
I feel like, in the olden days
of the Catholic Church,
pedophiles were
regarded as heroes.
All right, all right,
look, g-guys, uh,
St. Patrick didn't do
any of that shit, okay?
He drove the snakes
out of Ireland.
Uh, I-I don't know
about all this.
I kind of want to just do
the traditional thing
of, like, sticking
around the bar
and-and trying to catch the leprechaun.
No, no!
No, we don't want to do a
leprechaun thing again.
Stop, stop, guys...
I'm gonna catch one.
I'm, like, this close.
You're not gonna catch him
because he doesn't exist.
Guys, please...
You know what...
I don't even know
if I've set up
my glue traps for him yet.
Charlie, enough
with the leprechaun!
I mean, can you believe him?
Okay, wait.
Who cares? Look, I'm trying to...
You know what,
actually... I might
want to get myself a flute.
I was thinking the same thing.
We've been talking... you were?
Yeah, because I-I feel like
it's a really fun...
I know we're kind of old, but...
Go get a flute?
Go get a flute, yeah.
Go get... go get a flute!
Everybody go get a flute!
In the sixth grade,
I feel like it's kind of simple.
Frank, look...
All right, let me
explain it to you, at least.
No, he's gone.
Okay.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com.
So, Frank, here's the plan.
We're gonna fill the wagon
with hip, attractive clientele.
We're gonna use my streamlined
system to process drink orders.
We're gonna take photographs
with a retro filter
for the Web site.
And that will entice
future end users
to comment
and spread brand awareness
over various
social media platforms.
That seems insanely complicated.
Why don't we just take cash?
No, no, no, no. What I'm talking
about's way simpler than cash.
It's-it's streamlined.
I'm lost. It's... I'm
trying to explain it to you
and I feel like you're not
even listening. I-I...
Top o' the morning,
you filthy lads.
I'm fixing to have a whale of
a time in this here mobile pub.
I'm so sorry... what is this?
Crazy Paddy, you big, dumb arse.
Yeah. Why?
'Cause it's fun. No.
I thought that's the thing
about St. Patrick's Day...
People want clownery and-and
they want to embrace
the Irish stereotypes. No, no, no.
This isn't innovative.
It's outdated and it's gonna
offend people.
Well, I brought my piece in case
anybody gets out of line. Oh, I...
Okay, Frank, Frank,
look... no guns.
Let go. No guns, no costumes.
Trust me, I got this.
Frank, you're gonna drive.
Drive.
Okay, Dee, you're
gonna serve drinks. In the back.
As a human being. A real one.
Mm. Guys,
I'm gonna provide...
the experience.
Ooh.
Okay, yeah. Yeah, right?
Yeah, I like this. Nice.
I... See, I told you.
I know what I'm doing.
Come on, let's go.
Frank, you're driving.
Okay. Here we go.
Ho! Check it out, Mac...
Got some cool stuff.
I got some green paint
and I found a snake.
Great. Why?
You know, the snakes, 'cause,
like, we... I don't remember
where we landed on St. Paddy,
but I remember snakes
were involved. And the green
paint's for the, uh, beer.
Okay, love the snake.
Great catch there.
But why not just use food
coloring for the beer?
Uh, 'cause beer's not a food.
When was the last time
you ate a beer?
you drank paint?
Have you been drinking paint?
No.
Let me see your tongue.
Oh, my God, dude!
Oh, that shit's just disgusting!
It's not bad.
You... you can't drink paint. I know.
I hear you, I hear you.
You say that, but I don't think
that you're gonna stop.
Yeah, I get it, though, man.
It's, uh... Right.
I-I feel like you're saying you
get it, but you don't get it.
It's cool. It's not cool.
It is what it is. Oh, my God,
this is so frustrating! Look,
I'm gonna go down
to the basement
and I'm gonna check
out my glue traps
and see if I, you know, got a leprechaun
in there. Wait, no, no, no, no.
What... We said
no leprechaun this year.
You're not chasing leprechauns.
I know, and I kind of forgot
where we landed on that.
I got these great cookie sheets,
they're filled with glue, so...
But I-I hear you, I hear you.
It's a frustrating thing.
It's like the guy doesn't
listen to us, man, when we're
trying to get through to him.
It's a bummer.
No, not you.
Keep moving, let's go,
come on. You kidding me?
Oh, oh, h-hey-hey,
there, fellas.
What's going on?
Where you going? You know what?
Don't answer that.
Because I already know.
You're going for a ride
in the Paddy's Wagon.
Oh, cool. Is this,
like, a car service thing?
Hey, can you take us
to Center City?
No, it's not a goddamn car
service. Why does everyone...
You get in that
wagon right now or I'm gonna
sock you a good one
right in the kisser!
Yeah, you dumb bi...
What the hell are you doing?
Uh, just innovating.
I took the Paddy's wig
and I cut it
into an awesome beard.
Great new character. No.
Hilarious.
You've just created another
offensive Irish stereotype, Dee.
The Fighting Irish...
I-it's true.
I mean, that's what Irish people do.
That is not what...
They get drunk,
they fight people.
All right, I'm trying to give
these guys... Look, guys,
don't pay attention to her.
I-I want to give you
an authentic, um, uh,
once-in-a-lifetime
experience here.
Oh. Oh, wait, so is
this, like, a bang bus?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not a bang bus, okay?
Look... Just get in the wagon,
I'll give you a ride
to Center City.
Get in.
Gentlemen,
let me walk you through how
our simple business works.
God, take it easy, Frank!
Don't tell me
how to drive, you bitch.
Let... Let's keep it light for
the customers, all right, Frank?
As I was saying, fellas,
uh, what you're gonna
need to do is you,
uh, you're gonna
take a picture of this QR code,
you're gonna download the app,
log in using Facebook,
and you're gonna watch
a-a brief, 30-second
advertisement.
And then once we receive
your online order,
you will promptly
be served a beer.
Can't I just pay you cash?
That's what I... Yeah.
Well, no, cash is the way
that antiquated
companies do business.
Yeah, I just want a beer.
I don't really
want you to have
all my personal information.
A beer. Just want a beer.
Don't want you to have my...
Yeah.
Look, man, um, if I
just gave you a beer,
and you just gave me cash,
then you wouldn't
be able to experience
everything that we've
got to offer here, okay?
Look, I'll show you. This...
Let me just pull up my...
I got a little presentation
here that I put together.
But, uh, can't get the goddamn
thing to... to go online.
I don't have a signal here.
Goddamn it. You know what?
Dee, uh, why don't you just
give him a couple free beers?
We'll-we'll call
'em "freemiums."
Don't know if you're
familiar with that term.
This is like all foam.
Dee, you goddamn bitch!
Hey! Oh, this thing's
bouncing around
like a pinball. Don't blame me.
Keep it light, you bitch!
All right.
Yeah, this is weird to me.
Can we just get out here?
Hey, it's locked.
Can you guys let us out?
No, I'm not gonna let you out. Screw this.
I'm calling the cops.
Why would you call the cops?
We're just hanging out, man!
All right, stop, stop, stop.
All right, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh. Push "end." End.
Give the phones to the girl.
Let's go, guys. I don't want
to have to do this shit.
Frank, we got to
pivot the business.
Mm-hmm.
Come on, get the hell out.
Everybody out.
Out, out, out, out,
out, out, out, out.
All right.
Don't worry. We're gonna mail
your phones back to you, but
we're gonna need your addresses,
so fork over your I.D.'s.
Let's go. Come on.
And their money.
We can't have 'em
cabbing it back to the city
and going straight to the cops.
Goddamn it. That's a good point.
Okay, you know what?
Dee, collect their wallets.
Don't worry, guys.
We're not thieves.
You'll get your
wallets back, too.
Yeah. Don't be babies.
All right, uh,
come on, come on, guys,
let's go, let's go.
Let's go. Shut the doors.
Did we just kidnap
and rob those guys?
We just drove the
snakes out of Philly,
the way St. Patrick did.
Oh!
So, what you're saying is,
technically, we gave those guys
a very authentic
St. Patty's Day experience.
Oh. Yeah.
Nice. In a way.
Oh. All right.
That's good. That's good. Yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Here.
Jesus Christ, where's Charlie?
Hey, Mac, somebody stole my damn wallet.
What?!
Beat it! Beat it, Mauricio!
I need to talk to Mac.
Charlie, where have
you been, dude?
I can't run the bar by myself
and do security.
People are getting
their wallets stolen.
Okay, uh, look, just come
to the basement with me,
like, really quick.
Goddamn it! All right.
Attention, everybody.
Irish honor system.
Please serve yourselves.
Put the money in the bucket.
Thank you.
Uh, I don't think the Irish
honor system's a thing, man.
Oh, it's a thing.
It's an ancient Irish tradition.
Know your history, bro.
What could possibly
be so important?
Charlie...
what the hell am I looking at?
I caught him.
Wake up that son of a bitch.
Dude, I think you've
kidnapped a little person.
Huh?
Nah... nah, nah. First of all,
I've captured
a leprechaun, okay?
You wouldn't say,
"I kidnapped Bigfoot," right?
You'd say, "I captured Bigfoot."
Well, that may be true,
but leprechauns aren't real.
So what we're dealing with here
is a little person
in a glue trap.
Yeah, I thought about that,
ruled it out, okay?
'Cause the basement door
is locked, so unless
he's a being
who's unrestrained by the laws
of the physical world,
he's not getting down here, man.
Dude, if he is a human being,
he's going to sue
the shit out of us.
If he's a leprechaun,
he's got a pot of gold.
Yeah...
Well, yeah, that's... No, no.
Well, let's not rule
one out over the other.
I mean, it's very weird
that he's down here, right?
Okay. Let's ask him.
Uh, sir, I'm gonna ask
you a direct question.
Are you now or have you
ever been a leprechaun?
No, I'm not
a goddamn leprechaun!
Please... It was
pretty convincing.
Are you kidding me?
If he's a leprechaun, that's
what he has to say, right?
Sir, why are you
dressed like a leprechaun?
'Cause it's St. Paddy's Day,
you idiots!
- This guy's good. He's good.
- Yeah.
Nasty little son of a bitch,
isn't he? You think?
There's, like,
a real bite to him.
I know. You know what
I think we should do?
We just rough him
up a little bit.
You know, just get the truth
out of him, just a little bit.
It's a great idea.
We don't want to bruise him up.
Yeah.
You know, so, I just wish we
had, like, a hose or something.
Yeah. You know, we could
blast the truth out of him.
Right? That'd be good...
Oh, shit.
There's a hose right here.
I... I don't ever remember
a hose being down here, do you?
No. I don't know. Dude...
do you realize
what just happened?
You made a wish, which
the leprechaun clearly granted.
You know, everyone knows,
you capture a leprechaun,
you get three wishes, right?
So we got to think very carefully
what our next two are here.
I wish I could live forever?
What are you doing?!
I wish you don't. How about that?
No, no! Why did you do that?
Why did you do that?
Why didn't you say,
"I wish I could live forever."?
And live forever with you?!
Well...
Look, I'm not a leprechaun!
Just let me out of here,
you dickheads!
Ah. Wish there was a way
we could just know
for sure, you know.
Charlie?
Get the snake.
The problem was, Frank...
that last group of belligerent
hooligans just didn't understand
how to experience
our business properly,
but I think this new group
is gonna get it.
Plus, they're physically weaker,
in case anything goes wrong.
What's happening?
I'll tell ya what's happenin'.
One day you're young and pretty,
and the next, the years
of drinking and abuse
have robbed you of your youth.
Abuse? Did these guys hurt you?
No!
Me husband did this to me.
Arrr!
Dee... Mm?
What the hell are you doing?
What are you...?
What, are you a pirate?
I can't tell if you're
doing a thing now,
or if this is just
who you've become.
I've giving them
an authentic Irish experience,
like you were begging for
before...
You're giving them a
completely inauthentic,
frightening experience,
and you're scaring them.
Okay, listen, ladies,
nobody's gonna get hurt.
Will you just let us out,
please?
Well, no.
No, I'm not gonna let you out.
I need you to
experience everything.
I-I have to offer,
okay, so you're...
Rahr! So, experience... Dee!
Shut up!
All right, look, we're gonna
have a good time here, okay?
You're experiencing some
free beers right now
because I can't get the
goddamn Internet to work.
That's a problem for me.
Do you guys know how to use
tablet computers? You're young.
No.
I just want to connect the
goddamn thing to the Internet.
They told me it'd be easy.
It's not, though.
Okay. Well, I'll tell you what.
I'll let you out after I take
a couple photographs of you.
How's that sound? Yeah?
Take some photographs
for my... for my Web site?
So, look happy.
Look like you're having fun.
No need to cover those up.
My customers like those.
They're like me.
They're gonna want to see that.
Yeah, okay, so smiling
smiling and...
You're not convincing me. Smile!
Oh, damn!
This is not
supposed to be scary.
This is supposed to be an
authentic, fun time for you.
Yeah, all right, well,
I need to buy it, okay?
I'm... Please let us out.
I don't want to be on
your weird Web site. Shh.
Well, if you don't comply with
me, then you're gonna end up
on the weird one, okay?
So, smile.
Ugh! All right.
You know what?
This isn't gonna work.
All right, come on, come on.
Let's go. Come on.
All right, out you go, ladies.
Out you go.
I know you didn't
threaten to call the cops,
but you would have...
I'm certain of it...
So I'm gonna need
your wallets and your phones.
Give 'em to the girl.
Oh, yeah, I'm probably gonna
pop on your Twitter accounts,
just so you know. Write us some,
uh, enthusiastic reviews,
which you would have done,
as well,
had you experienced
our business properly,
but you decided to be...
All right, well...
Talk, bitch! I'm blasting you! Come on!
Talk! Come on, leprechaun!
Come on, leprechaun, admit it!
Where's the gold?!
Aw, what's the point, dude?
There's no water pressure.
I feel like I'm giving him a baby bath.
Yeah, I know.
Snake's not working either, man.
Well, that's
because the snake is dead.
Because you put it in a plastic
bag and it couldn't breathe.
All right, doesn't matter.
He probably killed it
with his leprechaun
magic, anyway.
I'm not a leprechaun,
you goddamn assholes!
Yeah, yeah, guy. How are we
gonna get his pot of gold
if he won't even admit to us
that he's a leprechaun?
I mean, if this guy would
just admit he was a leprechaun,
we could be done with this whole mess.
Well, yeah.
- Of course.
- Okay, fine, you got me.
I'm a leprechaun. I admit it.
What?
God... I am a... I'm a...
damn... a... I'm a leprechaun.
Yeah, right, but you don't
have the accent, That's...
and that's throwing me off, right?
It's throwing me off.
I live in a faraway land,
and I was transported here
by a giant magical rainbow.
And you never got me
Lucky Charms.
Oh! That's it! That's it!
You were right! Dude! You caught a
leprechaun! I told you, man! I knew it!
Hey, can you let me go now?
No, you can't go. You know...
No. No.
We need your pot of gold.
Where is it? Yeah.
It's at the bottom
of the rainbow.
Hmm. Must be some sort
of leprechaun riddle,
'cause there's no
rainbows out today.
No, dude... I don't think
this guy's talking in metaphors.
I think he means exactly
what he's saying. Yeah?
Dude, he's talking
about that gay bar
down on Locust Street...
The Rainbow.
You know which one I'm
talking about, right? No.
Right. I'm gonna go
check it out, alone.
Why?
Well, because you'll be here.
And if, uh, the gang comes back,
they'll also be here,
and I'll be there, alone.
Right.
But you'll be here.
Great. Great.
All right, you go do that,
Okay. Yeah.
And, uh, remember, you're there
to look for a pot of gold.
Okay. Alone.
Yeah. You'll be there, alone.
Okay! Got it.
All right, well, that
just leaves you and me, and, uh,
we both know there's no pot
of gold at that gay bar.
So the question is...
what to do with the little liar.
We haven't made
a goddamn penny today.
We actually lost money,
with all the gas we burned
going back and forth.
Yeah, well, it's not my fault.
The business model's flawless.
If you knew how to drive
and you knew how to serve
a goddamn beer, we wouldn't
be in this mess.
Hmm.
All right. Mmm.
Okay, everybody out.
Get out. Let's go. Come on.
Go, go, go, go, go. You guys
are in the wrong demographic.
Where have you taken us?
Right. Yeah, I guess, uh,
we got so used to our routine of
picking people up and dropping
'em off outside of town
that we never even tried
to sell you people beer, did we?
They're too old, anyway.
Who's gonna watch 'em on a Web site?
That's true.
Yeah, you guys are a little too old
for our, uh...
So... Wallets and phones.
You know the drill.
I don't know why we don't
just do the car service thing.
People seem to be really needing
rides all over the town.
No, you know, that idea may work.
You think so?
Thank you. You're welcome.
Oh. B-But before we
pivot to that one,
um, Deandra,
you mind, uh, jumpin' out
to see about the gas cap?
I think I left it off.
Yeah. Oop.
Oh! Hey!
Oh, goddamn!
Goddamn it...!
What you did there, Frank, that's, like...
Very funny. Yeah. That bitch
was dragging us down. Yeah.
She was driving me crazy, man.
Oh.
Oh... shit. What?
She didn't put the gas cap on.
Oh, is it open for real?
Big-time.
Oh, shit. Yeah, let me
grab that real quick.
I got it.
No, no, no, no, n...
Aw, goddamn!
I can't believe Uber jacks up their
prices just because it's a holiday.
That's unbelie... It's a scam.
We should have been doing
that the entire time.
Are you kidding me?
That was my whole idea.
Dee, stop trying to take
credit for everything. Wait...
What is going on in here?
Weren't Mac and Charlie
taking care of the bar?
Yeah, they were.
- Why is the bar empty?
- It ain't empty.
What are you doing back here,
you piece of shit?
It's a long story.
The business hit a wall,
went up in smoke,
and then went under.
Why are you speaking
in metaphors?
It ain't a metaphor.
I fell asleep,
crashed into a wall,
the engine burst into flames,
and I had to drive it into a river.
Right.
What the hell is that?
♪ ...to keep this smile
from my face ♪
♪ Listen, Tony ♪
♪ I'm all over the place ♪
♪ Clowns to the left of me,
jokers to the right ♪
♪ Here I am, stuck in
the middle with you... ♪
Well, you may be a man.
You may be a leprechaun.
But only one thing's for sure:
You're in the wrong basement.
Goddamn it! No!
I'm gonna see if you bleed green.
No! No! No, no, no!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Charlie, Charlie,
what the hell is... Whoa, whoa. Hey!
What are you doing?
What does
it look like I'm doing?
It looks like you've tied
a little person to a chair
and you're gonna torture him.
No, I've tied
a leprechaun to a chair,
and, uh, yeah,
I was gonna cut him to pieces.
Charlie...
you been drinking
straight paint?
Yeah.
Charlie, he's not a leprechaun!
Do not hurt him! I repeat:
He is not a leprechaun! Oh, hey.
What is this?
Why are you covered in glitter?
I would love to answer
all of your questions,
but there is no time.
You see, I went to the Rainbow
to look for a pot of gold.
The gay bar? Oh.
Again, no questions.
And when I got back,
I found this bag...
full of wallets,
hidden where we keep the towels.
Why did you need towels?
Not answering questions, okay?
Because apparently this son
of a bitch is a pickpocket.
That's why he's been
lurking around Paddy's.
Oh! Well, that makes a lot
of sense, 'cause he kept saying,
like, "I'm a pickpocket. I'm
a pickpocket. Stop hurting me."
"I'm not a leprechaun." And
I just thought that was, like,
a metaphor for, you know,
"I-I am a leprechaun."
This little son of a bitch
has been picking pockets
at our bar every St. Paddy's Day
- for years.
- Well, we got a whole bag
full of wallets and phones, too.
You did? That's good. Because the
bar did not do so great. Yeah.
Turns out the Irish honor
system, that's not a thing.
Yeah, we were gonna
actually return the wallets
that we got, but, uh, Yeah.
Since no one seems to be...
being honorable, uh,
maybe we keep our wallets
and those and, you know, Yeah.
Chalk it up as a win. Yeah.
Oh, the luck of the Irish.
Let's not make
it a tradition, though.
Sure. Yeah, probably
better not to.
All right, well, what do we do
with this piece of shit?
Oh, shit, that leprechaun
just flew up a rainbow!
Stop drinking paint, Charlie.
Huh.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com